0	0	UNCERTAINTY	O
0	1	SURROUNDS	O
0	2	EC	ORGANIZATION
0	3	SUGAR	O
0	4	TENDER	O
0	5	RESULT	O
0	6	-	O
0	7	TRADE	O
0	8	Considerable	O
0	9	uncertainty	O
0	10	surrounds	O
0	11	the	O
0	12	outcome	O
0	13	of	O
0	14	today	O
0	15	'	O
0	16	s	O
0	17	EC	ORGANIZATION
0	18	white	O
0	19	sugar	O
0	20	tender	O
0	21	,	O
0	22	traders	O
0	23	here	O
0	24	said	O
0	25	,	O
0	26	noting	O
0	27	it	O
0	28	remains	O
0	29	overshadowed	O
0	30	by	O
0	31	European	O
0	32	operator	O
0	33	threats	O
0	34	to	O
0	35	move	O
0	36	over	O
0	37	800	O
0	38	,	O
0	39	000	O
0	40	tonnes	O
0	41	of	O
0	42	sugar	O
0	43	into	O
0	44	intervention	O
0	45	.	O


1	0	They	O
1	1	said	O
1	2	that	O
1	3	due	O
1	4	to	O
1	5	the	O
1	6	dispute	O
1	7	between	O
1	8	the	O
1	9	Commission	ORGANIZATION
1	10	and	O
1	11	producers	O
1	12	over	O
1	13	the	O
1	14	issue	O
1	15	,	O
1	16	it	O
1	17	is	O
1	18	not	O
1	19	clear	O
1	20	whether	O
1	21	the	O
1	22	Commission	ORGANIZATION
1	23	will	O
1	24	authorise	O
1	25	any	O
1	26	exports	O
1	27	at	O
1	28	all	O
1	29	or	O
1	30	grant	O
1	31	licences	O
1	32	on	O
1	33	a	O
1	34	large	O
1	35	tonnage	O
1	36	.	O


2	0	Earlier	O
2	1	,	O
2	2	traders	O
2	3	in	O
2	4	Paris	LOCATION
2	5	said	O
2	6	they	O
2	7	expected	O
2	8	the	O
2	9	Commission	ORGANIZATION
2	10	to	O
2	11	award	O
2	12	licences	O
2	13	for	O
2	14	around	O
2	15	50	O
2	16	,	O
2	17	000	O
2	18	tonnes	O
2	19	of	O
2	20	white	O
2	21	sugar	O
2	22	with	O
2	23	a	O
2	24	maximum	O
2	25	export	O
2	26	rebate	O
2	27	of	O
2	28	45	O
2	29	.	O
2	30	75	O
2	31	to	O
2	32	46	O
2	33	.	O
2	34	0	O
2	35	Ecus	O
2	36	.	O


3	0	BROWN	PERSON
3	1	&	O
3	2	lt	O
3	3	;	O
3	4	ABSB	O
3	5	>	O
3	6	SETS	O
3	7	SPLIT	O
3	8	,	O
3	9	TO	O
3	10	OFFER	O
3	11	SHARES	O
3	12	Alex	PERSON
3	13	.	O


4	0	Brown	PERSON
4	1	and	O
4	2	Sons	ORGANIZATION
4	3	Inc	ORGANIZATION
4	4	subsidiary	O
4	5	is	O
4	6	lead	O
4	7	underwriter	O
4	8	.	O


5	0	S	O
5	1	.	O
5	2	ATLANTIC	LOCATION
5	3	&	O
5	4	lt	O
5	5	;	O
5	6	SOAF	O
5	7	.	O
5	8	O	O
5	9	>,	O
5	10	INDEPENDENCE	O
5	11	&	O
5	12	lt	O
5	13	;	O
5	14	INHO	O
5	15	.	O
5	16	O	O
5	17	>	O
5	18	MERGE	O
5	19	South	ORGANIZATION
5	20	Atlantic	ORGANIZATION
5	21	Financial	ORGANIZATION
5	22	Corp	ORGANIZATION
5	23	said	O
5	24	it	O
5	25	has	O
5	26	agreed	O
5	27	in	O
5	28	principle	O
5	29	to	O
5	30	merge	O
5	31	with	O
5	32	Independence	ORGANIZATION
5	33	Holding	ORGANIZATION
5	34	Co	ORGANIZATION
5	35	into	O
5	36	a	O
5	37	new	O
5	38	company	O
5	39	to	O
5	40	be	O
5	41	called	O
5	42	SAFCO	ORGANIZATION
5	43	International	ORGANIZATION
5	44	Ltd	ORGANIZATION
5	45	.	O

6	0	It	O
6	1	said	O
6	2	each	O
6	3	South	ORGANIZATION
6	4	Atlantic	ORGANIZATION
6	5	share	O
6	6	would	O
6	7	be	O
6	8	exchanged	O
6	9	for	O
6	10	one	O
6	11	SAFCO	ORGANIZATION
6	12	share	O
6	13	and	O
6	14	each	O
6	15	Independence	ORGANIZATION
6	16	share	O
6	17	for	O
6	18	2	O
6	19	.	O
6	20	822	O
6	21	SAFCO	ORGANIZATION
6	22	shares	O
6	23	.	O

7	0	South	ORGANIZATION
7	1	Atlantic	ORGANIZATION
7	2	said	O
7	3	said	O
7	4	its	O
7	5	chairman	O
7	6	and	O
7	7	chief	O
7	8	executive	O
7	9	officer	O
7	10	Sheldon	PERSON
7	11	S	PERSON
7	12	.	O
7	13	Gordon	PERSON
7	14	would	O
7	15	have	O
7	16	the	O
7	17	same	O
7	18	posts	O
7	19	with	O
7	20	SAFCO	ORGANIZATION
7	21	and	O
7	22	Independence	O
7	23	president	O
7	24	Ronald	PERSON
7	25	G	PERSON
7	26	.	O
7	27	Strackbein	PERSON
7	28	would	O
7	29	be	O
7	30	president	O
7	31	of	O
7	32	SAFCO	ORGANIZATION
7	33	.	O

0	10	employee
0	20	employee
24	32	employee

8	0	PORT	ORGANIZATION
8	1	COSTS	O
8	2	The	O
8	3	New	ORGANIZATION
8	4	York	ORGANIZATION
8	5	Shipping	ORGANIZATION
8	6	Association	ORGANIZATION
8	7	and	ORGANIZATION
8	8	International	ORGANIZATION
8	9	Longshoremen	ORGANIZATION
8	10	'	ORGANIZATION
8	11	s	ORGANIZATION
8	12	Association	ORGANIZATION
8	13	said	O
8	14	they	O
8	15	agreed	O
8	16	to	O
8	17	cut	O
8	18	cargo	O
8	19	assessments	O
8	20	at	O
8	21	the	O
8	22	Port	LOCATION
8	23	of	LOCATION
8	24	New	LOCATION
8	25	York	LOCATION
8	26	and	O
8	27	New	LOCATION
8	28	Jersey	LOCATION
8	29	by	O
8	30	more	O
8	31	than	O
8	32	50	O
8	33	pct	O
8	34	on	O
8	35	some	O
8	36	labor	O
8	37	intensive	O
8	38	cargos	O
8	39	.	O

3	22	location
3	27	location

9	0	AGREEMENT	O
9	1	REACHED	O
9	2	IN	O
9	3	GREEK	O
9	4	ALUMINA	O
9	5	DEAL	O
9	6	WITH	O
9	7	MOSCOW	O
9	8	Greece	LOCATION
9	9	and	O
9	10	the	O
9	11	Soviet	LOCATION
9	12	Union	LOCATION
9	13	have	O
9	14	reached	O
9	15	agreement	O
9	16	in	O
9	17	Moscow	LOCATION
9	18	on	O
9	19	a	O
9	20	joint	O
9	21	venture	O
9	22	for	O
9	23	a	O
9	24	450	O
9	25	mln	O
9	26	dlr	O
9	27	alumina	O
9	28	plant	O
9	29	in	O
9	30	Greece	LOCATION
9	31	,	O
9	32	government	O
9	33	spokesman	O
9	34	Yannis	PERSON
9	35	Roubatis	PERSON
9	36	said	O
9	37	.	O

11	17	containsPlace

10	0	Roubatis	PERSON
10	1	told	O
10	2	reporters	O
10	3	the	O
10	4	Soviet	LOCATION
10	5	Union	LOCATION
10	6	agreed	O
10	7	to	O
10	8	buy	O
10	9	the	O
10	10	plant	O
10	11	'	O
10	12	s	O
10	13	entire	O
10	14	annual	O
10	15	output	O
10	16	of	O
10	17	600	O
10	18	,	O
10	19	000	O
10	20	tonnes	O
10	21	of	O
10	22	alumina	O
10	23	.	O


11	0	More	O
11	1	details	O
11	2	would	O
11	3	be	O
11	4	given	O
11	5	later	O
11	6	by	O
11	7	Greek	O
11	8	Industry	O
11	9	Undersecretary	O
11	10	George	PERSON
11	11	Petsos	PERSON
11	12	,	O
11	13	who	O
11	14	was	O
11	15	in	O
11	16	Moscow	LOCATION
11	17	.	O


12	0	GENCORP	ORGANIZATION
12	1	&	O
12	2	lt	O
12	3	;	O
12	4	GY	O
12	5	>	O
12	6	UNIT	O
12	7	COMPLETES	O
12	8	WOR	O
12	9	-	O
12	10	TV	O
12	11	SALE	O
12	12	GenCorp	ORGANIZATION
12	13	said	O
12	14	its	O
12	15	RKO	ORGANIZATION
12	16	General	ORGANIZATION
12	17	Inc	ORGANIZATION
12	18	subsidiary	O
12	19	completed	O
12	20	the	O
12	21	sale	O
12	22	of	O
12	23	WOR	ORGANIZATION
12	24	-	ORGANIZATION
12	25	TV	ORGANIZATION
12	26	to	O
12	27	MCA	ORGANIZATION
12	28	Inc	ORGANIZATION
12	29	&	O
12	30	lt	O
12	31	;	O
12	32	MCA	ORGANIZATION
12	33	>	O
12	34	for	O
12	35	387	O
12	36	mln	O
12	37	dlrs	O
12	38	.	O


14	0	The	O
14	1	closing	O
14	2	was	O
14	3	delayed	O
14	4	because	O
14	5	that	O
14	6	decision	O
14	7	was	O
14	8	appealed	O
14	9	by	O
14	10	four	O
14	11	parties	O
14	12	to	O
14	13	the	O
14	14	U	O
14	15	.	O
14	16	S	O
14	17	.	O
14	18	Court	ORGANIZATION
14	19	of	ORGANIZATION
14	20	Appeals	ORGANIZATION
14	21	,	O
14	22	GenCorp	ORGANIZATION
14	23	explained	O
14	24	.	O


15	0	WOR	ORGANIZATION
15	1	-	ORGANIZATION
15	2	TV	ORGANIZATION
15	3	is	O
15	4	based	O
15	5	in	O
15	6	Secaucus	LOCATION
15	7	,	O
15	8	N	O
15	9	.	O
15	10	J	O
15	11	.,	O
15	12	GenCorp	ORGANIZATION
15	13	said	O
15	14	.	O

0	6	location

16	0	Earlier	O
16	1	today	O
16	2	,	O
16	3	&	O
16	4	lt	O
16	5	;	O
16	6	General	ORGANIZATION
16	7	Partners	ORGANIZATION
16	8	>	O
16	9	said	O
16	10	it	O
16	11	was	O
16	12	prepared	O
16	13	to	O
16	14	raise	O
16	15	its	O
16	16	bid	O
16	17	to	O
16	18	110	O
16	19	dlrs	O
16	20	per	O
16	21	share	O
16	22	,	O
16	23	or	O
16	24	even	O
16	25	more	O
16	26	,	O
16	27	in	O
16	28	its	O
16	29	bid	O
16	30	for	O
16	31	GenCorp	ORGANIZATION
16	32	.	O


17	0	INVESTMENT	O
17	1	FIRM	O
17	2	RAISES	O
17	3	TVX	O
17	4	&	O
17	5	lt	O
17	6	;	O
17	7	TVXG	O
17	8	.	O
17	9	O	O
17	10	>	O
17	11	STAKE	ORGANIZATION
17	12	WEDGE	ORGANIZATION
17	13	Group	ORGANIZATION
17	14	Inc	ORGANIZATION
17	15	,	O
17	16	a	O
17	17	Houston	LOCATION
17	18	investment	O
17	19	firm	O
17	20	,	O
17	21	said	O
17	22	it	O
17	23	raised	O
17	24	its	O
17	25	stake	O
17	26	in	O
17	27	TVX	ORGANIZATION
17	28	Broadcast	ORGANIZATION
17	29	Group	ORGANIZATION
17	30	Inc	ORGANIZATION
17	31	to	O
17	32	682	O
17	33	,	O
17	34	419	O
17	35	shares	O
17	36	,	O
17	37	or	O
17	38	15	O
17	39	.	O
17	40	1	O
17	41	pct	O
17	42	of	O
17	43	the	O
17	44	total	O
17	45	outstanding	O
17	46	common	O
17	47	stock	O
17	48	,	O
17	49	from	O
17	50	559	O
17	51	,	O
17	52	219	O
17	53	shares	O
17	54	,	O
17	55	or	O
17	56	12	O
17	57	.	O
17	58	4	O
17	59	pct	O
17	60	.	O

11	17	location
27	0	parentOrganization

18	0	MOODY	ORGANIZATION
18	1	'	O
18	2	S	O
18	3	MAY	O
18	4	DOWNGRADE	O
18	5	PIEDMONT	LOCATION
18	6	AVIATION	O
18	7	&	O
18	8	lt	O
18	9	;	O
18	10	PIE	O
18	11	>	O
18	12	Moody	ORGANIZATION
18	13	'	ORGANIZATION
18	14	s	ORGANIZATION
18	15	Investors	ORGANIZATION
18	16	Service	ORGANIZATION
18	17	Inc	ORGANIZATION
18	18	said	O
18	19	it	O
18	20	may	O
18	21	downgrade	O
18	22	120	O
18	23	mln	O
18	24	dlrs	O
18	25	of	O
18	26	debt	O
18	27	of	O
18	28	Piedmont	ORGANIZATION
18	29	Aviation	ORGANIZATION
18	30	Inc	ORGANIZATION
18	31	because	O
18	32	of	O
18	33	the	O
18	34	airline	O
18	35	'	O
18	36	s	O
18	37	agreement	O
18	38	to	O
18	39	be	O
18	40	acquired	O
18	41	by	O
18	42	USAir	ORGANIZATION
18	43	Group	ORGANIZATION
18	44	Inc	ORGANIZATION
18	45	&	ORGANIZATION
18	46	lt	ORGANIZATION
18	47	;	O
18	48	U	O
18	49	>.	O

28	42	parentOrganization


20	0	The	O
20	1	case	O
20	2	involving	O
20	3	the	O
20	4	Toyota	ORGANIZATION
20	5	Shoji	ORGANIZATION
20	6	Company	ORGANIZATION
20	7	was	O
20	8	highlighted	O
20	9	when	O
20	10	its	O
20	11	32	O
20	12	-	O
20	13	year	O
20	14	-	O
20	15	old	O
20	16	Chairman	O
20	17	Kazuo	PERSON
20	18	Nagano	PERSON
20	19	was	O
20	20	stabbed	O
20	21	to	O
20	22	death	O
20	23	here	O
20	24	in	O
20	25	public	O
20	26	view	O
20	27	in	O
20	28	June	O
20	29	,	O
20	30	1985	O
20	31	.	O

4	17	employee

21	0	Police	O
21	1	said	O
21	2	the	O
21	3	five	O
21	4	arrested	O
21	5	on	O
21	6	charge	O
21	7	of	O
21	8	fraud	O
21	9	today	O
21	10	included	O
21	11	Hiroshi	PERSON
21	12	Ishikawa	PERSON
21	13	,	O
21	14	47	O
21	15	,	O
21	16	former	O
21	17	Toyota	ORGANIZATION
21	18	Shoji	ORGANIZATION
21	19	president	O
21	20	,	O
21	21	and	O
21	22	a	O
21	23	sixth	O
21	24	former	O
21	25	executive	O
21	26	was	O
21	27	placed	O
21	28	on	O
21	29	a	O
21	30	wanted	O
21	31	list	O
21	32	.	O

17	11	employee

22	0	They	O
22	1	were	O
22	2	suspected	O
22	3	of	O
22	4	having	O
22	5	collaborated	O
22	6	with	O
22	7	the	O
22	8	late	O
22	9	Nagano	LOCATION
22	10	in	O
22	11	swindling	O
22	12	about	O
22	13	1	O
22	14	.	O
22	15	5	O
22	16	billion	O
22	17	yen	O
22	18	from	O
22	19	about	O
22	20	450	O
22	21	people	O
22	22	in	O
22	23	Osaka	LOCATION
22	24	and	O
22	25	nearby	O
22	26	Kobe	LOCATION
22	27	during	O
22	28	a	O
22	29	six	O
22	30	month	O
22	31	period	O
22	32	just	O
22	33	before	O
22	34	the	O
22	35	firm	O
22	36	'	O
22	37	s	O
22	38	bankruptcy	O
22	39	,	O
22	40	they	O
22	41	said	O
22	42	.	O


23	0	COLGATE	ORGANIZATION
23	1	-	O
23	2	PALMOLIVE	ORGANIZATION
23	3	CO	O
23	4	&	O
23	5	lt	O
23	6	;	O
23	7	CL	O
23	8	>	O
23	9	SETS	O
23	10	PAYOUT	O
23	11	Qtrly	O
23	12	div	O
23	13	34	O
23	14	cts	O
23	15	vs	O
23	16	34	O
23	17	cts	O
23	18	Pay	O
23	19	May	O
23	20	15	O
23	21	Record	O
23	22	April	O
23	23	24	O


24	0	ZAMBIA	LOCATION
24	1	CUTS	O
24	2	PRICES	O
24	3	AS	O
24	4	TROOPS	O
24	5	PATROL	O
24	6	COPPERBELT	O
24	7	The	O
24	8	Zambian	O
24	9	government	O
24	10	today	O
24	11	announced	O
24	12	minor	O
24	13	price	O
24	14	cuts	O
24	15	for	O
24	16	essential	O
24	17	commodities	O
24	18	as	O
24	19	part	O
24	20	of	O
24	21	its	O
24	22	new	O
24	23	economic	O
24	24	strategy	O
24	25	,	O
24	26	while	O
24	27	police	O
24	28	and	O
24	29	troops	O
24	30	patrolled	O
24	31	the	O
24	32	northern	O
24	33	Copperbelt	LOCATION
24	34	to	O
24	35	prevent	O
24	36	any	O
24	37	outbreaks	O
24	38	of	O
24	39	rioting	O
24	40	.	O

0	33	containsPlace

25	0	The	O
25	1	revaluation	O
25	2	formed	O
25	3	part	O
25	4	of	O
25	5	a	O
25	6	new	O
25	7	go	O
25	8	-	O
25	9	it	O
25	10	-	O
25	11	alone	O
25	12	economic	O
25	13	strategy	O
25	14	which	O
25	15	Kaunda	PERSON
25	16	adopted	O
25	17	to	O
25	18	replace	O
25	19	Zambia	LOCATION
25	20	'	O
25	21	s	O
25	22	IMF	ORGANIZATION
25	23	austerity	O
25	24	program	O
25	25	.	O

15	19	nationality

26	0	EMERY	O
26	1	&	O
26	2	lt	O
26	3	;	O
26	4	EAF	O
26	5	>	O
26	6	PLANS	O
26	7	PUROLATOR	O
26	8	&	O
26	9	lt	O
26	10	;	O
26	11	PCC	O
26	12	>	O
26	13	ASSET	O
26	14	SALES	O
26	15	Emery	ORGANIZATION
26	16	Air	ORGANIZATION
26	17	Frieght	ORGANIZATION
26	18	Corp	ORGANIZATION
26	19	,	O
26	20	which	O
26	21	has	O
26	22	launched	O
26	23	a	O
26	24	40	O
26	25	dlr	O
26	26	a	O
26	27	share	O
26	28	tender	O
26	29	offer	O
26	30	for	O
26	31	83	O
26	32	pct	O
26	33	of	O
26	34	Purolator	ORGANIZATION
26	35	Courier	ORGANIZATION
26	36	Corp	ORGANIZATION
26	37	,	O
26	38	said	O
26	39	it	O
26	40	would	O
26	41	sell	O
26	42	some	O
26	43	Purolator	ORGANIZATION
26	44	assets	O
26	45	to	O
26	46	help	O
26	47	pay	O
26	48	the	O
26	49	estimated	O
26	50	265	O
26	51	mln	O
26	52	dlr	O
26	53	cost	O
26	54	of	O
26	55	the	O
26	56	stock	O
26	57	purchase	O
26	58	deal	O
26	59	.	O

27	0	In	O
27	1	a	O
27	2	filing	O
27	3	with	O
27	4	the	O
27	5	Securities	ORGANIZATION
27	6	and	ORGANIZATION
27	7	Exchange	ORGANIZATION
27	8	Commission	ORGANIZATION
27	9	,	O
27	10	Emery	PERSON
27	11	said	O
27	12	it	O
27	13	would	O
27	14	sell	O
27	15	or	O
27	16	lease	O
27	17	Purolator	ORGANIZATION
27	18	'	O
27	19	s	O
27	20	air	O
27	21	hub	O
27	22	in	O
27	23	Indianapolis	LOCATION
27	24	,	O
27	25	Ind	O
27	26	.,	O
27	27	which	O
27	28	is	O
27	29	currently	O
27	30	under	O
27	31	construction	O
27	32	,	O
27	33	and	O
27	34	would	O
27	35	divest	O
27	36	Purolator	ORGANIZATION
27	37	'	O
27	38	s	O
27	39	Stant	ORGANIZATION
27	40	Inc	ORGANIZATION
27	41	subsidiary	O
27	42	.	O

17	10	employee
17	23	location
39	17	parentOrganization
39	36	parentOrganization

28	0	Emery	PERSON
28	1	said	O
28	2	it	O
28	3	would	O
28	4	operate	O
28	5	Purolator	ORGANIZATION
28	6	as	O
28	7	a	O
28	8	subsidiary	O
28	9	if	O
28	10	it	O
28	11	succeeded	O
28	12	in	O
28	13	the	O
28	14	takever	O
28	15	,	O
28	16	but	O
28	17	would	O
28	18	integrate	O
28	19	its	O
28	20	air	O
28	21	hub	O
28	22	.	O

5	0	employee

29	0	It	O
29	1	said	O
29	2	it	O
29	3	plans	O
29	4	to	O
29	5	finance	O
29	6	its	O
29	7	stock	O
29	8	purchases	O
29	9	with	O
29	10	borrowings	O
29	11	from	O
29	12	Chemical	ORGANIZATION
29	13	Bank	ORGANIZATION
29	14	,	O
29	15	Morgan	ORGANIZATION
29	16	Guaranty	ORGANIZATION
29	17	Trust	ORGANIZATION
29	18	Co	ORGANIZATION
29	19	of	O
29	20	New	LOCATION
29	21	York	LOCATION
29	22	,	O
29	23	Bankers	ORGANIZATION
29	24	Trust	ORGANIZATION
29	25	Co	ORGANIZATION
29	26	and	O
29	27	Salomon	ORGANIZATION
29	28	Brothers	ORGANIZATION
29	29	Holding	ORGANIZATION
29	30	Co	ORGANIZATION
29	31	Inc	ORGANIZATION
29	32	,	O
29	33	the	O
29	34	parent	O
29	35	of	O
29	36	Salmon	ORGANIZATION
29	37	Brothers	ORGANIZATION
29	38	Inc	ORGANIZATION
29	39	,	O
29	40	Emery	PERSON
29	41	'	O
29	42	s	O
29	43	financial	O
29	44	advisor	O
29	45	.	O

15	20	location
36	27	parentOrganization

30	0	GERMAN	O
30	1	MONEY	O
30	2	SUPPLY	O
30	3	GROWTH	O
30	4	SLOWS	O
30	5	IN	O
30	6	FEBRUARY	O
30	7	West	LOCATION
30	8	Germany	LOCATION
30	9	'	O
30	10	s	O
30	11	money	O
30	12	supply	O
30	13	growth	O
30	14	slowed	O
30	15	in	O
30	16	February	O
30	17	after	O
30	18	January	O
30	19	'	O
30	20	s	O
30	21	sharp	O
30	22	rise	O
30	23	but	O
30	24	the	O
30	25	trend	O
30	26	is	O
30	27	still	O
30	28	definitely	O
30	29	upward	O
30	30	,	O
30	31	the	O
30	32	Bundesbank	ORGANIZATION
30	33	said	O
30	34	in	O
30	35	a	O
30	36	statement	O
30	37	.	O

32	7	location

31	0	BALL	O
31	1	CORP	O
31	2	&	O
31	3	lt	O
31	4	;	O
31	5	BLL	O
31	6	>	O
31	7	COMPLETES	O
31	8	ACQUISITION	O
31	9	Ball	ORGANIZATION
31	10	Corp	ORGANIZATION
31	11	said	O
31	12	it	O
31	13	completed	O
31	14	the	O
31	15	purchase	O
31	16	of	O
31	17	privately	O
31	18	held	O
31	19	&	O
31	20	lt	O
31	21	;	O
31	22	Verac	ORGANIZATION
31	23	Inc	ORGANIZATION
31	24	>,	O
31	25	a	O
31	26	San	LOCATION
31	27	Diego	LOCATION
31	28	defense	O
31	29	systems	O
31	30	and	O
31	31	software	O
31	32	development	O
31	33	company	O
31	34	.	O

22	9	parentOrganization
22	26	location

32	0	DEAN	O
32	1	FOODS	O
32	2	&	O
32	3	lt	O
32	4	;	O
32	5	DF	O
32	6	>	O
32	7	SEES	O
32	8	STRONG	O
32	9	4TH	O
32	10	QTR	O
32	11	EARNINGS	O
32	12	Dean	ORGANIZATION
32	13	Foods	ORGANIZATION
32	14	Co	ORGANIZATION
32	15	expects	O
32	16	earnings	O
32	17	for	O
32	18	the	O
32	19	fourth	O
32	20	quarter	O
32	21	ending	O
32	22	May	O
32	23	30	O
32	24	to	O
32	25	exceed	O
32	26	those	O
32	27	of	O
32	28	the	O
32	29	same	O
32	30	year	O
32	31	-	O
32	32	ago	O
32	33	period	O
32	34	,	O
32	35	Chairman	O
32	36	Kenneth	PERSON
32	37	Douglas	PERSON
32	38	told	O
32	39	analysts	O
32	40	.	O

12	36	employee

33	0	In	O
33	1	1988	O
33	2	,	O
33	3	Douglas	PERSON
33	4	said	O
33	5	Dean	PERSON
33	6	should	O
33	7	experience	O
33	8	"	O
33	9	a	O
33	10	20	O
33	11	pct	O
33	12	improvement	O
33	13	in	O
33	14	our	O
33	15	bottom	O
33	16	line	O
33	17	from	O
33	18	effects	O
33	19	of	O
33	20	the	O
33	21	tax	O
33	22	reform	O
33	23	act	O
33	24	alone	O
33	25	."	O


34	0	President	O
34	1	Howard	PERSON
34	2	Dean	PERSON
34	3	said	O
34	4	in	O
34	5	fiscal	O
34	6	1988	O
34	7	the	O
34	8	company	O
34	9	will	O
34	10	derive	O
34	11	benefits	O
34	12	of	O
34	13	various	O
34	14	dairy	O
34	15	and	O
34	16	frozen	O
34	17	vegetable	O
34	18	acquisitions	O
34	19	from	O
34	20	Ryan	ORGANIZATION
34	21	Milk	ORGANIZATION
34	22	to	O
34	23	the	O
34	24	Larsen	ORGANIZATION
34	25	Co	ORGANIZATION
34	26	.	O
34	27	Dean	PERSON
34	28	also	O
34	29	said	O
34	30	the	O
34	31	company	O
34	32	will	O
34	33	benefit	O
34	34	from	O
34	35	its	O
34	36	acquisition	O
34	37	in	O
34	38	late	O
34	39	December	O
34	40	of	O
34	41	Elgin	ORGANIZATION
34	42	Blenders	ORGANIZATION
34	43	Inc	ORGANIZATION
34	44	,	O
34	45	West	LOCATION
34	46	Chicago	LOCATION
34	47	.	O

41	45	location

35	0	Foods	ORGANIZATION
35	1	Ltd	ORGANIZATION
35	2	,	O
35	3	a	O
35	4	United	LOCATION
35	5	Kingdom	LOCATION
35	6	blender	O
35	7	,	O
35	8	and	O
35	9	has	O
35	10	licensing	O
35	11	arrangements	O
35	12	in	O
35	13	Australia	LOCATION
35	14	,	O
35	15	Canada	LOCATION
35	16	,	O
35	17	Brazil	LOCATION
35	18	and	O
35	19	Japan	LOCATION
35	20	.	O

0	4	location

36	0	"	O
36	1	It	O
36	2	provides	O
36	3	ann	O
36	4	entry	O
36	5	to	O
36	6	McDonalds	ORGANIZATION
36	7	Corp	ORGANIZATION
36	8	&	ORGANIZATION
36	9	lt	ORGANIZATION
36	10	;	O
36	11	MCD	O
36	12	>	O
36	13	we	O
36	14	'	O
36	15	ve	O
36	16	been	O
36	17	after	O
36	18	for	O
36	19	years	O
36	20	,"	O
36	21	Douglas	PERSON
36	22	told	O
36	23	analysts	O
36	24	.	O

6	21	employee

37	0	&	O
37	1	lt	O
37	2	;	O
37	3	THL	ORGANIZATION
37	4	HOLDINGS	ORGANIZATION
37	5	INC	ORGANIZATION
37	6	>	O
37	7	YEAR	O
37	8	JAN	O
37	9	31	O
37	10	NET	O
37	11	Oper	O
37	12	net	O
37	13	94	O
37	14	.	O
37	15	4	O
37	16	mln	O
37	17	vs	O
37	18	74	O
37	19	.	O
37	20	1	O
37	21	mln	O
37	22	Revs	O
37	23	1	O
37	24	.	O
37	25	3	O
37	26	bilion	O
37	27	vs	O
37	28	1	O
37	29	.	O
37	30	2	O
37	31	billion	O
37	32	NOTE	O
37	33	:	O
37	34	THL	ORGANIZATION
37	35	is	O
37	36	parent	O
37	37	to	O
37	38	SCOA	ORGANIZATION
37	39	Industries	ORGANIZATION
37	40	Inc	ORGANIZATION
37	41	,	O
37	42	acquired	O
37	43	in	O
37	44	a	O
37	45	leveraged	O
37	46	buyout	O
37	47	in	O
37	48	December	O
37	49	1985	O
37	50	.	O

38	34	parentOrganization

38	0	At	O
38	1	a	O
38	2	meeting	O
38	3	this	O
38	4	week	O
38	5	in	O
38	6	Paris	LOCATION
38	7	,	O
38	8	senior	O
38	9	government	O
38	10	officials	O
38	11	from	O
38	12	major	O
38	13	nations	O
38	14	are	O
38	15	considering	O
38	16	an	O
38	17	Organisation	ORGANIZATION
38	18	for	ORGANIZATION
38	19	Economic	ORGANIZATION
38	20	Cooperation	ORGANIZATION
38	21	and	ORGANIZATION
38	22	Development	ORGANIZATION
38	23	(	O
38	24	OECD	ORGANIZATION
38	25	)	O
38	26	staff	O
38	27	report	O
38	28	that	O
38	29	forecasts	O
38	30	a	O
38	31	continuing	O
38	32	large	O
38	33	Japanese	O
38	34	trade	O
38	35	surplus	O
38	36	,	O
38	37	they	O
38	38	said	O
38	39	.	O

17	24	brand

39	0	As	O
39	1	a	O
39	2	solution	O
39	3	,	O
39	4	the	O
39	5	OECD	ORGANIZATION
39	6	staff	O
39	7	has	O
39	8	urged	O
39	9	Japan	LOCATION
39	10	to	O
39	11	redirect	O
39	12	its	O
39	13	export	O
39	14	-	O
39	15	driven	O
39	16	economy	O
39	17	,	O
39	18	boosting	O
39	19	domestic	O
39	20	demand	O
39	21	and	O
39	22	imports	O
39	23	by	O
39	24	adopting	O
39	25	a	O
39	26	more	O
39	27	flexible	O
39	28	fiscal	O
39	29	policy	O
39	30	,	O
39	31	they	O
39	32	said	O
39	33	.	O


40	0	The	O
40	1	United	LOCATION
40	2	States	LOCATION
40	3	,	O
40	4	which	O
40	5	until	O
40	6	recently	O
40	7	has	O
40	8	been	O
40	9	reluctant	O
40	10	to	O
40	11	criticize	O
40	12	Japan	LOCATION
40	13	'	O
40	14	s	O
40	15	fiscal	O
40	16	stance	O
40	17	,	O
40	18	joined	O
40	19	in	O
40	20	the	O
40	21	attack	O
40	22	,	O
40	23	he	O
40	24	said	O
40	25	.	O


41	0	Japan	LOCATION
41	1	cannot	O
41	2	tolerate	O
41	3	a	O
41	4	further	O
41	5	rise	O
41	6	of	O
41	7	the	O
41	8	yen	O
41	9	,	O
41	10	Foreign	O
41	11	Minister	O
41	12	Tadashi	PERSON
41	13	Kuranari	PERSON
41	14	said	O
41	15	recently	O
41	16	.	O

12	0	nationality

42	0	At	O
42	1	a	O
42	2	meeting	O
42	3	in	O
42	4	Paris	LOCATION
42	5	last	O
42	6	month	O
42	7	,	O
42	8	Britain	LOCATION
42	9	,	O
42	10	Canada	LOCATION
42	11	,	O
42	12	France	LOCATION
42	13	,	O
42	14	Japan	LOCATION
42	15	,	O
42	16	the	O
42	17	United	LOCATION
42	18	States	LOCATION
42	19	and	O
42	20	West	LOCATION
42	21	Germany	LOCATION
42	22	,	O
42	23	agreed	O
42	24	to	O
42	25	cooperate	O
42	26	to	O
42	27	hold	O
42	28	currencies	O
42	29	at	O
42	30	around	O
42	31	current	O
42	32	levels	O
42	33	.	O

12	4	containsPlace

43	0	Japan	LOCATION
43	1	wanted	O
43	2	the	O
43	3	Paris	LOCATION
43	4	communique	O
43	5	to	O
43	6	imply	O
43	7	a	O
43	8	higher	O
43	9	value	O
43	10	for	O
43	11	the	O
43	12	dollar	O
43	13	,	O
43	14	perhaps	O
43	15	by	O
43	16	substituting	O
43	17	the	O
43	18	word	O
43	19	"	O
43	20	recent	O
43	21	"	O
43	22	for	O
43	23	"	O
43	24	current	O
43	25	,"	O
43	26	while	O
43	27	the	O
43	28	United	LOCATION
43	29	States	LOCATION
43	30	wanted	O
43	31	it	O
43	32	to	O
43	33	more	O
43	34	clearly	O
43	35	point	O
43	36	to	O
43	37	the	O
43	38	dollar	O
43	39	'	O
43	40	s	O
43	41	weaker	O
43	42	levels	O
43	43	now	O
43	44	,	O
43	45	perhaps	O
43	46	by	O
43	47	use	O
43	48	of	O
43	49	the	O
43	50	word	O
43	51	"	O
43	52	present	O
43	53	,"	O
43	54	they	O
43	55	said	O
43	56	.	O


44	0	Japan	LOCATION
44	1	has	O
44	2	also	O
44	3	attacked	O
44	4	OECD	ORGANIZATION
44	5	forecasts	O
44	6	,	O
44	7	which	O
44	8	it	O
44	9	says	O
44	10	do	O
44	11	not	O
44	12	take	O
44	13	account	O
44	14	of	O
44	15	the	O
44	16	structural	O
44	17	changes	O
44	18	in	O
44	19	the	O
44	20	Japanese	O
44	21	economy	O
44	22	that	O
44	23	will	O
44	24	be	O
44	25	triggered	O
44	26	by	O
44	27	the	O
44	28	strong	O
44	29	yen	O
44	30	.	O


45	0	FERRUZZI	ORGANIZATION
45	1	NEGOTIATING	O
45	2	EUROPEAN	O
45	3	ACQUISITION	O
45	4	Italy	LOCATION
45	5	'	O
45	6	s	O
45	7	&	O
45	8	lt	O
45	9	;	O
45	10	Gruppo	ORGANIZATION
45	11	Ferruzzi	ORGANIZATION
45	12	>	O
45	13	is	O
45	14	in	O
45	15	the	O
45	16	advanced	O
45	17	stages	O
45	18	of	O
45	19	negotiations	O
45	20	that	O
45	21	could	O
45	22	result	O
45	23	in	O
45	24	an	O
45	25	acquisition	O
45	26	worth	O
45	27	"	O
45	28	some	O
45	29	hundreds	O
45	30	of	O
45	31	billions	O
45	32	of	O
45	33	lire	O
45	34	"	O
45	35	in	O
45	36	the	O
45	37	European	O
45	38	agro	O
45	39	-	O
45	40	industrial	O
45	41	sector	O
45	42	,	O
45	43	a	O
45	44	company	O
45	45	spokesman	O
45	46	told	O
45	47	Reuters	ORGANIZATION
45	48	.	O

0	4	location
10	4	location

46	0	The	O
46	1	spokesman	O
46	2	declined	O
46	3	to	O
46	4	identify	O
46	5	the	O
46	6	other	O
46	7	party	O
46	8	or	O
46	9	parties	O
46	10	involved	O
46	11	in	O
46	12	talks	O
46	13	,	O
46	14	or	O
46	15	whether	O
46	16	a	O
46	17	complete	O
46	18	takeover	O
46	19	was	O
46	20	under	O
46	21	discussion	O
46	22	,	O
46	23	but	O
46	24	said	O
46	25	an	O
46	26	Italian	O
46	27	newspaper	O
46	28	report	O
46	29	that	O
46	30	Ferruzzi	ORGANIZATION
46	31	was	O
46	32	studying	O
46	33	the	O
46	34	possibility	O
46	35	of	O
46	36	advancing	O
46	37	an	O
46	38	offer	O
46	39	for	O
46	40	13	O
46	41	European	O
46	42	cereal	O
46	43	processing	O
46	44	plants	O
46	45	owned	O
46	46	by	O
46	47	the	O
46	48	U	O
46	49	.	O
46	50	S	O
46	51	.	O
46	52	Group	ORGANIZATION
46	53	CPC	ORGANIZATION
46	54	International	ORGANIZATION
46	55	Inc	ORGANIZATION
46	56	&	ORGANIZATION
46	57	lt	ORGANIZATION
46	58	;	O
46	59	CPC	ORGANIZATION
46	60	.	O
46	61	N	O
46	62	>	O
46	63	was	O
46	64	incorrect	O
46	65	.	O


47	0	The	O
47	1	spokesman	O
47	2	,	O
47	3	responding	O
47	4	to	O
47	5	a	O
47	6	report	O
47	7	in	O
47	8	the	O
47	9	Italian	O
47	10	economic	O
47	11	daily	O
47	12	Il	O
47	13	Sole	O
47	14	-	O
47	15	24	O
47	16	Ore	O
47	17	that	O
47	18	Ferruzzi	ORGANIZATION
47	19	was	O
47	20	considering	O
47	21	a	O
47	22	possible	O
47	23	bid	O
47	24	for	O
47	25	the	O
47	26	CPC	ORGANIZATION
47	27	plants	O
47	28	,	O
47	29	told	O
47	30	Reuters	ORGANIZATION
47	31	his	O
47	32	company	O
47	33	hoped	O
47	34	to	O
47	35	conclude	O
47	36	the	O
47	37	talks	O
47	38	currently	O
47	39	underway	O
47	40	in	O
47	41	a	O
47	42	couple	O
47	43	of	O
47	44	months	O
47	45	.	O

26	18	parentOrganization

48	0	The	O
48	1	spokesman	O
48	2	said	O
48	3	that	O
48	4	since	O
48	5	the	O
48	6	U	O
48	7	.	O
48	8	K	O
48	9	.	O
48	10	Government	O
48	11	last	O
48	12	month	O
48	13	blocked	O
48	14	Ferruzzi	ORGANIZATION
48	15	'	O
48	16	s	O
48	17	bid	O
48	18	to	O
48	19	acquire	O
48	20	&	O
48	21	lt	O
48	22	;	O
48	23	British	ORGANIZATION
48	24	Sugar	ORGANIZATION
48	25	Plc	ORGANIZATION
48	26	>,	O
48	27	the	O
48	28	company	O
48	29	had	O
48	30	been	O
48	31	looking	O
48	32	at	O
48	33	other	O
48	34	investment	O
48	35	opportunities	O
48	36	.	O


49	0	IBC	ORGANIZATION
49	1	PRESIDENT	O
49	2	TO	O
49	3	ATTEND	O
49	4	MANAGUA	LOCATION
49	5	COFFEE	O
49	6	MEETING	O
49	7	Brazilian	O
49	8	Coffee	ORGANIZATION
49	9	Institute	ORGANIZATION
49	10	(	O
49	11	IBC	ORGANIZATION
49	12	)	O
49	13	president	O
49	14	Jorio	PERSON
49	15	Dauster	PERSON
49	16	said	O
49	17	he	O
49	18	will	O
49	19	attend	O
49	20	a	O
49	21	meeting	O
49	22	in	O
49	23	Managua	LOCATION
49	24	this	O
49	25	weekend	O
49	26	.	O

8	11	brand
8	14	employee

50	0	He	O
50	1	told	O
50	2	Reuters	ORGANIZATION
50	3	by	O
50	4	telephone	O
50	5	from	O
50	6	Brasilia	LOCATION
50	7	that	O
50	8	the	O
50	9	meeting	O
50	10	,	O
50	11	involving	O
50	12	Brazil	LOCATION
50	13	,	O
50	14	Colombia	LOCATION
50	15	and	O
50	16	Central	O
50	17	American	O
50	18	coffee	O
50	19	producers	O
50	20	,	O
50	21	will	O
50	22	be	O
50	23	strictly	O
50	24	to	O
50	25	review	O
50	26	the	O
50	27	coffee	O
50	28	market	O
50	29	situation	O
50	30	.	O

12	6	containsPlace

51	0	U	O
51	1	.	O
51	2	S	O
51	3	.	O
51	4	CORPORATE	O
51	5	FINANCE	O
51	6	-	O
51	7	NEW	LOCATION
51	8	ZEALAND	LOCATION
51	9	DLR	O
51	10	FRNS	O
51	11	Floating	O
51	12	-	O
51	13	rate	O
51	14	notes	O
51	15	denominated	O
51	16	in	O
51	17	a	O
51	18	foreign	O
51	19	currency	O
51	20	,	O
51	21	a	O
51	22	relatively	O
51	23	new	O
51	24	wrinkle	O
51	25	on	O
51	26	Wall	LOCATION
51	27	Street	LOCATION
51	28	,	O
51	29	will	O
51	30	probably	O
51	31	be	O
51	32	issued	O
51	33	infrequently	O
51	34	because	O
51	35	the	O
51	36	so	O
51	37	-	O
51	38	called	O
51	39	"	O
51	40	window	O
51	41	of	O
51	42	opportunity	O
51	43	"	O
51	44	opens	O
51	45	and	O
51	46	closes	O
51	47	quickly	O
51	48	,	O
51	49	traders	O
51	50	say	O
51	51	.	O


52	0	On	O
52	1	Thursday	O
52	2	,	O
52	3	Bear	ORGANIZATION
52	4	,	ORGANIZATION
52	5	Stearns	ORGANIZATION
52	6	and	ORGANIZATION
52	7	Co	ORGANIZATION
52	8	sole	O
52	9	-	O
52	10	managed	O
52	11	a	O
52	12	100	O
52	13	mln	O
52	14	New	LOCATION
52	15	Zealand	LOCATION
52	16	dlr	O
52	17	offering	O
52	18	of	O
52	19	three	O
52	20	-	O
52	21	year	O
52	22	floating	O
52	23	-	O
52	24	rate	O
52	25	notes	O
52	26	issued	O
52	27	by	O
52	28	Ford	ORGANIZATION
52	29	Motor	ORGANIZATION
52	30	Credit	ORGANIZATION
52	31	Co	ORGANIZATION
52	32	,	O
52	33	a	O
52	34	unit	O
52	35	of	O
52	36	Ford	ORGANIZATION
52	37	Motor	ORGANIZATION
52	38	Co	ORGANIZATION
52	39	&	O
52	40	lt	O
52	41	;	O
52	42	F	O
52	43	>.	O

28	36	parentOrganization

53	0	This	O
53	1	followed	O
53	2	by	O
53	3	a	O
53	4	week	O
53	5	another	O
53	6	Bear	ORGANIZATION
53	7	Stearns	ORGANIZATION
53	8	-	O
53	9	led	O
53	10	offering	O
53	11	of	O
53	12	the	O
53	13	same	O
53	14	amount	O
53	15	of	O
53	16	New	LOCATION
53	17	Zealand	LOCATION
53	18	dollar	O
53	19	notes	O
53	20	for	O
53	21	Dow	ORGANIZATION
53	22	Chemical	ORGANIZATION
53	23	Co	ORGANIZATION
53	24	&	O
53	25	lt	O
53	26	;	O
53	27	DOW	O
53	28	>.	O


54	0	But	O
54	1	the	O
54	2	Ford	ORGANIZATION
54	3	Credit	ORGANIZATION
54	4	notes	O
54	5	and	O
54	6	Friday	O
54	7	'	O
54	8	s	O
54	9	offering	O
54	10	of	O
54	11	130	O
54	12	mln	O
54	13	New	LOCATION
54	14	Zealand	LOCATION
54	15	dlrs	O
54	16	of	O
54	17	floating	O
54	18	-	O
54	19	rate	O
54	20	notes	O
54	21	due	O
54	22	1990	O
54	23	issued	O
54	24	by	O
54	25	General	ORGANIZATION
54	26	Electric	ORGANIZATION
54	27	Co	ORGANIZATION
54	28	'	O
54	29	s	O
54	30	&	O
54	31	lt	O
54	32	;	O
54	33	GE	ORGANIZATION
54	34	>	O
54	35	General	ORGANIZATION
54	36	Electric	ORGANIZATION
54	37	Credit	ORGANIZATION
54	38	Corp	ORGANIZATION
54	39	via	O
54	40	Prudential	ORGANIZATION
54	41	-	ORGANIZATION
54	42	Bache	ORGANIZATION
54	43	Securities	ORGANIZATION
54	44	Inc	ORGANIZATION
54	45	,	O
54	46	did	O
54	47	not	O
54	48	have	O
54	49	such	O
54	50	a	O
54	51	floor	O
54	52	.	O

35	25	parentOrganization

55	0	An	O
55	1	underwriter	O
55	2	familiar	O
55	3	with	O
55	4	the	O
55	5	Dow	ORGANIZATION
55	6	Chemical	ORGANIZATION
55	7	deal	O
55	8	pointed	O
55	9	out	O
55	10	that	O
55	11	because	O
55	12	of	O
55	13	the	O
55	14	interest	O
55	15	rate	O
55	16	and	O
55	17	currency	O
55	18	swaps	O
55	19	Dow	ORGANIZATION
55	20	did	O
55	21	,	O
55	22	the	O
55	23	issuer	O
55	24	felt	O
55	25	comfortable	O
55	26	setting	O
55	27	a	O
55	28	rate	O
55	29	floor	O
55	30	.	O

5	19	brand

56	0	A	O
56	1	Bear	ORGANIZATION
56	2	Stearns	ORGANIZATION
56	3	officer	O
56	4	said	O
56	5	more	O
56	6	than	O
56	7	half	O
56	8	of	O
56	9	the	O
56	10	Ford	ORGANIZATION
56	11	Credit	ORGANIZATION
56	12	notes	O
56	13	were	O
56	14	sold	O
56	15	by	O
56	16	late	O
56	17	Friday	O
56	18	afternoon	O
56	19	,	O
56	20	the	O
56	21	second	O
56	22	day	O
56	23	of	O
56	24	offering	O
56	25	.	O


57	0	However	O
57	1	,	O
57	2	underwriters	O
57	3	away	O
57	4	from	O
57	5	the	O
57	6	Bear	ORGANIZATION
57	7	Stearns	ORGANIZATION
57	8	syndicate	ORGANIZATION
57	9	said	O
57	10	the	O
57	11	issue	O
57	12	may	O
57	13	have	O
57	14	sold	O
57	15	even	O
57	16	faster	O
57	17	if	O
57	18	Prudential	ORGANIZATION
57	19	-	ORGANIZATION
57	20	Bache	ORGANIZATION
57	21	did	O
57	22	not	O
57	23	offer	O
57	24	the	O
57	25	General	ORGANIZATION
57	26	Electric	ORGANIZATION
57	27	Credit	ORGANIZATION
57	28	notes	O
57	29	on	O
57	30	Friday	O
57	31	.	O


58	0	They	O
58	1	pointed	O
58	2	out	O
58	3	that	O
58	4	the	O
58	5	Ford	ORGANIZATION
58	6	notes	O
58	7	were	O
58	8	rated	O
58	9	A	O
58	10	-	O
58	11	1	O
58	12	by	O
58	13	Moody	ORGANIZATION
58	14	'	O
58	15	s	O
58	16	Investors	O
58	17	and	O
58	18	AA	O
58	19	-	O
58	20	minus	O
58	21	by	O
58	22	Standard	O
58	23	and	O
58	24	Poor	O
58	25	'	O
58	26	s	O
58	27	,	O
58	28	while	O
58	29	the	O
58	30	General	ORGANIZATION
58	31	Electric	ORGANIZATION
58	32	notes	O
58	33	,	O
58	34	which	O
58	35	had	O
58	36	the	O
58	37	same	O
58	38	interest	O
58	39	rate	O
58	40	terms	O
58	41	and	O
58	42	were	O
58	43	also	O
58	44	non	O
58	45	-	O
58	46	callable	O
58	47	to	O
58	48	maturity	O
58	49	,	O
58	50	carried	O
58	51	top	O
58	52	-	O
58	53	flight	O
58	54	AAA	O
58	55	ratings	O
58	56	by	O
58	57	both	O
58	58	agencies	O
58	59	.	O


59	0	But	O
59	1	with	O
59	2	the	O
59	3	Dow	O
59	4	,	O
59	5	Ford	ORGANIZATION
59	6	and	O
59	7	GE	ORGANIZATION
59	8	offerings	O
59	9	,	O
59	10	the	O
59	11	marketplace	O
59	12	has	O
59	13	had	O
59	14	enough	O
59	15	for	O
59	16	the	O
59	17	time	O
59	18	being	O
59	19	,"	O
59	20	the	O
59	21	Prudential	ORGANIZATION
59	22	-	ORGANIZATION
59	23	Bache	ORGANIZATION
59	24	officer	O
59	25	admitted	O
59	26	.	O


60	0	GENCORP	ORGANIZATION
60	1	TAKES	O
60	2	NO	O
60	3	ACTION	O
60	4	ON	O
60	5	STOCK	O
60	6	DIVIDEND	O
60	7	Gencorp	ORGANIZATION
60	8	Inc	ORGANIZATION
60	9	said	O
60	10	its	O
60	11	board	O
60	12	took	O
60	13	no	O
60	14	action	O
60	15	with	O
60	16	respect	O
60	17	to	O
60	18	a	O
60	19	two	O
60	20	pct	O
60	21	stock	O
60	22	dividend	O
60	23	at	O
60	24	its	O
60	25	annual	O
60	26	meeting	O
60	27	yesterday	O
60	28	due	O
60	29	to	O
60	30	the	O
60	31	press	O
60	32	of	O
60	33	other	O
60	34	business	O
60	35	,	O
60	36	specifically	O
60	37	the	O
60	38	company	O
60	39	'	O
60	40	s	O
60	41	pending	O
60	42	takeover	O
60	43	offer	O
60	44	by	O
60	45	General	ORGANIZATION
60	46	Acquisition	ORGANIZATION
60	47	Corp	ORGANIZATION
60	48	,	O
60	49	formed	O
60	50	by	O
60	51	AFG	ORGANIZATION
60	52	industries	O
60	53	inc	O
60	54	and	O
60	55	Wagner	PERSON
60	56	and	O
60	57	brown	O
60	58	.	O

7	0	brand
7	45	parentOrganization

61	0	INT	O
61	1	'	O
61	2	L	O
61	3	BROADCASTING	O
61	4	&	O
61	5	lt	O
61	6	;	O
61	7	IBCA	ORGANIZATION
61	8	>	O
61	9	SETS	O
61	10	REVERSE	O
61	11	SPLIT	O
61	12	International	ORGANIZATION
61	13	Broadcasting	ORGANIZATION
61	14	Corp	ORGANIZATION
61	15	said	O
61	16	shareholders	O
61	17	at	O
61	18	its	O
61	19	annual	O
61	20	meeting	O
61	21	approved	O
61	22	a	O
61	23	one	O
61	24	for	O
61	25	25	O
61	26	reverse	O
61	27	stock	O
61	28	split	O
61	29	.	O


62	0	KUWAITI	O
62	1	DAILY	O
62	2	SAYS	O
62	3	OPEC	ORGANIZATION
62	4	CREDIBILITY	O
62	5	AT	O
62	6	STAKE	O
62	7	OPEC	ORGANIZATION
62	8	'	O
62	9	s	O
62	10	credibility	O
62	11	faces	O
62	12	fresh	O
62	13	scrutiny	O
62	14	in	O
62	15	coming	O
62	16	weeks	O
62	17	amid	O
62	18	signs	O
62	19	of	O
62	20	a	O
62	21	significant	O
62	22	rise	O
62	23	in	O
62	24	supplies	O
62	25	of	O
62	26	oil	O
62	27	to	O
62	28	international	O
62	29	oil	O
62	30	markets	O
62	31	,	O
62	32	the	O
62	33	Kuwait	LOCATION
62	34	daily	O
62	35	al	O
62	36	-	O
62	37	Qabas	PERSON
62	38	said	O
62	39	.	O


63	0	In	O
63	1	an	O
63	2	article	O
63	3	headlined	O
63	4	,	O
63	5	"	O
63	6	Gulf	LOCATION
63	7	oil	O
63	8	sources	O
63	9	say	O
63	10	Middle	LOCATION
63	11	East	LOCATION
63	12	production	O
63	13	up	O
63	14	1	O
63	15	.	O
63	16	4	O
63	17	mln	O
63	18	bpd	O
63	19	,"	O
63	20	it	O
63	21	warned	O
63	22	OPEC	ORGANIZATION
63	23	'	O
63	24	s	O
63	25	official	O
63	26	prices	O
63	27	could	O
63	28	face	O
63	29	fresh	O
63	30	pressure	O
63	31	from	O
63	32	international	O
63	33	oil	O
63	34	companies	O
63	35	seeking	O
63	36	cheaper	O
63	37	supplies	O
63	38	.	O

10	6	containsPlace

64	0	It	O
64	1	did	O
64	2	not	O
64	3	say	O
64	4	whether	O
64	5	only	O
64	6	OPEC	ORGANIZATION
64	7	or	O
64	8	both	O
64	9	OPEC	ORGANIZATION
64	10	and	O
64	11	other	O
64	12	producers	O
64	13	were	O
64	14	behind	O
64	15	the	O
64	16	reported	O
64	17	rise	O
64	18	in	O
64	19	Mideast	LOCATION
64	20	output	O
64	21	.	O


65	0	"	O
65	1	The	O
65	2	sources	O
65	3	believed	O
65	4	a	O
65	5	return	O
65	6	of	O
65	7	oil	O
65	8	below	O
65	9	18	O
65	10	dlrs	O
65	11	a	O
65	12	barrel	O
65	13	may	O
65	14	open	O
65	15	the	O
65	16	doors	O
65	17	for	O
65	18	international	O
65	19	oil	O
65	20	companies	O
65	21	to	O
65	22	pressure	O
65	23	OPEC	ORGANIZATION
65	24	over	O
65	25	contract	O
65	26	prices	O
65	27	,	O
65	28	similar	O
65	29	to	O
65	30	the	O
65	31	struggle	O
65	32	last	O
65	33	March	O
65	34	,"	O
65	35	it	O
65	36	said	O
65	37	,	O
65	38	apparently	O
65	39	referring	O
65	40	to	O
65	41	resistance	O
65	42	by	O
65	43	buyers	O
65	44	to	O
65	45	lift	O
65	46	from	O
65	47	Qatar	LOCATION
65	48	unless	O
65	49	it	O
65	50	gave	O
65	51	price	O
65	52	discounts	O
65	53	.	O


66	0	JAPAN	O
66	1	WHOLESALE	O
66	2	PRICES	O
66	3	FALL	O
66	4	0	O
66	5	.	O
66	6	1	O
66	7	PCT	O
66	8	IN	O
66	9	FEBRUARY	O
66	10	Japan	LOCATION
66	11	'	O
66	12	s	O
66	13	overall	O
66	14	wholesale	O
66	15	price	O
66	16	index	O
66	17	(	O
66	18	base	O
66	19	1980	O
66	20	)	O
66	21	fell	O
66	22	0	O
66	23	.	O
66	24	1	O
66	25	pct	O
66	26	in	O
66	27	February	O
66	28	from	O
66	29	a	O
66	30	month	O
66	31	earlier	O
66	32	to	O
66	33	86	O
66	34	.	O
66	35	4	O
66	36	for	O
66	37	the	O
66	38	second	O
66	39	consecutive	O
66	40	month	O
66	41	-	O
66	42	on	O
66	43	-	O
66	44	month	O
66	45	fall	O
66	46	,	O
66	47	the	O
66	48	Bank	ORGANIZATION
66	49	of	ORGANIZATION
66	50	Japan	ORGANIZATION
66	51	said	O
66	52	.	O

48	10	location

67	0	ARMEL	ORGANIZATION
67	1	INC	ORGANIZATION
67	2	&	O
67	3	lt	O
67	4	;	O
67	5	AML	ORGANIZATION
67	6	>	O
67	7	4TH	O
67	8	QTR	O
67	9	LOSS	O
67	10	Oper	O
67	11	shr	O
67	12	loss	O
67	13	79	O
67	14	cts	O
67	15	vs	O
67	16	loss	O
67	17	2	O
67	18	.	O
67	19	32	O
67	20	dlrs	O
67	21	Oper	O
67	22	net	O
67	23	loss	O
67	24	2	O
67	25	,	O
67	26	536	O
67	27	,	O
67	28	896	O
67	29	vs	O
67	30	loss	O
67	31	6	O
67	32	,	O
67	33	562	O
67	34	,	O
67	35	472	O
67	36	Revs	O
67	37	13	O
67	38	.	O
67	39	8	O
67	40	mln	O
67	41	vs	O
67	42	14	O
67	43	.	O
67	44	5	O
67	45	mln	O
67	46	Year	O
67	47	Oper	O
67	48	shr	O
67	49	loss	O
67	50	59	O
67	51	cts	O
67	52	vs	O
67	53	loss	O
67	54	2	O
67	55	.	O
67	56	35	O
67	57	dlrs	O
67	58	Oper	O
67	59	net	O
67	60	loss	O
67	61	1	O
67	62	,	O
67	63	712	O
67	64	,	O
67	65	896	O
67	66	vs	O
67	67	loss	O
67	68	5	O
67	69	,	O
67	70	747	O
67	71	,	O
67	72	472	O
67	73	Revs	O
67	74	43	O
67	75	.	O
67	76	6	O
67	77	mln	O
67	78	vs	O
67	79	44	O
67	80	.	O
67	81	2	O
67	82	mln	O
67	83	NOTE	O
67	84	:	O
67	85	1986	O
67	86	excludes	O
67	87	charge	O
67	88	of	O
67	89	12	O
67	90	cts	O
67	91	per	O
67	92	share	O
67	93	in	O
67	94	the	O
67	95	fourth	O
67	96	quarter	O
67	97	and	O
67	98	gain	O
67	99	of	O
67	100	11	O
67	101	cts	O
67	102	per	O
67	103	share	O
67	104	in	O
67	105	the	O
67	106	year	O
67	107	.	O


68	0	OXFORD	ORGANIZATION
68	1	FINANCIAL	O
68	2	BUYS	O
68	3	CLANCY	ORGANIZATION
68	4	SYSTEMS	ORGANIZATION
68	5	&	ORGANIZATION
68	6	lt	ORGANIZATION
68	7	;	O
68	8	Oxford	ORGANIZATION
68	9	Financial	ORGANIZATION
68	10	Inc	ORGANIZATION
68	11	>	O
68	12	said	O
68	13	it	O
68	14	acquired	O
68	15	&	O
68	16	lt	O
68	17	;	O
68	18	Clancy	ORGANIZATION
68	19	Systems	ORGANIZATION
68	20	International	ORGANIZATION
68	21	Inc	ORGANIZATION
68	22	>	O
68	23	for	O
68	24	an	O
68	25	undisclosed	O
68	26	sum	O
68	27	.	O

18	8	parentOrganization

69	0	The	O
69	1	company	O
69	2	said	O
69	3	Clancy	PERSON
69	4	has	O
69	5	developed	O
69	6	a	O
69	7	fully	O
69	8	automated	O
69	9	parking	O
69	10	citation	O
69	11	system	O
69	12	,	O
69	13	currently	O
69	14	in	O
69	15	use	O
69	16	in	O
69	17	Oklahoma	LOCATION
69	18	City	LOCATION
69	19	,	O
69	20	the	O
69	21	University	ORGANIZATION
69	22	of	ORGANIZATION
69	23	California	ORGANIZATION
69	24	at	O
69	25	Sacramento	LOCATION
69	26	,	O
69	27	and	O
69	28	in	O
69	29	a	O
69	30	pilot	O
69	31	program	O
69	32	in	O
69	33	San	LOCATION
69	34	Francisco	LOCATION
69	35	.	O

21	25	location

70	0	USDA	ORGANIZATION
70	1	'	O
70	2	S	O
70	3	AMSTUTZ	PERSON
70	4	"	O
70	5	SYMPATHETIC	O
70	6	"	O
70	7	TO	O
70	8	WOOD	O
70	9	CREDITS	O
70	10	U	O
70	11	.	O
70	12	S	O
70	13	.	O
70	14	Agriculture	O
70	15	Undersecretary	O
70	16	Daniel	PERSON
70	17	Amstutz	PERSON
70	18	said	O
70	19	he	O
70	20	was	O
70	21	"	O
70	22	totally	O
70	23	sympathetic	O
70	24	"	O
70	25	with	O
70	26	U	O
70	27	.	O
70	28	S	O
70	29	.	O
70	30	wood	O
70	31	producers	O
70	32	'	O
70	33	desire	O
70	34	to	O
70	35	have	O
70	36	their	O
70	37	exports	O
70	38	eligible	O
70	39	for	O
70	40	government	O
70	41	credit	O
70	42	guarantees	O
70	43	.	O

0	16	employee

71	0	He	O
71	1	said	O
71	2	USDA	ORGANIZATION
71	3	had	O
71	4	devoted	O
71	5	an	O
71	6	"	O
71	7	enormous	O
71	8	amount	O
71	9	"	O
71	10	of	O
71	11	time	O
71	12	to	O
71	13	considering	O
71	14	making	O
71	15	wood	O
71	16	products	O
71	17	eligible	O
71	18	for	O
71	19	the	O
71	20	guarantees	O
71	21	and	O
71	22	that	O
71	23	Congress	ORGANIZATION
71	24	was	O
71	25	considering	O
71	26	a	O
71	27	measure	O
71	28	to	O
71	29	do	O
71	30	so	O
71	31	.	O


72	0	SAUDI	ORGANIZATION
72	1	ARABIA	ORGANIZATION
72	2	'	O
72	3	S	O
72	4	KING	O
72	5	FAHD	O
72	6	WANTS	O
72	7	STABLE	O
72	8	OIL	O
72	9	PRICES	O
72	10	King	O
72	11	Fahd	PERSON
72	12	said	O
72	13	today	O
72	14	Saudi	LOCATION
72	15	Arabia	LOCATION
72	16	wants	O
72	17	oil	O
72	18	price	O
72	19	stability	O
72	20	and	O
72	21	he	O
72	22	called	O
72	23	on	O
72	24	non	O
72	25	-	O
72	26	OPEC	ORGANIZATION
72	27	producers	O
72	28	to	O
72	29	avoid	O
72	30	harmful	O
72	31	competition	O
72	32	with	O
72	33	the	O
72	34	13	O
72	35	nation	O
72	36	group	O
72	37	.	O

11	14	nationality

73	0	His	O
73	1	plea	O
73	2	,	O
73	3	in	O
73	4	an	O
73	5	interview	O
73	6	with	O
73	7	Reuters	ORGANIZATION
73	8	and	O
73	9	the	O
73	10	television	O
73	11	news	O
73	12	agency	O
73	13	Visnews	O
73	14	,	O
73	15	came	O
73	16	ahead	O
73	17	of	O
73	18	a	O
73	19	state	O
73	20	visit	O
73	21	he	O
73	22	will	O
73	23	make	O
73	24	to	O
73	25	Britain	LOCATION
73	26	later	O
73	27	this	O
73	28	month	O
73	29	.	O


74	0	King	O
74	1	Fahd	PERSON
74	2	was	O
74	3	asked	O
74	4	whether	O
74	5	Saudi	LOCATION
74	6	Arabia	LOCATION
74	7	would	O
74	8	be	O
74	9	prepared	O
74	10	to	O
74	11	reduce	O
74	12	its	O
74	13	oil	O
74	14	output	O
74	15	below	O
74	16	its	O
74	17	OPEC	ORGANIZATION
74	18	quota	O
74	19	of	O
74	20	4	O
74	21	.	O
74	22	133	O
74	23	mln	O
74	24	barrels	O
74	25	per	O
74	26	day	O
74	27	(	O
74	28	bpd	O
74	29	)	O
74	30	to	O
74	31	defend	O
74	32	the	O
74	33	18	O
74	34	dlr	O
74	35	benchmark	O
74	36	price	O
74	37	agreed	O
74	38	to	O
74	39	by	O
74	40	OPEC	ORGANIZATION
74	41	last	O
74	42	December	O
74	43	.	O

1	5	nationality

75	0	Asked	O
75	1	if	O
75	2	he	O
75	3	saw	O
75	4	the	O
75	5	18	O
75	6	dlr	O
75	7	per	O
75	8	barrel	O
75	9	benchmark	O
75	10	as	O
75	11	a	O
75	12	first	O
75	13	step	O
75	14	towards	O
75	15	higher	O
75	16	world	O
75	17	oil	O
75	18	prices	O
75	19	,	O
75	20	King	ORGANIZATION
75	21	Fahd	ORGANIZATION
75	22	said	O
75	23	it	O
75	24	was	O
75	25	not	O
75	26	for	O
75	27	Saudi	LOCATION
75	28	Arabia	LOCATION
75	29	but	O
75	30	for	O
75	31	all	O
75	32	OPEC	ORGANIZATION
75	33	countries	O
75	34	to	O
75	35	determine	O
75	36	such	O
75	37	issues	O
75	38	.	O


76	0	Iran	LOCATION
76	1	and	O
76	2	Algeria	LOCATION
76	3	have	O
76	4	already	O
76	5	called	O
76	6	for	O
76	7	a	O
76	8	higher	O
76	9	benchmark	O
76	10	.	O


77	0	King	O
77	1	Fahd	PERSON
77	2	said	O
77	3	Saudi	LOCATION
77	4	Arabia	LOCATION
77	5	,	O
77	6	the	O
77	7	world	O
77	8	'	O
77	9	s	O
77	10	largest	O
77	11	oil	O
77	12	exporter	O
77	13	,	O
77	14	was	O
77	15	adhering	O
77	16	to	O
77	17	decisions	O
77	18	made	O
77	19	at	O
77	20	OPEC	ORGANIZATION
77	21	'	O
77	22	s	O
77	23	December	O
77	24	conference	O
77	25	which	O
77	26	set	O
77	27	a	O
77	28	15	O
77	29	.	O
77	30	8	O
77	31	mln	O
77	32	bpd	O
77	33	output	O
77	34	ceiling	O
77	35	for	O
77	36	the	O
77	37	first	O
77	38	half	O
77	39	of	O
77	40	1987	O
77	41	.	O

1	3	nationality

78	0	A	O
78	1	major	O
78	2	non	O
78	3	-	O
78	4	OPEC	ORGANIZATION
78	5	producer	O
78	6	,	O
78	7	Britain	LOCATION
78	8	has	O
78	9	so	O
78	10	far	O
78	11	resisted	O
78	12	the	O
78	13	group	O
78	14	'	O
78	15	s	O
78	16	pleas	O
78	17	to	O
78	18	curb	O
78	19	its	O
78	20	North	LOCATION
78	21	Sea	LOCATION
78	22	oil	O
78	23	output	O
78	24	.	O

7	20	containsPlace

79	0	TREASURY	ORGANIZATION
79	1	SECRETARY	O
79	2	BAKER	PERSON
79	3	DECLINES	O
79	4	COMMENT	O
79	5	ON	O
79	6	G	O
79	7	-	O
79	8	6	O
79	9	U	O
79	10	.	O
79	11	S	O
79	12	.	O
79	13	Treasury	ORGANIZATION
79	14	Secretary	O
79	15	James	PERSON
79	16	Baker	PERSON
79	17	declined	O
79	18	comment	O
79	19	on	O
79	20	the	O
79	21	February	O
79	22	22	O
79	23	Paris	LOCATION
79	24	accord	O
79	25	between	O
79	26	the	O
79	27	six	O
79	28	major	O
79	29	industrial	O
79	30	nations	O
79	31	under	O
79	32	which	O
79	33	they	O
79	34	agreed	O
79	35	to	O
79	36	foster	O
79	37	exchange	O
79	38	rate	O
79	39	stability	O
79	40	.	O

13	15	employee

80	0	Asked	O
80	1	by	O
80	2	reporters	O
80	3	after	O
80	4	a	O
80	5	speech	O
80	6	before	O
80	7	the	O
80	8	National	ORGANIZATION
80	9	Fitness	ORGANIZATION
80	10	Foundation	ORGANIZATION
80	11	banquet	O
80	12	what	O
80	13	,	O
80	14	if	O
80	15	any	O
80	16	,	O
80	17	currency	O
80	18	intervention	O
80	19	levels	O
80	20	had	O
80	21	been	O
80	22	set	O
80	23	in	O
80	24	Paris	LOCATION
80	25	,	O
80	26	Baker	PERSON
80	27	replied	O
80	28	:	O
80	29	"	O
80	30	We	O
80	31	never	O
80	32	talk	O
80	33	about	O
80	34	intervention	O
80	35	."	O


81	0	CHELSEA	ORGANIZATION
81	1	&	O
81	2	lt	O
81	3	;	O
81	4	CHD	O
81	5	>	O
81	6	SEES	O
81	7	LOWER	O
81	8	2ND	O
81	9	QTR	O
81	10	NET	O
81	11	Chelsea	ORGANIZATION
81	12	Industries	ORGANIZATION
81	13	Inc	ORGANIZATION
81	14	said	O
81	15	earnings	O
81	16	for	O
81	17	its	O
81	18	fiscal	O
81	19	second	O
81	20	quarter	O
81	21	ended	O
81	22	March	O
81	23	30	O
81	24	will	O
81	25	be	O
81	26	"	O
81	27	sharply	O
81	28	lower	O
81	29	"	O
81	30	than	O
81	31	the	O
81	32	1	O
81	33	,	O
81	34	414	O
81	35	,	O
81	36	000	O
81	37	dlrs	O
81	38	or	O
81	39	55	O
81	40	cts	O
81	41	a	O
81	42	share	O
81	43	it	O
81	44	earned	O
81	45	for	O
81	46	the	O
81	47	same	O
81	48	quarter	O
81	49	last	O
81	50	year	O
81	51	.	O


82	0	TOTAL	O
82	1	PETROLEUM	O
82	2	&	O
82	3	lt	O
82	4	;	O
82	5	TPN	O
82	6	>	O
82	7	SHUTS	O
82	8	TEXAS	O
82	9	PIPELINES	O
82	10	Total	ORGANIZATION
82	11	Petroleum	ORGANIZATION
82	12	NA	ORGANIZATION
82	13	&	O
82	14	lt	O
82	15	;	O
82	16	TPN	O
82	17	>	O
82	18	shut	O
82	19	down	O
82	20	several	O
82	21	small	O
82	22	crude	O
82	23	oil	O
82	24	pipelines	O
82	25	operating	O
82	26	near	O
82	27	the	O
82	28	Texas	LOCATION
82	29		O
82	30	Oklahoma	LOCATION
82	31	border	O
82	32	last	O
82	33	Friday	O
82	34	as	O
82	35	a	O
82	36	precaution	O
82	37	against	O
82	38	damage	O
82	39	from	O
82	40	local	O
82	41	flooding	O
82	42	,	O
82	43	according	O
82	44	to	O
82	45	Gary	PERSON
82	46	Zollinger	PERSON
82	47	,	O
82	48	manager	O
82	49	of	O
82	50	operations	O
82	51	.	O

10	28	location
10	30	location
10	45	employee

83	0	Total	O
83	1	shut	O
83	2	a	O
83	3	12	O
83	4	-	O
83	5	inch	O
83	6	line	O
83	7	that	O
83	8	runs	O
83	9	across	O
83	10	the	O
83	11	Ouachita	LOCATION
83	12	River	LOCATION
83	13	from	O
83	14	Wynnewood	LOCATION
83	15	to	O
83	16	Ardmore	LOCATION
83	17	with	O
83	18	a	O
83	19	capacity	O
83	20	of	O
83	21	62	O
83	22	,	O
83	23	000	O
83	24	bpd	O
83	25	as	O
83	26	well	O
83	27	as	O
83	28	several	O
83	29	smaller	O
83	30	pipelines	O
83	31	a	O
83	32	few	O
83	33	inches	O
83	34	wide	O
83	35	with	O
83	36	capacities	O
83	37	of	O
83	38	several	O
83	39	thousand	O
83	40	bpd	O
83	41	or	O
83	42	less	O
83	43	,	O
83	44	Zollinger	PERSON
83	45	said	O
83	46	.	O


84	0	One	O
84	1	other	O
84	2	small	O
84	3	pipeline	O
84	4	that	O
84	5	Total	O
84	6	also	O
84	7	closed	O
84	8	has	O
84	9	a	O
84	10	capacity	O
84	11	of	O
84	12	3	O
84	13	,	O
84	14	000	O
84	15	to	O
84	16	4	O
84	17	,	O
84	18	000	O
84	19	bpd	O
84	20	and	O
84	21	crosses	O
84	22	the	O
84	23	Red	LOCATION
84	24	River	LOCATION
84	25	in	O
84	26	Fargo	LOCATION
84	27	,	O
84	28	Texas	LOCATION
84	29	,	O
84	30	Zollinger	PERSON
84	31	said	O
84	32	.	O

28	26	containsPlace
28	23	containsPlace
26	23	containsPlace

85	0	BP	O
85	1	CUTS	O
85	2	NORTH	O
85	3	SEA	O
85	4	PROPANE	O
85	5	PRICE	O
85	6	,	O
85	7	BUTANE	O
85	8	UNCHANGED	O
85	9	British	ORGANIZATION
85	10	Petroleum	ORGANIZATION
85	11	LP	ORGANIZATION
85	12	Gas	ORGANIZATION
85	13	International	ORGANIZATION
85	14	said	O
85	15	it	O
85	16	cut	O
85	17	its	O
85	18	North	LOCATION
85	19	Sea	LOCATION
85	20	LPG	O
85	21	(	O
85	22	Liquified	O
85	23	Petroleum	O
85	24	Gas	O
85	25	)	O
85	26	posted	O
85	27	price	O
85	28	for	O
85	29	propane	O
85	30	to	O
85	31	95	O
85	32	dlrs	O
85	33	from	O
85	34	110	O
85	35	dlrs	O
85	36	a	O
85	37	tonne	O
85	38	,	O
85	39	effective	O
85	40	June	O
85	41	1	O
85	42	.	O

9	18	location

86	0	The	O
86	1	move	O
86	2	follows	O
86	3	a	O
86	4	similar	O
86	5	cut	O
86	6	to	O
86	7	92	O
86	8	from	O
86	9	108	O
86	10	dlrs	O
86	11	a	O
86	12	tonne	O
86	13	announced	O
86	14	by	O
86	15	Shell	ORGANIZATION
86	16	U	ORGANIZATION
86	17	.	ORGANIZATION
86	18	K	ORGANIZATION
86	19	.	ORGANIZATION
86	20	Ltd	ORGANIZATION
86	21	Friday	O
86	22	,	O
86	23	also	O
86	24	fob	O
86	25	North	LOCATION
86	26	Sea	LOCATION
86	27	terminals	O
86	28	and	O
86	29	effective	O
86	30	June	O
86	31	1	O
86	32	until	O
86	33	further	O
86	34	notice	O
86	35	.	O

15	25	location

87	0	CANADA	LOCATION
87	1	NORTHWEST	O
87	2	TO	O
87	3	SELL	O
87	4	PREFERRED	O
87	5	SHARES	O
87	6	&	O
87	7	lt	O
87	8	;	O
87	9	Canada	ORGANIZATION
87	10	Northwest	ORGANIZATION
87	11	Energy	ORGANIZATION
87	12	Ltd	ORGANIZATION
87	13	>	O
87	14	said	O
87	15	it	O
87	16	reached	O
87	17	agreement	O
87	18	in	O
87	19	principle	O
87	20	to	O
87	21	sell	O
87	22	one	O
87	23	mln	O
87	24	preferred	O
87	25	shares	O
87	26	by	O
87	27	way	O
87	28	of	O
87	29	private	O
87	30	placement	O
87	31	to	O
87	32	raise	O
87	33	32	O
87	34	.	O
87	35	5	O
87	36	mln	O
87	37	dlrs	O
87	38	for	O
87	39	oil	O
87	40	and	O
87	41	gas	O
87	42	exploration	O
87	43	.	O


88	0	INTERNATIONAL	O
88	1	LPG	O
88	2	PRICES	O
88	3	MIXED	O
88	4	International	O
88	5	LPG	O
88	6	prices	O
88	7	were	O
88	8	mixed	O
88	9	in	O
88	10	the	O
88	11	past	O
88	12	week	O
88	13	,	O
88	14	with	O
88	15	North	LOCATION
88	16	Sea	LOCATION
88	17	prices	O
88	18	easier	O
88	19	while	O
88	20	prices	O
88	21	in	O
88	22	the	O
88	23	Mediterranean	LOCATION
88	24	and	O
88	25	the	O
88	26	Gulf	LOCATION
88	27	were	O
88	28	up	O
88	29	in	O
88	30	April	O
88	31	,	O
88	32	traders	O
88	33	said	O
88	34	.	O


89	0	British	ORGANIZATION
89	1	Petroleum	ORGANIZATION
89	2	plc	ORGANIZATION
89	3	&	O
89	4	lt	O
89	5	;	O
89	6	BP	O
89	7	>	O
89	8	left	O
89	9	propane	O
89	10	unchanged	O
89	11	at	O
89	12	110	O
89	13	dlrs	O
89	14	and	O
89	15	raised	O
89	16	butane	O
89	17	prices	O
89	18	5	O
89	19	.	O
89	20	50	O
89	21	dlrs	O
89	22	to	O
89	23	123	O
89	24	dlrs	O
89	25	,	O
89	26	Shell	ORGANIZATION
89	27	,	O
89	28	a	O
89	29	unit	O
89	30	of	O
89	31	Royal	ORGANIZATION
89	32	Dutch	ORGANIZATION
89	33		ORGANIZATION
89	34	Shell	ORGANIZATION
89	35	Group	ORGANIZATION
89	36	&	O
89	37	lt	O
89	38	;	O
89	39	RD	O
89	40	>	O
89	41	&	O
89	42	lt	O
89	43	;	O
89	44	ST	O
89	45	>	O
89	46	raised	O
89	47	propane	O
89	48	three	O
89	49	dlrs	O
89	50	to	O
89	51	113	O
89	52	and	O
89	53	butane	O
89	54	5	O
89	55	.	O
89	56	50	O
89	57	dlrs	O
89	58	to	O
89	59	123	O
89	60	dlrs	O
89	61	,	O
89	62	they	O
89	63	said	O
89	64	.	O

26	31	parentOrganization

90	0	In	O
90	1	the	O
90	2	Mediterranean	LOCATION
90	3	,	O
90	4	prices	O
90	5	firm	O
90	6	in	O
90	7	Lavera	LOCATION
90	8	as	O
90	9	Algerian	O
90	10	supplies	O
90	11	were	O
90	12	not	O
90	13	always	O
90	14	available	O
90	15	.	O

2	7	containsPlace

91	0	In	O
91	1	the	O
91	2	Gulf	LOCATION
91	3	,	O
91	4	strong	O
91	5	demand	O
91	6	from	O
91	7	the	O
91	8	Far	LOCATION
91	9	East	LOCATION
91	10	pushed	O
91	11	premium	O
91	12	on	O
91	13	small	O
91	14	cargoes	O
91	15	five	O
91	16	to	O
91	17	10	O
91	18	dlrs	O
91	19	above	O
91	20	government	O
91	21	selling	O
91	22	price	O
91	23	(	O
91	24	gsp	O
91	25	)	O
91	26	for	O
91	27	propane	O
91	28	and	O
91	29	10	O
91	30	dlrs	O
91	31	for	O
91	32	butane	O
91	33	,	O
91	34	traders	O
91	35	said	O
91	36	.	O


92	0	THE	O
92	1	GULF	O


93	0	The	O
93	1	three	O
93	2	research	O
93	3	groups	O
93	4	of	O
93	5	Kiel	LOCATION
93	6	,	O
93	7	Hamburg	LOCATION
93	8	and	O
93	9	Essen	LOCATION
93	10	predicted	O
93	11	in	O
93	12	the	O
93	13	institutes	O
93	14	'	O
93	15	joint	O
93	16	spring	O
93	17	report	O
93	18	that	O
93	19	gross	O
93	20	national	O
93	21	product	O
93	22	(	O
93	23	GNP	O
93	24	)	O
93	25	would	O
93	26	rise	O
93	27	by	O
93	28	two	O
93	29	pct	O
93	30	in	O
93	31	1987	O
93	32	,	O
93	33	compared	O
93	34	with	O
93	35	2	O
93	36	.	O
93	37	4	O
93	38	pct	O
93	39	in	O
93	40	1986	O
93	41	.	O


94	0	Taking	O
94	1	a	O
94	2	dissenting	O
94	3	view	O
94	4	,	O
94	5	the	O
94	6	DIW	ORGANIZATION
94	7	institute	O
94	8	of	O
94	9	West	LOCATION
94	10	Berlin	LOCATION
94	11	and	O
94	12	Munich	LOCATION
94	13	'	O
94	14	s	O
94	15	Ifo	ORGANIZATION
94	16	institute	O
94	17	predicted	O
94	18	only	O
94	19	one	O
94	20	pct	O
94	21	1987	O
94	22	growth	O
94	23	.	O

6	9	location
15	12	location

95	0	The	O
95	1	joint	O
95	2	report	O
95	3	said	O
95	4	that	O
95	5	the	O
95	6	estimates	O
95	7	of	O
95	8	economic	O
95	9	development	O
95	10	made	O
95	11	by	O
95	12	the	O
95	13	DIW	ORGANIZATION
95	14	and	O
95	15	Ifo	ORGANIZATION
95	16	were	O
95	17	"	O
95	18	markedly	O
95	19	less	O
95	20	favourable	O
95	21	"	O
95	22	than	O
95	23	those	O
95	24	of	O
95	25	the	O
95	26	other	O
95	27	three	O
95	28	.	O


96	0	The	O
96	1	DIW	ORGANIZATION
96	2	and	O
96	3	Ifo	ORGANIZATION
96	4	forecast	O
96	5	the	O
96	6	economy	O
96	7	would	O
96	8	pick	O
96	9	up	O
96	10	after	O
96	11	a	O
96	12	slow	O
96	13	start	O
96	14	to	O
96	15	the	O
96	16	year	O
96	17	.	O


97	0	Contrary	O
97	1	to	O
97	2	the	O
97	3	DIW	ORGANIZATION
97	4	and	O
97	5	Ifo	ORGANIZATION
97	6	,	O
97	7	the	O
97	8	three	O
97	9	institutes	O
97	10	said	O
97	11	that	O
97	12	while	O
97	13	exports	O
97	14	would	O
97	15	continue	O
97	16	to	O
97	17	be	O
97	18	the	O
97	19	weak	O
97	20	point	O
97	21	of	O
97	22	the	O
97	23	economy	O
97	24	in	O
97	25	1987	O
97	26	,	O
97	27	"	O
97	28	there	O
97	29	is	O
97	30	good	O
97	31	reason	O
97	32	to	O
97	33	believe	O
97	34	that	O
97	35	exports	O
97	36	will	O
97	37	soon	O
97	38	bottom	O
97	39	out	O
97	40	and	O
97	41	that	O
97	42	a	O
97	43	slight	O
97	44	rise	O
97	45	will	O
97	46	emerge	O
97	47	during	O
97	48	the	O
97	49	course	O
97	50	of	O
97	51	the	O
97	52	year	O
97	53	."	O


98	0	The	O
98	1	three	O
98	2	more	O
98	3	positive	O
98	4	institutes	O
98	5	saw	O
98	6	private	O
98	7	consumption	O
98	8	rising	O
98	9	by	O
98	10	four	O
98	11	pct	O
98	12	in	O
98	13	1987	O
98	14	,	O
98	15	compared	O
98	16	with	O
98	17	4	O
98	18	.	O
98	19	2	O
98	20	pct	O
98	21	in	O
98	22	1986	O
98	23	,	O
98	24	while	O
98	25	DIW	ORGANIZATION
98	26	and	O
98	27	Ifo	ORGANIZATION
98	28	predicted	O
98	29	a	O
98	30	three	O
98	31	pct	O
98	32	increase	O
98	33	.	O


99	0	The	O
99	1	Kiel	LOCATION
99	2	,	O
99	3	Hamburg	LOCATION
99	4	and	O
99	5	Essen	LOCATION
99	6	institutes	O
99	7	said	O
99	8	the	O
99	9	jobless	O
99	10	total	O
99	11	would	O
99	12	average	O
99	13	2	O
99	14	.	O
99	15	17	O
99	16	mln	O
99	17	in	O
99	18	1987	O
99	19	compared	O
99	20	with	O
99	21	2	O
99	22	.	O
99	23	23	O
99	24	mln	O
99	25	in	O
99	26	1986	O
99	27	and	O
99	28	predicted	O
99	29	a	O
99	30	rise	O
99	31	in	O
99	32	the	O
99	33	number	O
99	34	of	O
99	35	people	O
99	36	in	O
99	37	work	O
99	38	of	O
99	39	about	O
99	40	200	O
99	41	,	O
99	42	000	O
99	43	.	O


100	0	The	O
100	1	DIW	ORGANIZATION
100	2	and	O
100	3	Ifo	ORGANIZATION
100	4	said	O
100	5	rises	O
100	6	in	O
100	7	employment	O
100	8	would	O
100	9	occur	O
100	10	only	O
100	11	in	O
100	12	the	O
100	13	tertiary	O
100	14	sector	O
100	15	,	O
100	16	while	O
100	17	"	O
100	18	the	O
100	19	number	O
100	20	employed	O
100	21	in	O
100	22	the	O
100	23	manufacturing	O
100	24	industry	O
100	25	will	O
100	26	decline	O
100	27	."	O


101	0	The	O
101	1	DIW	ORGANIZATION
101	2	and	O
101	3	Ifo	ORGANIZATION
101	4	said	O
101	5	unemployment	O
101	6	would	O
101	7	only	O
101	8	decline	O
101	9	to	O
101	10	2	O
101	11	.	O
101	12	20	O
101	13	mln	O
101	14	in	O
101	15	1987	O
101	16	from	O
101	17	2	O
101	18	.	O
101	19	23	O
101	20	mln	O
101	21	in	O
101	22	1986	O
101	23	.	O


102	0	WEST	O
102	1	VIRGINIA	LOCATION
102	2	FREE	O
102	3	OF	O
102	4	TWO	O
102	5	MAJOR	O
102	6	CATTLE	O
102	7	DISEASES	O
102	8	West	LOCATION
102	9	Virginia	LOCATION
102	10	has	O
102	11	been	O
102	12	declared	O
102	13	free	O
102	14	of	O
102	15	tuberculosis	O
102	16	and	O
102	17	brucellosis	O
102	18	from	O
102	19	its	O
102	20	cattle	O
102	21	population	O
102	22	,	O
102	23	the	O
102	24	U	O
102	25	.	O
102	26	S	O
102	27	.	O
102	28	Agriculture	ORGANIZATION
102	29	Department	ORGANIZATION
102	30	said	O
102	31	.	O


103	0	There	O
103	1	are	O
103	2	33	O
103	3	states	O
103	4	,	O
103	5	plus	O
103	6	the	O
103	7	U	O
103	8	.	O
103	9	S	O
103	10	.	O
103	11	Virgin	LOCATION
103	12	Islands	LOCATION
103	13	,	O
103	14	classified	O
103	15	as	O
103	16	free	O
103	17	of	O
103	18	bovine	O
103	19	tuberculosis	O
103	20	and	O
103	21	24	O
103	22	states	O
103	23	,	O
103	24	plus	O
103	25	Puerto	LOCATION
103	26	Rico	LOCATION
103	27	and	O
103	28	the	O
103	29	U	O
103	30	.	O
103	31	S	O
103	32	.	O
103	33	Virgin	LOCATION
103	34	Islands	LOCATION
103	35	,	O
103	36	which	O
103	37	have	O
103	38	eradicated	O
103	39	brucellosis	O
103	40	.	O


104	0	ATICO	ORGANIZATION
104	1	FINANCIAL	ORGANIZATION
104	2	CORP	ORGANIZATION
104	3	&	O
104	4	lt	O
104	5	;	O
104	6	ATFC	O
104	7	>	O
104	8	4TH	O
104	9	QTR	O
104	10	NET	O
104	11	Shr	O
104	12	30	O
104	13	cts	O
104	14	vs	O
104	15	5	O
104	16	.	O
104	17	92	O
104	18	dlrs	O
104	19	Net	O
104	20	1	O
104	21	,	O
104	22	142	O
104	23	,	O
104	24	000	O
104	25	vs	O
104	26	16	O
104	27	.	O
104	28	0	O
104	29	mln	O
104	30	Revs	O
104	31	10	O
104	32	.	O
104	33	6	O
104	34	mln	O
104	35	vs	O
104	36	24	O
104	37	.	O
104	38	2	O
104	39	mln	O
104	40	Year	O
104	41	Shr	O
104	42	90	O
104	43	cts	O
104	44	vs	O
104	45	6	O
104	46	.	O
104	47	20	O
104	48	dlrs	O
104	49	Net	O
104	50	3	O
104	51	,	O
104	52	320	O
104	53	,	O
104	54	000	O
104	55	vs	O
104	56	16	O
104	57	.	O
104	58	9	O
104	59	mln	O
104	60	Revs	O
104	61	45	O
104	62	.	O
104	63	00	O
104	64	mln	O
104	65	vs	O
104	66	26	O
104	67	.	O
104	68	2	O
104	69	mln	O
104	70	NOTE	O
104	71	:	O
104	72	1986	O
104	73	4th	O
104	74	qtr	O
104	75	and	O
104	76	yr	O
104	77	amounts	O
104	78	include	O
104	79	acquisition	O
104	80	of	O
104	81	98	O
104	82	.	O
104	83	8	O
104	84	pct	O
104	85	of	O
104	86	common	O
104	87	of	O
104	88	Atico	LOCATION
104	89	,	O
104	90	formerly	O
104	91	Peninsula	ORGANIZATION
104	92	Federal	ORGANIZATION
104	93	Savings	ORGANIZATION
104	94	and	ORGANIZATION
104	95	Loan	ORGANIZATION
104	96	Association	ORGANIZATION
104	97	,	O
104	98	on	O
104	99	January	O
104	100	24	O
104	101	,	O
104	102	1986	O
104	103	.	O

91	88	brand

105	0	1985	O
105	1	4th	O
105	2	qtr	O
105	3	and	O
105	4	yr	O
105	5	net	O
105	6	include	O
105	7	net	O
105	8	gain	O
105	9	of	O
105	10	15	O
105	11	.	O
105	12	9	O
105	13	mln	O
105	14	dlrs	O
105	15	or	O
105	16	5	O
105	17	.	O
105	18	86	O
105	19	dlrs	O
105	20	per	O
105	21	share	O
105	22	on	O
105	23	exchange	O
105	24	of	O
105	25	common	O
105	26	of	O
105	27	Pan	ORGANIZATION
105	28	America	ORGANIZATION
105	29	Banks	ORGANIZATION
105	30	Inc	ORGANIZATION
105	31	for	O
105	32	common	O
105	33	of	O
105	34	NCNB	ORGANIZATION
105	35	Corp	ORGANIZATION
105	36	purusant	O
105	37	to	O
105	38	a	O
105	39	merger	O
105	40	of	O
105	41	the	O
105	42	companies	O
105	43	.	O


106	0	CHAVIN	O
106	1	RAISES	O
106	2	STAKE	O
106	3	IN	O
106	4	MYERS	O
106	5	(	O
106	6	MYR	O
106	7	)	O
106	8	Chicago	LOCATION
106	9	real	O
106	10	estate	O
106	11	developer	O
106	12	Leonard	PERSON
106	13	Chavin	PERSON
106	14	told	O
106	15	the	O
106	16	Securities	ORGANIZATION
106	17	and	ORGANIZATION
106	18	Exchange	ORGANIZATION
106	19	Commission	ORGANIZATION
106	20	he	O
106	21	had	O
106	22	raised	O
106	23	his	O
106	24	stake	O
106	25	in	O
106	26	the	O
106	27	L	O
106	28	.	O
106	29	E	O
106	30	.	O

12	8	homeLocation

107	0	He	O
107	1	also	O
107	2	said	O
107	3	an	O
107	4	investment	O
107	5	banker	O
107	6	repesenting	O
107	7	him	O
107	8	met	O
107	9	with	O
107	10	Myers	PERSON
107	11	'	O
107	12	officers	O
107	13	,	O
107	14	telling	O
107	15	them	O
107	16	of	O
107	17	his	O
107	18	plans	O
107	19	for	O
107	20	a	O
107	21	takeover	O
107	22	and	O
107	23	that	O
107	24	he	O
107	25	may	O
107	26	solicit	O
107	27	proxies	O
107	28	for	O
107	29	a	O
107	30	seat	O
107	31	on	O
107	32	Myers	PERSON
107	33	'	O
107	34	board	O
107	35	.	O


108	0	Chavin	PERSON
108	1	also	O
108	2	said	O
108	3	if	O
108	4	he	O
108	5	takes	O
108	6	control	O
108	7	of	O
108	8	the	O
108	9	firm	O
108	10	,	O
108	11	it	O
108	12	could	O
108	13	result	O
108	14	in	O
108	15	delisting	O
108	16	Meyers	PERSON
108	17	'	O
108	18	from	O
108	19	the	O
108	20	New	ORGANIZATION
108	21	York	ORGANIZATION
108	22	Stock	ORGANIZATION
108	23	Exchange	ORGANIZATION
108	24	.	O


109	0	The	O
109	1	company	O
109	2	said	O
109	3	it	O
109	4	will	O
109	5	make	O
109	6	the	O
109	7	proposal	O
109	8	to	O
109	9	shareowners	O
109	10	at	O
109	11	its	O
109	12	annual	O
109	13	mmeting	O
109	14	May	O
109	15	6	O
109	16	in	O
109	17	Dothan	LOCATION
109	18	,	O
109	19	Ala	PERSON
109	20	.,	O
109	21	near	O
109	22	the	O
109	23	company	O
109	24	'	O
109	25	s	O
109	26	Great	ORGANIZATION
109	27	Southern	ORGANIZATION
109	28	Paper	ORGANIZATION
109	29	division	O
109	30	operations	O
109	31	.	O

26	17	location

110	0	ALUSUISSE	ORGANIZATION
110	1	PLANS	O
110	2	50	O
110	3	PCT	O
110	4	CAPITAL	O
110	5	CUT	O
110	6	Schweizerische	ORGANIZATION
110	7	Aluminium	ORGANIZATION
110	8	AG	ORGANIZATION
110	9	,	O
110	10	Alusuisse	ORGANIZATION
110	11	,	O
110	12	plans	O
110	13	to	O
110	14	reduce	O
110	15	share	O
110	16	and	O
110	17	participation	O
110	18	certificate	O
110	19	capital	O
110	20	by	O
110	21	50	O
110	22	pct	O
110	23	to	O
110	24	cover	O
110	25	losses	O
110	26	in	O
110	27	1986	O
110	28	and	O
110	29	those	O
110	30	carried	O
110	31	forward	O
110	32	from	O
110	33	the	O
110	34	previous	O
110	35	year	O
110	36	,	O
110	37	chief	O
110	38	executive	O
110	39	Hans	PERSON
110	40	Jucker	PERSON
110	41	said	O
110	42	.	O

6	10	brand
6	39	employee

111	0	Trading	O
111	1	in	O
111	2	Alusuisse	ORGANIZATION
111	3	shares	O
111	4	was	O
111	5	suspended	O
111	6	on	O
111	7	the	O
111	8	Zurich	LOCATION
111	9	stock	O
111	10	exchange	O
111	11	after	O
111	12	today	O
111	13	'	O
111	14	s	O
111	15	announcement	O
111	16	by	O
111	17	the	O
111	18	company	O
111	19	that	O
111	20	it	O
111	21	would	O
111	22	cut	O
111	23	its	O
111	24	share	O
111	25	capital	O
111	26	by	O
111	27	50	O
111	28	pct	O
111	29	,	O
111	30	the	O
111	31	bourse	O
111	32	said	O
111	33	.	O


112	0	PUBLISHERS	O
112	1	EQUIPMENT	O
112	2	&	O
112	3	lt	O
112	4	;	O
112	5	PECN	O
112	6	>,	O
112	7	TRENTONIAN	O
112	8	IN	O
112	9	DEAL	O
112	10	Publishers	ORGANIZATION
112	11	Equipment	ORGANIZATION
112	12	Corp	ORGANIZATION
112	13	said	O
112	14	it	O
112	15	reached	O
112	16	an	O
112	17	agreement	O
112	18	to	O
112	19	incorporate	O
112	20	flexo	O
112	21	printing	O
112	22	technology	O
112	23	into	O
112	24	The	O
112	25	Tentonian	O
112	26	,	O
112	27	an	O
112	28	Ingersoll	ORGANIZATION
112	29	newspaper	O
112	30	in	O
112	31	Trenton	LOCATION
112	32	,	O
112	33	N	O
112	34	.	O
112	35	J	O
112	36	.	O

28	31	location

113	0	MCO	O
113	1	&	O
113	2	lt	O
113	3	;	O
113	4	MCO	O
113	5	>,	O
113	6	MAXXAM	O
113	7	&	O
113	8	lt	O
113	9	;	O
113	10	MXM	O
113	11	>	O
113	12	HOLDERS	O
113	13	APPROVE	O
113	14	MERGER	O
113	15	MCO	ORGANIZATION
113	16	Holdings	ORGANIZATION
113	17	Inc	ORGANIZATION
113	18	said	O
113	19	its	O
113	20	shareholders	O
113	21	and	O
113	22	those	O
113	23	of	O
113	24	MAXXAM	ORGANIZATION
113	25	Group	ORGANIZATION
113	26	Inc	ORGANIZATION
113	27	have	O
113	28	approved	O
113	29	the	O
113	30	proposed	O
113	31	merger	O
113	32	of	O
113	33	the	O
113	34	two	O
113	35	companies	O
113	36	.	O


114	0	MCO	ORGANIZATION
114	1	said	O
114	2	one	O
114	3	MAXXAM	ORGANIZATION
114	4	shareholder	O
114	5	has	O
114	6	filed	O
114	7	an	O
114	8	objection	O
114	9	to	O
114	10	the	O
114	11	proposed	O
114	12	settlement	O
114	13	of	O
114	14	shareholder	O
114	15	actions	O
114	16	related	O
114	17	to	O
114	18	the	O
114	19	merger	O
114	20	in	O
114	21	the	O
114	22	Delaware	ORGANIZATION
114	23	Court	ORGANIZATION
114	24	of	ORGANIZATION
114	25	Chancery	ORGANIZATION
114	26	.	O


115	0	ATCOR	ORGANIZATION
115	1	INC	ORGANIZATION
115	2	&	O
115	3	lt	O
115	4	;	O
115	5	ATCO	ORGANIZATION
115	6	>	O
115	7	CUT	O
115	8	DIVIDEND	O
115	9	Qtly	O
115	10	div	O
115	11	three	O
115	12	cts	O
115	13	vs	O
115	14	12	O
115	15	cts	O
115	16	prior	O
115	17	Pay	O
115	18	April	O
115	19	15	O
115	20	Record	O
115	21	April	O
115	22	6	O


116	0	TAIWAN	O
116	1	PLANS	O
116	2	MISSION	O
116	3	TO	O
116	4	CLOSE	O
116	5	TRADE	O
116	6	GAP	O
116	7	WITH	O
116	8	U	O
116	9	.	O
116	10	S	O
116	11	.	O
116	12	Taiwan	LOCATION
116	13	'	O
116	14	s	O
116	15	leading	O
116	16	industrial	O
116	17	organisation	O
116	18	said	O
116	19	it	O
116	20	will	O
116	21	send	O
116	22	its	O
116	23	first	O
116	24	buying	O
116	25	mission	O
116	26	to	O
116	27	the	O
116	28	U	O
116	29	.	O
116	30	S	O
116	31	.	O
116	32	Later	O
116	33	this	O
116	34	year	O
116	35	in	O
116	36	an	O
116	37	effort	O
116	38	to	O
116	39	reduce	O
116	40	the	O
116	41	country	O
116	42	'	O
116	43	s	O
116	44	trade	O
116	45	surplus	O
116	46	with	O
116	47	Washington	LOCATION
116	48	.	O


117	0	A	O
117	1	spokesman	O
117	2	for	O
117	3	the	O
117	4	Chinese	ORGANIZATION
117	5	National	ORGANIZATION
117	6	Federation	ORGANIZATION
117	7	of	ORGANIZATION
117	8	Industries	ORGANIZATION
117	9	told	O
117	10	Reuters	ORGANIZATION
117	11	the	O
117	12	mission	O
117	13	was	O
117	14	part	O
117	15	of	O
117	16	a	O
117	17	broader	O
117	18	plan	O
117	19	to	O
117	20	switch	O
117	21	large	O
117	22	purchases	O
117	23	to	O
117	24	the	O
117	25	U	O
117	26	.	O
117	27	S	O
117	28	.	O
117	29	From	O
117	30	Japan	LOCATION
117	31	.	O


118	0	The	O
118	1	spokesman	O
118	2	said	O
118	3	Federation	ORGANIZATION
118	4	members	O
118	5	were	O
118	6	now	O
118	7	discussing	O
118	8	the	O
118	9	volume	O
118	10	of	O
118	11	business	O
118	12	they	O
118	13	could	O
118	14	transfer	O
118	15	to	O
118	16	America	LOCATION
118	17	.	O


119	0	A	O
119	1	Board	ORGANIZATION
119	2	of	ORGANIZATION
119	3	Foreign	ORGANIZATION
119	4	Trade	ORGANIZATION
119	5	official	O
119	6	told	O
119	7	Reuters	ORGANIZATION
119	8	the	O
119	9	government	O
119	10	would	O
119	11	send	O
119	12	two	O
119	13	buying	O
119	14	missions	O
119	15	to	O
119	16	America	LOCATION
119	17	between	O
119	18	June	O
119	19	and	O
119	20	July	O
119	21	this	O
119	22	year	O
119	23	and	O
119	24	might	O
119	25	send	O
119	26	others	O
119	27	later	O
119	28	.	O


120	0	WARBURG	ORGANIZATION
120	1	PINCUS	ORGANIZATION
120	2	DECLINES	O
120	3	TO	O
120	4	UP	O
120	5	SYMBION	O
120	6	&	O
120	7	lt	O
120	8	;	O
120	9	SYMB	O
120	10	>	O
120	11	BID	O
120	12	Warburg	ORGANIZATION
120	13	,	O
120	14	Pincus	ORGANIZATION
120	15	Capital	ORGANIZATION
120	16	Co	ORGANIZATION
120	17	L	O
120	18	.	O
120	19	P	O
120	20	.,	O
120	21	an	O
120	22	investment	O
120	23	partnership	O
120	24	,	O
120	25	said	O
120	26	it	O
120	27	told	O
120	28	representatives	O
120	29	of	O
120	30	Symbion	ORGANIZATION
120	31	Inc	ORGANIZATION
120	32	it	O
120	33	would	O
120	34	not	O
120	35	increase	O
120	36	the	O
120	37	3	O
120	38	.	O
120	39	50	O
120	40	-	O
120	41	dlr	O
120	42	-	O
120	43	per	O
120	44	-	O
120	45	share	O
120	46	cash	O
120	47	price	O
120	48	it	O
120	49	has	O
120	50	offered	O
120	51	for	O
120	52	the	O
120	53	company	O
120	54	.	O

121	0	In	O
121	1	a	O
121	2	filing	O
121	3	with	O
121	4	the	O
121	5	Securities	ORGANIZATION
121	6	and	ORGANIZATION
121	7	Exchange	ORGANIZATION
121	8	Commission	ORGANIZATION
121	9	,	O
121	10	Warburg	ORGANIZATION
121	11	Pincus	ORGANIZATION
121	12	said	O
121	13	one	O
121	14	of	O
121	15	its	O
121	16	top	O
121	17	executives	O
121	18	,	O
121	19	Rodman	PERSON
121	20	Moorhead	PERSON
121	21	,	O
121	22	who	O
121	23	is	O
121	24	also	O
121	25	a	O
121	26	Symbion	ORGANIZATION
121	27	director	O
121	28	,	O
121	29	met	O
121	30	April	O
121	31	1	O
121	32	with	O
121	33	Symbion	PERSON
121	34	'	O
121	35	s	O
121	36	financial	O
121	37	advisor	O
121	38	,	O
121	39	L	O
121	40	.	O
121	41	F	O
121	42	.	O
121	43	Rothschild	ORGANIZATION
121	44	,	ORGANIZATION
121	45	Unterberg	ORGANIZATION
121	46	,	ORGANIZATION
121	47	Towbin	ORGANIZATION
121	48	Inc	ORGANIZATION
121	49	.	O

10	19	employee
26	19	employee

122	0	In	O
122	1	a	O
122	2	discussion	O
122	3	of	O
122	4	the	O
122	5	offer	O
122	6	,	O
122	7	Warburg	PERSON
122	8	Pincus	PERSON
122	9	said	O
122	10	Moorhead	PERSON
122	11	told	O
122	12	the	O
122	13	meeting	O
122	14	there	O
122	15	are	O
122	16	no	O
122	17	plans	O
122	18	to	O
122	19	raise	O
122	20	the	O
122	21	3	O
122	22	.	O
122	23	50	O
122	24	dlr	O
122	25	bid	O
122	26	.	O

7	10	employee

123	0	Moorhead	PERSON
123	1	told	O
123	2	the	O
123	3	Rothschild	ORGANIZATION
123	4	officials	O
123	5	that	O
123	6	Warburg	ORGANIZATION
123	7	Pincus	ORGANIZATION
123	8	considers	O
123	9	the	O
123	10	offered	O
123	11	price	O
123	12	to	O
123	13	be	O
123	14	a	O
123	15	fair	O
123	16	one	O
123	17	,	O
123	18	Warburg	PERSON
123	19	Pincus	PERSON
123	20	said	O
123	21	.	O

6	0	employee

124	0	RTE	ORGANIZATION
124	1	CORP	ORGANIZATION
124	2	&	O
124	3	lt	O
124	4	;	O
124	5	RTE	O
124	6	>	O
124	7	BUYS	O
124	8	EMHART	ORGANIZATION
124	9	CORP	ORGANIZATION
124	10	UNIT	O
124	11	RTE	ORGANIZATION
124	12	Corp	ORGANIZATION
124	13	said	O
124	14	it	O
124	15	completed	O
124	16	the	O
124	17	purchase	O
124	18	of	O
124	19	Emhart	ORGANIZATION
124	20	Corp	ORGANIZATION
124	21	'	O
124	22	s	O
124	23	United	LOCATION
124	24	States	LOCATION
124	25	aluminum	O
124	26	electrolytic	O
124	27	capacitor	O
124	28	business	O
124	29	for	O
124	30	an	O
124	31	undisclosed	O
124	32	sum	O
124	33	.	O

19	11	parentOrganization
19	23	location

125	0	TRADERS	O
125	1	DETAIL	O
125	2	IRISH	O
125	3	INTERVENTION	O
125	4	BARLEY	O
125	5	TENDER	O
125	6	The	O
125	7	European	ORGANIZATION
125	8	Commission	ORGANIZATION
125	9	authorised	O
125	10	the	O
125	11	export	O
125	12	of	O
125	13	33	O
125	14	,	O
125	15	500	O
125	16	tonnes	O
125	17	of	O
125	18	Irish	O
125	19	intervention	O
125	20	barley	O
125	21	at	O
125	22	today	O
125	23	'	O
125	24	s	O
125	25	tender	O
125	26	for	O
125	27	non	O
125	28	-	O
125	29	European	ORGANIZATION
125	30	Community	ORGANIZATION
125	31	destinations	O
125	32	at	O
125	33	53	O
125	34	.	O
125	35	10	O
125	36	Ecus	O
125	37	per	O
125	38	tonne	O
125	39	,	O
125	40	grain	O
125	41	traders	O
125	42	said	O
125	43	.	O


126	0	GROUP	O
126	1	HAS	O
126	2	5	O
126	3	.	O
126	4	2	O
126	5	PCT	O
126	6	OF	O
126	7	DISTRIBUTED	O
126	8	LOGIC	O
126	9	&	O
126	10	lt	O
126	11	;	O
126	12	DLOG	O
126	13	.	O
126	14	O	O
126	15	>	O
126	16	An	O
126	17	investor	O
126	18	group	O
126	19	led	O
126	20	by	O
126	21	Technology	ORGANIZATION
126	22	Growth	ORGANIZATION
126	23	Fund	ORGANIZATION
126	24	Ltd	ORGANIZATION
126	25	,	O
126	26	an	O
126	27	Aspen	LOCATION
126	28	,	O
126	29	Colo	O
126	30	.,	O
126	31	investment	O
126	32	firm	O
126	33	,	O
126	34	said	O
126	35	it	O
126	36	has	O
126	37	acquired	O
126	38	129	O
126	39	,	O
126	40	000	O
126	41	shares	O
126	42	of	O
126	43	Distributed	ORGANIZATION
126	44	Logic	ORGANIZATION
126	45	Corp	ORGANIZATION
126	46	,	O
126	47	or	O
126	48	5	O
126	49	.	O
126	50	2	O
126	51	pct	O
126	52	of	O
126	53	the	O
126	54	total	O
126	55	,	O
126	56	and	O
126	57	may	O
126	58	try	O
126	59	to	O
126	60	influence	O
126	61	the	O
126	62	company	O
126	63	.	O

127	0	In	O
127	1	a	O
127	2	filing	O
127	3	with	O
127	4	the	O
127	5	Securities	ORGANIZATION
127	6	and	ORGANIZATION
127	7	Exchange	ORGANIZATION
127	8	Commission	ORGANIZATION
127	9	,	O
127	10	the	O
127	11	group	O
127	12	,	O
127	13	which	O
127	14	also	O
127	15	includes	O
127	16	individual	O
127	17	investors	O
127	18	and	O
127	19	a	O
127	20	non	O
127	21	-	O
127	22	profit	O
127	23	foundation	O
127	24	,	O
127	25	said	O
127	26	it	O
127	27	bought	O
127	28	the	O
127	29	stake	O
127	30	for	O
127	31	884	O
127	32	,	O
127	33	414	O
127	34	dlrs	O
127	35	as	O
127	36	an	O
127	37	investment	O
127	38	in	O
127	39	the	O
127	40	Anaheim	LOCATION
127	41	,	O
127	42	Calif	LOCATION
127	43	.,	O
127	44	company	O
127	45	.	O

42	40	containsPlace

128	0	VW	ORGANIZATION
128	1	'	O
128	2	S	O
128	3	AUDI	ORGANIZATION
128	4	SAYS	O
128	5	PROFIT	O
128	6	FELL	O
128	7	AROUND	O
128	8	50	O
128	9	PCT	O
128	10	IN	O
128	11	1986	O
128	12	Audi	ORGANIZATION
128	13	AG	ORGANIZATION
128	14	&	O
128	15	lt	O
128	16	;	O
128	17	NSUG	ORGANIZATION
128	18	.	O
128	19	F	O
128	20	>,	O
128	21	the	O
128	22	99	O
128	23	pct	O
128	24	owned	O
128	25	subsidiary	O
128	26	of	O
128	27	Volkswagen	ORGANIZATION
128	28	AG	ORGANIZATION
128	29	&	ORGANIZATION
128	30	lt	ORGANIZATION
128	31	;	O
128	32	VOWG	O
128	33	.	O
128	34	F	O
128	35	>,	O
128	36	said	O
128	37	profit	O
128	38	in	O
128	39	1986	O
128	40	fell	O
128	41	by	O
128	42	around	O
128	43	half	O
128	44	compared	O
128	45	with	O
128	46	1985	O
128	47	,	O
128	48	when	O
128	49	it	O
128	50	achieved	O
128	51	a	O
128	52	record	O
128	53	221	O
128	54	mln	O
128	55	marks	O
128	56	net	O
128	57	profit	O
128	58	,	O
128	59	a	O
128	60	rise	O
128	61	of	O
128	62	19	O
128	63	.	O
128	64	5	O
128	65	pct	O
128	66	on	O
128	67	the	O
128	68	previous	O
128	69	year	O
128	70	.	O

12	27	parentOrganization
27	0	brand

129	0	Asked	O
129	1	whether	O
129	2	Audi	ORGANIZATION
129	3	would	O
129	4	pay	O
129	5	a	O
129	6	dividend	O
129	7	to	O
129	8	VW	ORGANIZATION
129	9	to	O
129	10	help	O
129	11	the	O
129	12	parent	O
129	13	company	O
129	14	overcome	O
129	15	its	O
129	16	currency	O
129	17	losses	O
129	18	,	O
129	19	Habbel	PERSON
129	20	said	O
129	21	Audi	ORGANIZATION
129	22	would	O
129	23	ensure	O
129	24	VW	ORGANIZATION
129	25	got	O
129	26	a	O
129	27	share	O
129	28	of	O
129	29	profits	O
129	30	.	O

2	8	parentOrganization
19	2	employee
21	24	parentOrganization

130	0	In	O
130	1	the	O
130	2	previous	O
130	3	10	O
130	4	years	O
130	5	VW	ORGANIZATION
130	6	had	O
130	7	received	O
130	8	80	O
130	9	pct	O
130	10	of	O
130	11	Audi	ORGANIZATION
130	12	'	O
130	13	s	O
130	14	earnings	O
130	15	as	O
130	16	a	O
130	17	dividend	O
130	18	.	O

11	5	parentOrganization

131	0	Habbel	PERSON
131	1	blamed	O
131	2	the	O
131	3	profit	O
131	4	decline	O
131	5	on	O
131	6	disruptions	O
131	7	to	O
131	8	output	O
131	9	caused	O
131	10	by	O
131	11	the	O
131	12	introduction	O
131	13	of	O
131	14	the	O
131	15	new	O
131	16	Audi	ORGANIZATION
131	17	80	O
131	18	model	O
131	19	,	O
131	20	on	O
131	21	currency	O
131	22	factors	O
131	23	and	O
131	24	on	O
131	25	negative	O
131	26	publicity	O
131	27	in	O
131	28	the	O
131	29	U	O
131	30	.	O
131	31	S	O
131	32	.	O
131	33	About	O
131	34	alleged	O
131	35	"	O
131	36	sudden	O
131	37	acceleration	O
131	38	"	O
131	39	of	O
131	40	some	O
131	41	of	O
131	42	its	O
131	43	Audi	O
131	44	5000	O
131	45	models	O
131	46	.	O

16	0	employee

132	0	Habbel	PERSON
132	1	said	O
132	2	the	O
132	3	new	O
132	4	Audi	ORGANIZATION
132	5	80	O
132	6	had	O
132	7	sold	O
132	8	extremely	O
132	9	well	O
132	10	in	O
132	11	the	O
132	12	first	O
132	13	two	O
132	14	months	O
132	15	of	O
132	16	1987	O
132	17	,	O
132	18	helping	O
132	19	Audi	ORGANIZATION
132	20	to	O
132	21	increase	O
132	22	its	O
132	23	overall	O
132	24	market	O
132	25	share	O
132	26	in	O
132	27	West	LOCATION
132	28	Germany	LOCATION
132	29	to	O
132	30	8	O
132	31	.	O
132	32	4	O
132	33	pct	O
132	34	from	O
132	35	5	O
132	36	.	O
132	37	2	O
132	38	pct	O
132	39	in	O
132	40	the	O
132	41	same	O
132	42	months	O
132	43	of	O
132	44	1986	O
132	45	.	O

4	0	employee
19	27	location

133	0	Habbel	PERSON
133	1	said	O
133	2	Audi	ORGANIZATION
133	3	expected	O
133	4	the	O
133	5	rise	O
133	6	in	O
133	7	output	O
133	8	to	O
133	9	lead	O
133	10	to	O
133	11	further	O
133	12	new	O
133	13	hiring	O
133	14	of	O
133	15	employees	O
133	16	.	O

2	0	employee

134	0	GRAIN	O
134	1	SHIPS	O
134	2	LOADING	O
134	3	AT	O
134	4	PORTLAND	LOCATION
134	5	There	O
134	6	were	O
134	7	three	O
134	8	grain	O
134	9	ships	O
134	10	loading	O
134	11	and	O
134	12	two	O
134	13	ships	O
134	14	were	O
134	15	waiting	O
134	16	to	O
134	17	load	O
134	18	at	O
134	19	Portland	LOCATION
134	20	,	O
134	21	according	O
134	22	to	O
134	23	the	O
134	24	Portland	ORGANIZATION
134	25	Merchants	ORGANIZATION
134	26	Exchange	ORGANIZATION
134	27	.	O

24	19	location

135	0	"	O
135	1	People	O
135	2	,	O
135	3	however	O
135	4	,	O
135	5	cannot	O
135	6	afford	O
135	7	to	O
135	8	wait	O
135	9	for	O
135	10	drilling	O
135	11	to	O
135	12	go	O
135	13	up	O
135	14	to	O
135	15	start	O
135	16	buying	O
135	17	,"	O
135	18	said	O
135	19	Sandi	PERSON
135	20	Haber	PERSON
135	21	Sweeney	PERSON
135	22	,	O
135	23	senior	O
135	24	research	O
135	25	analyst	O
135	26	at	O
135	27	Sanford	ORGANIZATION
135	28	C	ORGANIZATION
135	29	.	O
135	30	Bernstein	PERSON
135	31	and	O
135	32	Co	ORGANIZATION
135	33	Inc	ORGANIZATION
135	34	.	O

27	19	employee

136	0	Among	O
136	1	the	O
136	2	recommended	O
136	3	buys	O
136	4	are	O
136	5	Schlumberger	ORGANIZATION
136	6	Ltd	ORGANIZATION
136	7	&	O
136	8	lt	O
136	9	;	O
136	10	SLB	O
136	11	>,	O
136	12	Halliburton	ORGANIZATION
136	13	Co	ORGANIZATION
136	14	&	ORGANIZATION
136	15	lt	ORGANIZATION
136	16	;	O
136	17	HAL	O
136	18	>,	O
136	19	Dresser	ORGANIZATION
136	20	Industries	ORGANIZATION
136	21	&	O
136	22	lt	O
136	23	;	O
136	24	DI	O
136	25	>,	O
136	26	Baker	O
136	27	International	O
136	28	&	O
136	29	lt	O
136	30	;	O
136	31	BKO	O
136	32	>,	O
136	33	and	O
136	34	McDermott	ORGANIZATION
136	35	International	ORGANIZATION
136	36	Inc	ORGANIZATION
136	37	&	O
136	38	lt	O
136	39	;	O
136	40	MDR	O
136	41	>,	O
136	42	which	O
136	43	may	O
136	44	be	O
136	45	the	O
136	46	target	O
136	47	of	O
136	48	a	O
136	49	takeover	O
136	50	by	O
136	51	Harold	PERSON
136	52	Simmons	PERSON
136	53	,	O
136	54	a	O
136	55	Dallas	LOCATION
136	56	-	O
136	57	based	O
136	58	investor	O
136	59	.	O

51	55	homeLocation

137	0	Analysts	O
137	1	said	O
137	2	although	O
137	3	major	O
137	4	oil	O
137	5	companies	O
137	6	are	O
137	7	increasing	O
137	8	exploration	O
137	9	and	O
137	10	development	O
137	11	overseas	O
137	12	,	O
137	13	they	O
137	14	expect	O
137	15	the	O
137	16	pickup	O
137	17	in	O
137	18	oil	O
137	19	services	O
137	20	will	O
137	21	begin	O
137	22	in	O
137	23	the	O
137	24	U	ORGANIZATION
137	25	.	O
137	26	S	O
137	27	.	O
137	28	"	O
137	29	Activity	O
137	30	in	O
137	31	the	O
137	32	U	O
137	33	.	O
137	34	S	O
137	35	.	O
137	36	is	O
137	37	so	O
137	38	depressed	O
137	39	it	O
137	40	should	O
137	41	move	O
137	42	up	O
137	43	faster	O
137	44	,"	O
137	45	said	O
137	46	Vishnu	PERSON
137	47	Sharp	PERSON
137	48	of	O
137	49	Goldman	ORGANIZATION
137	50	Sachs	ORGANIZATION
137	51	.	O

49	46	employee

138	0	The	O
138	1	average	O
138	2	number	O
138	3	of	O
138	4	working	O
138	5	rigs	O
138	6	in	O
138	7	the	O
138	8	U	O
138	9	.	O
138	10	S	O
138	11	.	O
138	12	for	O
138	13	1987	O
138	14	is	O
138	15	projected	O
138	16	at	O
138	17	978	O
138	18	versus	O
138	19	964	O
138	20	in	O
138	21	1986	O
138	22	,	O
138	23	according	O
138	24	to	O
138	25	Ike	PERSON
138	26	Kerridge	PERSON
138	27	,	O
138	28	vice	O
138	29	president	O
138	30	of	O
138	31	stockholder	O
138	32	relations	O
138	33	at	O
138	34	Hughes	ORGANIZATION
138	35	Tool	ORGANIZATION
138	36	.	O

34	25	employee

139	0	"	O
139	1	Halliburton	ORGANIZATION
139	2	is	O
139	3	the	O
139	4	best	O
139	5	value	O
139	6	,"	O
139	7	said	O
139	8	Jeffrey	PERSON
139	9	Freedman	PERSON
139	10	,	O
139	11	vice	O
139	12	president	O
139	13	at	O
139	14	Smith	ORGANIZATION
139	15	Barney	ORGANIZATION
139	16	,	O
139	17	Harris	PERSON
139	18	and	O
139	19	Upham	ORGANIZATION
139	20	Inc	ORGANIZATION
139	21	,	O
139	22	adding	O
139	23	the	O
139	24	company	O
139	25	controls	O
139	26	the	O
139	27	greatest	O
139	28	amount	O
139	29	of	O
139	30	liquidity	O
139	31	of	O
139	32	common	O
139	33	stock	O
139	34	market	O
139	35	value	O
139	36	,	O
139	37	is	O
139	38	diversifed	O
139	39	in	O
139	40	non	O
139	41	-	O
139	42	oil	O
139	43	field	O
139	44	businesess	O
139	45	,	O
139	46	and	O
139	47	has	O
139	48	the	O
139	49	lowest	O
139	50	multiple	O
139	51	of	O
139	52	stock	O
139	53	price	O
139	54	to	O
139	55	operating	O
139	56	cash	O
139	57	flow	O
139	58	including	O
139	59	debt	O
139	60	.	O

14	8	employee
1	14	parentOrganization

140	0	Schlumberger	ORGANIZATION
140	1	is	O
140	2	Freedman	PERSON
140	3	'	O
140	4	s	O
140	5	second	O
140	6	favorite	O
140	7	oil	O
140	8	service	O
140	9	stock	O
140	10	.	O


141	0	"	O
141	1	Schlumberger	ORGANIZATION
141	2	is	O
141	3	expected	O
141	4	to	O
141	5	continue	O
141	6	to	O
141	7	be	O
141	8	the	O
141	9	dominant	O
141	10	technical	O
141	11	leader	O
141	12	in	O
141	13	the	O
141	14	industry	O
141	15	,"	O
141	16	Freedman	PERSON
141	17	said	O
141	18	.	O


142	0	"	O
142	1	Schlumberger	ORGANIZATION
142	2	'	O
142	3	s	O
142	4	management	O
142	5	shift	O
142	6	,	O
142	7	asset	O
142	8	restructuring	O
142	9	,	O
142	10	including	O
142	11	a	O
142	12	pending	O
142	13	merger	O
142	14	of	O
142	15	Fairchild	ORGANIZATION
142	16	Semiconductor	ORGANIZATION
142	17	,	O
142	18	and	O
142	19	its	O
142	20	considerable	O
142	21	cash	O
142	22	horde	O
142	23	sets	O
142	24	the	O
142	25	stage	O
142	26	for	O
142	27	the	O
142	28	company	O
142	29	to	O
142	30	maximize	O
142	31	its	O
142	32	significant	O
142	33	industry	O
142	34	advantage	O
142	35	and	O
142	36	capitalize	O
142	37	on	O
142	38	the	O
142	39	project	O
142	40	upturn	O
142	41	in	O
142	42	exploration	O
142	43	and	O
142	44	development	O
142	45	activity	O
142	46	,"	O
142	47	according	O
142	48	to	O
142	49	a	O
142	50	report	O
142	51	by	O
142	52	George	PERSON
142	53	Gaspar	PERSON
142	54	,	O
142	55	first	O
142	56	vice	O
142	57	president	O
142	58	at	O
142	59	Robert	ORGANIZATION
142	60	W	ORGANIZATION
142	61	.	O
142	62	Baird	ORGANIZATION
142	63	and	ORGANIZATION
142	64	Co	ORGANIZATION
142	65	Inc	ORGANIZATION
142	66	.	O
142	67	Gaspar	PERSON
142	68	estimates	O
142	69	earnings	O
142	70	per	O
142	71	share	O
142	72	for	O
142	73	Schlumberger	ORGANIZATION
142	74	at	O
142	75	25	O
142	76	cts	O
142	77	for	O
142	78	1987	O
142	79	and	O
142	80	one	O
142	81	to	O
142	82	1	O
142	83	.	O
142	84	75	O
142	85	dlrs	O
142	86	in	O
142	87	1988	O
142	88	compared	O
142	89	with	O
142	90	20	O
142	91	cts	O
142	92	in	O
142	93	1986	O
142	94	excluding	O
142	95	a	O
142	96	fourth	O
142	97	quarter	O
142	98	special	O
142	99	charge	O
142	100	of	O
142	101	1	O
142	102	.	O
142	103	87	O
142	104	billion	O
142	105	dlrs	O
142	106	.	O

15	1	parentOrganization
59	52	employee

143	0	Bernstein	PERSON
143	1	'	O
143	2	s	O
143	3	Sandi	PERSON
143	4	Sweeney	PERSON
143	5	is	O
143	6	recommending	O
143	7	a	O
143	8	group	O
143	9	of	O
143	10	oil	O
143	11	service	O
143	12	companies	O
143	13	and	O
143	14	said	O
143	15	choosing	O
143	16	among	O
143	17	them	O
143	18	is	O
143	19	difficult	O
143	20	.	O

0	3	employee

144	0	Her	O
144	1	favorite	O
144	2	is	O
144	3	Baker	ORGANIZATION
144	4	International	ORGANIZATION
144	5	,	O
144	6	which	O
144	7	is	O
144	8	involved	O
144	9	in	O
144	10	a	O
144	11	possible	O
144	12	merger	O
144	13	with	O
144	14	Hughes	ORGANIZATION
144	15	Tool	ORGANIZATION
144	16	Co	ORGANIZATION
144	17	.	O
144	18	Dresser	ORGANIZATION
144	19	Industries	ORGANIZATION
144	20	will	O
144	21	also	O
144	22	benefit	O
144	23	from	O
144	24	the	O
144	25	recovery	O
144	26	but	O
144	27	possibly	O
144	28	not	O
144	29	as	O
144	30	much	O
144	31	as	O
144	32	other	O
144	33	companies	O
144	34	because	O
144	35	it	O
144	36	is	O
144	37	not	O
144	38	a	O
144	39	pure	O
144	40	service	O
144	41	company	O
144	42	,	O
144	43	Sweeney	PERSON
144	44	said	O
144	45	.	O

14	3	parentOrganization

145	0	GRAIN	O
145	1	SHIPS	O
145	2	LOADING	O
145	3	AT	O
145	4	PORTLAND	LOCATION
145	5	There	O
145	6	were	O
145	7	five	O
145	8	grain	O
145	9	ships	O
145	10	loading	O
145	11	and	O
145	12	three	O
145	13	ships	O
145	14	were	O
145	15	waiting	O
145	16	to	O
145	17	load	O
145	18	at	O
145	19	Portland	LOCATION
145	20	,	O
145	21	according	O
145	22	to	O
145	23	the	O
145	24	Portland	ORGANIZATION
145	25	Merchants	ORGANIZATION
145	26	Exchange	ORGANIZATION
145	27	.	O

24	19	location

146	0	A	O
146	1	major	O
146	2	tax	O
146	3	payment	O
146	4	period	O
146	5	by	O
146	6	banks	O
146	7	on	O
146	8	behalf	O
146	9	of	O
146	10	customers	O
146	11	,	O
146	12	payments	O
146	13	for	O
146	14	the	O
146	15	federal	O
146	16	railways	O
146	17	loan	O
146	18	stock	O
146	19	and	O
146	20	repayments	O
146	21	of	O
146	22	mark	O
146	23	liabilities	O
146	24	incurred	O
146	25	by	O
146	26	foreign	O
146	27	central	O
146	28	banks	O
146	29	with	O
146	30	the	O
146	31	Bundesbank	ORGANIZATION
146	32	in	O
146	33	the	O
146	34	framework	O
146	35	of	O
146	36	the	O
146	37	European	ORGANIZATION
146	38	Monetary	ORGANIZATION
146	39	System	ORGANIZATION
146	40	(	O
146	41	EMS	ORGANIZATION
146	42	)	O
146	43	are	O
146	44	likely	O
146	45	to	O
146	46	significantly	O
146	47	burden	O
146	48	the	O
146	49	system	O
146	50	.	O

31	37	memberOf
37	41	brand

147	0	ILLINOIS	LOCATION
147	1	CO	O
147	2	-	O
147	3	OP	O
147	4	FUTURES	O
147	5	DISSOLUTION	O
147	6	VOTE	O
147	7	SET	O
147	8	The	O
147	9	shareholders	O
147	10	of	O
147	11	Illinois	ORGANIZATION
147	12	Cooperative	ORGANIZATION
147	13	Futures	ORGANIZATION
147	14	Co	ORGANIZATION
147	15	.,	O
147	16	the	O
147	17	futures	O
147	18	trading	O
147	19	arm	O
147	20	of	O
147	21	many	O
147	22	Midwest	LOCATION
147	23	farm	O
147	24	cooperatives	O
147	25	for	O
147	26	more	O
147	27	than	O
147	28	25	O
147	29	years	O
147	30	,	O
147	31	will	O
147	32	vote	O
147	33	Wednesday	O
147	34	on	O
147	35	its	O
147	36	possible	O
147	37	dissolution	O
147	38	.	O

11	22	location

148	0	Sources	O
148	1	close	O
148	2	to	O
148	3	the	O
148	4	organization	O
148	5	told	O
148	6	Reuters	ORGANIZATION
148	7	the	O
148	8	pullout	O
148	9	of	O
148	10	Growmark	ORGANIZATION
148	11	,	O
148	12	Inc	O
148	13	.,	O
148	14	which	O
148	15	holds	O
148	16	more	O
148	17	than	O
148	18	70	O
148	19	pct	O
148	20	of	O
148	21	the	O
148	22	capital	O
148	23	stock	O
148	24	,	O
148	25	led	O
148	26	to	O
148	27	the	O
148	28	call	O
148	29	for	O
148	30	dissolution	O
148	31	.	O


149	0	Ironically	O
149	1	,	O
149	2	it	O
149	3	was	O
149	4	Growmark	ORGANIZATION
149	5	,	O
149	6	at	O
149	7	that	O
149	8	time	O
149	9	a	O
149	10	regional	O
149	11	farm	O
149	12	cooperative	O
149	13	with	O
149	14	major	O
149	15	river	O
149	16	terminal	O
149	17	elevators	O
149	18	,	O
149	19	that	O
149	20	founded	O
149	21	Illinois	ORGANIZATION
149	22	Cooperative	ORGANIZATION
149	23	Futures	ORGANIZATION
149	24	on	O
149	25	December	O
149	26	1	O
149	27	,	O
149	28	1960	O
149	29	.	O

21	4	parentOrganization

150	0	But	O
150	1	Growmark	ORGANIZATION
150	2	became	O
150	3	affiliated	O
150	4	last	O
150	5	year	O
150	6	with	O
150	7	Archer	PERSON
150	8	Daniels	PERSON
150	9	Midland	PERSON
150	10	of	O
150	11	Decatur	LOCATION
150	12	,	O
150	13	Ill	O
150	14	.,	O
150	15	and	O
150	16	markets	O
150	17	its	O
150	18	grain	O
150	19	through	O
150	20	a	O
150	21	joint	O
150	22	subsidiary	O
150	23	of	O
150	24	the	O
150	25	two	O
150	26	companies	O
150	27	,	O
150	28	ADM	ORGANIZATION
150	29		ORGANIZATION
150	30	Growmark	ORGANIZATION
150	31	.	O


151	0	With	O
151	1	that	O
151	2	relationship	O
151	3	,	O
151	4	Growmark	ORGANIZATION
151	5	no	O
151	6	longer	O
151	7	needs	O
151	8	to	O
151	9	trade	O
151	10	futures	O
151	11	through	O
151	12	the	O
151	13	cooperative	O
151	14	,	O
151	15	said	O
151	16	Tom	PERSON
151	17	Mulligan	PERSON
151	18	,	O
151	19	president	O
151	20	of	O
151	21	the	O
151	22	co	O
151	23	-	O
151	24	op	O
151	25	.	O

16	4	employee

152	0	A	O
152	1	notable	O
152	2	loss	O
152	3	was	O
152	4	AgriIndustries	ORGANIZATION
152	5	of	O
152	6	Iowa	LOCATION
152	7	,	O
152	8	which	O
152	9	became	O
152	10	affiliated	O
152	11	with	O
152	12	Cargill	ORGANIZATION
152	13	,	ORGANIZATION
152	14	Inc	ORGANIZATION
152	15	.	O
152	16	Illinois	ORGANIZATION
152	17	Co	ORGANIZATION
152	18	-	O
152	19	op	O
152	20	'	O
152	21	s	O
152	22	other	O
152	23	members	O
152	24	include	O
152	25	such	O
152	26	regional	O
152	27	cooperatives	O
152	28	as	O
152	29	Indiana	ORGANIZATION
152	30	Grain	ORGANIZATION
152	31	,	O
152	32	based	O
152	33	in	O
152	34	Indianapolis	LOCATION
152	35	,	O
152	36	Goldkist	ORGANIZATION
152	37	,	O
152	38	of	O
152	39	Atlanta	LOCATION
152	40	,	O
152	41	Ga	O
152	42	.,	O
152	43	Midstates	O
152	44	in	O
152	45	Toledo	LOCATION
152	46	,	O
152	47	Ohio	LOCATION
152	48	,	O
152	49	Farmland	ORGANIZATION
152	50	Industries	ORGANIZATION
152	51	in	O
152	52	Kansas	LOCATION
152	53	City	LOCATION
152	54	,	O
152	55	Mo	O
152	56	.,	O
152	57	Farmers	ORGANIZATION
152	58	Commodities	ORGANIZATION
152	59	,	O
152	60	Des	PERSON
152	61	Moines	PERSON
152	62	,	O
152	63	and	O
152	64	Harvest	LOCATION
152	65	States	LOCATION
152	66	in	O
152	67	Minneapolis	LOCATION
152	68	.	O

4	6	location
29	16	memberOf
29	34	location
36	16	memberOf
36	39	location
47	45	containsPlace
49	16	memberOf
49	52	location
57	16	memberOf

153	0	Don	PERSON
153	1	Hanes	PERSON
153	2	,	O
153	3	vice	O
153	4	president	O
153	5	for	O
153	6	communications	O
153	7	with	O
153	8	the	O
153	9	National	ORGANIZATION
153	10	Council	ORGANIZATION
153	11	of	ORGANIZATION
153	12	Farm	ORGANIZATION
153	13	Cooperatives	ORGANIZATION
153	14	,	O
153	15	said	O
153	16	5	O
153	17	,	O
153	18	600	O
153	19	cooperatives	O
153	20	exist	O
153	21	today	O
153	22	,	O
153	23	down	O
153	24	from	O
153	25	6	O
153	26	,	O
153	27	700	O
153	28	five	O
153	29	years	O
153	30	ago	O
153	31	.	O

9	0	employee

154	0	Steven	PERSON
154	1	W	PERSON
154	2	.	PERSON
154	3	Cavanaugh	PERSON
154	4	,	O
154	5	vice	O
154	6	president	O
154	7	for	O
154	8	grain	O
154	9	marketing	O
154	10	with	O
154	11	Indiana	ORGANIZATION
154	12	Grain	ORGANIZATION
154	13	,	O
154	14	said	O
154	15	he	O
154	16	would	O
154	17	prefer	O
154	18	to	O
154	19	trade	O
154	20	futures	O
154	21	through	O
154	22	a	O
154	23	Chicago	LOCATION
154	24	-	O
154	25	based	O
154	26	cooperative	O
154	27	.	O

11	0	employee

155	0	According	O
155	1	to	O
155	2	the	O
155	3	company	O
155	4	'	O
155	5	s	O
155	6	1986	O
155	7	annual	O
155	8	report	O
155	9	,	O
155	10	Growmark	ORGANIZATION
155	11	owns	O
155	12	90	O
155	13	pct	O
155	14	of	O
155	15	the	O
155	16	preferred	O
155	17	shares	O
155	18	and	O
155	19	four	O
155	20	pct	O
155	21	of	O
155	22	the	O
155	23	common	O
155	24	shares	O
155	25	of	O
155	26	Illinois	ORGANIZATION
155	27	Cooperative	ORGANIZATION
155	28	Futures	ORGANIZATION
155	29	Co	ORGANIZATION
155	30	.	O
155	31	Mulligan	PERSON
155	32	declined	O
155	33	to	O
155	34	speculate	O
155	35	on	O
155	36	how	O
155	37	much	O
155	38	of	O
155	39	the	O
155	40	capital	O
155	41	Growmark	ORGANIZATION
155	42	is	O
155	43	entitled	O
155	44	to	O
155	45	.	O

26	10	parentOrganization
41	31	employee

156	0	However	O
156	1	,	O
156	2	Mulligan	PERSON
156	3	said	O
156	4	the	O
156	5	company	O
156	6	could	O
156	7	continue	O
156	8	to	O
156	9	meet	O
156	10	minimum	O
156	11	capital	O
156	12	requirements	O
156	13	to	O
156	14	trade	O
156	15	futures	O
156	16	even	O
156	17	if	O
156	18	Growmark	ORGANIZATION
156	19	pulled	O
156	20	out	O
156	21	.	O

18	2	employee

157	0	FRENCH	O
157	1	STATE	O
157	2	SELL	O
157	3	-	O
157	4	OFFS	O
157	5	RAISE	O
157	6	52	O
157	7	BILLION	O
157	8	FRANCS	O
157	9	The	O
157	10	French	O
157	11	government	O
157	12	'	O
157	13	s	O
157	14	privatisation	O
157	15	program	O
157	16	,	O
157	17	which	O
157	18	began	O
157	19	late	O
157	20	last	O
157	21	year	O
157	22	,	O
157	23	has	O
157	24	earned	O
157	25	the	O
157	26	French	ORGANIZATION
157	27	State	ORGANIZATION
157	28	about	O
157	29	52	O
157	30	billion	O
157	31	francs	O
157	32	to	O
157	33	date	O
157	34	,	O
157	35	the	O
157	36	Finance	ORGANIZATION
157	37	Ministry	ORGANIZATION
157	38	said	O
157	39	.	O

36	26	memberOf

158	0	The	O
158	1	Ministry	ORGANIZATION
158	2	said	O
158	3	in	O
158	4	a	O
158	5	communique	O
158	6	that	O
158	7	the	O
158	8	returns	O
158	9	included	O
158	10	banking	O
158	11	group	O
158	12	Societe	ORGANIZATION
158	13	Generale	ORGANIZATION
158	14	&	ORGANIZATION
158	15	lt	ORGANIZATION
158	16	;	O
158	17	SGEN	O
158	18	.	O
158	19	PA	O
158	20	>,	O
158	21	which	O
158	22	began	O
158	23	its	O
158	24	two	O
158	25	-	O
158	26	week	O
158	27	public	O
158	28	flotation	O
158	29	last	O
158	30	Monday	O
158	31	.	O


159	0	CHINA	LOCATION
159	1	,	O
159	2	TAIWAN	LOCATION
159	3	TRADE	O
159	4	VIA	O
159	5	HONG	LOCATION
159	6	KONG	LOCATION
159	7	FELL	O
159	8	IN	O
159	9	1986	O
159	10	The	O
159	11	value	O
159	12	of	O
159	13	trade	O
159	14	between	O
159	15	China	LOCATION
159	16	and	O
159	17	Taiwan	LOCATION
159	18	via	O
159	19	Hong	LOCATION
159	20	Kong	LOCATION
159	21	fell	O
159	22	13	O
159	23	pct	O
159	24	to	O
159	25	7	O
159	26	.	O
159	27	45	O
159	28	billion	O
159	29	H	O
159	30	.	O
159	31	K	O
159	32	.	O

15	19	containsPlace

160	0	Dlrs	O
160	1	in	O
160	2	1986	O
160	3	from	O
160	4	8	O
160	5	.	O
160	6	59	O
160	7	billion	O
160	8	dlrs	O
160	9	in	O
160	10	1985	O
160	11	,	O
160	12	Hong	LOCATION
160	13	Kong	LOCATION
160	14	'	O
160	15	s	O
160	16	Census	ORGANIZATION
160	17	and	ORGANIZATION
160	18	Statistics	ORGANIZATION
160	19	Department	ORGANIZATION
160	20	said	O
160	21	.	O

16	12	location

161	0	Taiwan	LOCATION
161	1	'	O
161	2	s	O
161	3	exports	O
161	4	to	O
161	5	China	LOCATION
161	6	through	O
161	7	Hong	LOCATION
161	8	Kong	LOCATION
161	9	fell	O
161	10	to	O
161	11	6	O
161	12	.	O
161	13	33	O
161	14	billion	O
161	15	dlrs	O
161	16	last	O
161	17	year	O
161	18	from	O
161	19	7	O
161	20	.	O
161	21	69	O
161	22	billion	O
161	23	in	O
161	24	1985	O
161	25	,	O
161	26	while	O
161	27	China	LOCATION
161	28	'	O
161	29	s	O
161	30	exports	O
161	31	rose	O
161	32	to	O
161	33	1	O
161	34	.	O
161	35	12	O
161	36	billion	O
161	37	dlrs	O
161	38	from	O
161	39	904	O
161	40	mln	O
161	41	dlrs	O
161	42	.	O

5	7	containsPlace

162	0	Economists	O
162	1	in	O
162	2	Hong	LOCATION
162	3	Kong	LOCATION
162	4	told	O
162	5	Reuters	ORGANIZATION
162	6	that	O
162	7	China	LOCATION
162	8	'	O
162	9	s	O
162	10	controls	O
162	11	on	O
162	12	scarce	O
162	13	foreign	O
162	14	currency	O
162	15	hurt	O
162	16	its	O
162	17	imports	O
162	18	of	O
162	19	Taiwanese	O
162	20	consumer	O
162	21	goods	O
162	22	,	O
162	23	such	O
162	24	as	O
162	25	electric	O
162	26	fans	O
162	27	and	O
162	28	television	O
162	29	sets	O
162	30	.	O

7	2	containsPlace

163	0	Herbal	O
163	1	medicine	O
163	2	and	O
163	3	textiles	O
163	4	were	O
163	5	among	O
163	6	China	LOCATION
163	7	'	O
163	8	s	O
163	9	chief	O
163	10	exports	O
163	11	to	O
163	12	Taiwan	LOCATION
163	13	.	O


164	0	Taiwan	LOCATION
164	1	does	O
164	2	not	O
164	3	allow	O
164	4	direct	O
164	5	trade	O
164	6	with	O
164	7	China	LOCATION
164	8	and	O
164	9	indirect	O
164	10	trade	O
164	11	is	O
164	12	routed	O
164	13	mainly	O
164	14	through	O
164	15	Hong	LOCATION
164	16	Kong	LOCATION
164	17	.	O

7	15	containsPlace

165	0	SQUIBB	O
165	1	&	O
165	2	lt	O
165	3	;	O
165	4	SQB	O
165	5	>	O
165	6	SAID	O
165	7	NOT	O
165	8	INTERESTED	O
165	9	IN	O
165	10	BUYING	O
165	11	CETUS	O
165	12	Robert	PERSON
165	13	Fildes	PERSON
165	14	,	O
165	15	president	O
165	16	and	O
165	17	chief	O
165	18	executive	O
165	19	of	O
165	20	Cetus	ORGANIZATION
165	21	Corp	ORGANIZATION
165	22	&	ORGANIZATION
165	23	lt	ORGANIZATION
165	24	;	O
165	25	CTUS	O
165	26	.	O
165	27	O	O
165	28	>,	O
165	29	told	O
165	30	Reuters	ORGANIZATION
165	31	that	O
165	32	Squibb	ORGANIZATION
165	33	Corp	ORGANIZATION
165	34	is	O
165	35	not	O
165	36	interested	O
165	37	in	O
165	38	buying	O
165	39	Cetus	ORGANIZATION
165	40	.	O

20	12	employee

166	0	Earlier	O
166	1	the	O
166	2	companies	O
166	3	said	O
166	4	Squibb	ORGANIZATION
166	5	would	O
166	6	buy	O
166	7	from	O
166	8	Cetus	ORGANIZATION
166	9	a	O
166	10	five	O
166	11	pct	O
166	12	equity	O
166	13	postion	O
166	14	in	O
166	15	Cetus	ORGANIZATION
166	16	for	O
166	17	about	O
166	18	40	O
166	19	mln	O
166	20	dlrs	O
166	21	.	O


167	0	"	O
167	1	This	O
167	2	is	O
167	3	not	O
167	4	an	O
167	5	attempt	O
167	6	by	O
167	7	Squibb	ORGANIZATION
167	8	to	O
167	9	become	O
167	10	a	O
167	11	major	O
167	12	majority	O
167	13	holder	O
167	14	in	O
167	15	Cetus	ORGANIZATION
167	16	,"	O
167	17	Fildes	PERSON
167	18	told	O
167	19	Reuters	ORGANIZATION
167	20	in	O
167	21	an	O
167	22	interview	O
167	23	.	O

15	17	employee

168	0	"	O
168	1	Squibb	ORGANIZATION
168	2	has	O
168	3	not	O
168	4	approached	O
168	5	us	O
168	6	with	O
168	7	any	O
168	8	indication	O
168	9	that	O
168	10	they	O
168	11	want	O
168	12	to	O
168	13	acquire	O
168	14	us	O
168	15	and	O
168	16	we	O
168	17	wouldn	O
168	18	'	O
168	19	t	O
168	20	be	O
168	21	interested	O
168	22	in	O
168	23	that	O
168	24	kind	O
168	25	of	O
168	26	arrangement	O
168	27	,"	O
168	28	said	O
168	29	Fildes	PERSON
168	30	.	O


169	0	Squibb	ORGANIZATION
169	1	could	O
169	2	not	O
169	3	be	O
169	4	reached	O
169	5	to	O
169	6	comment	O
169	7	on	O
169	8	the	O
169	9	late	O
169	10	comments	O
169	11	by	O
169	12	Fildes	PERSON
169	13	.	O


170	0	Squibb	ORGANIZATION
170	1	is	O
170	2	Cetus	ORGANIZATION
170	3	'	O
170	4	first	O
170	5	pharmaceutical	O
170	6	partner	O
170	7	and	O
170	8	the	O
170	9	only	O
170	10	one	O
170	11	to	O
170	12	own	O
170	13	an	O
170	14	equity	O
170	15	position	O
170	16	in	O
170	17	Cetus	ORGANIZATION
170	18	.	O


171	0	Eastman	ORGANIZATION
171	1	Kodak	ORGANIZATION
171	2	Co	ORGANIZATION
171	3	&	ORGANIZATION
171	4	lt	ORGANIZATION
171	5	;	O
171	6	EK	O
171	7	>	O
171	8	and	O
171	9	W	O
171	10	.	O
171	11	R	O
171	12	.	O
171	13	Grace	O
171	14	&	O
171	15	lt	O
171	16	;	O
171	17	WR	O
171	18	>	O
171	19	both	O
171	20	have	O
171	21	joint	O
171	22	ventures	O
171	23	with	O
171	24	Cetus	ORGANIZATION
171	25	,	O
171	26	but	O
171	27	neither	O
171	28	owns	O
171	29	an	O
171	30	equity	O
171	31	position	O
171	32	in	O
171	33	the	O
171	34	company	O
171	35	,	O
171	36	said	O
171	37	Fildes	PERSON
171	38	.	O


172	0	Cetus	ORGANIZATION
172	1	has	O
172	2	a	O
172	3	venture	O
172	4	with	O
172	5	Kodak	ORGANIZATION
172	6	to	O
172	7	develp	O
172	8	diagnostic	O
172	9	products	O
172	10	and	O
172	11	with	O
172	12	Grace	PERSON
172	13	to	O
172	14	develop	O
172	15	agricultural	O
172	16	products	O
172	17	.	O


173	0	Earlier	O
173	1	,	O
173	2	Squibb	ORGANIZATION
173	3	and	O
173	4	Cetus	ORGANIZATION
173	5	announced	O
173	6	in	O
173	7	a	O
173	8	joint	O
173	9	statement	O
173	10	an	O
173	11	agreement	O
173	12	in	O
173	13	principle	O
173	14	to	O
173	15	form	O
173	16	a	O
173	17	joint	O
173	18	venture	O
173	19	to	O
173	20	develop	O
173	21	new	O
173	22	biotechnology	O
173	23	products	O
173	24	in	O
173	25	several	O
173	26	fields	O
173	27	.	O


174	0	As	O
174	1	part	O
174	2	of	O
174	3	the	O
174	4	deal	O
174	5	Squibb	ORGANIZATION
174	6	will	O
174	7	license	O
174	8	several	O
174	9	of	O
174	10	Cetus	ORGANIZATION
174	11	'	O
174	12	anticancer	O
174	13	agents	O
174	14	,	O
174	15	including	O
174	16	interleukin	O
174	17	-	O
174	18	2	O
174	19	,	O
174	20	in	O
174	21	development	O
174	22	.	O


175	0	Squibb	ORGANIZATION
175	1	will	O
175	2	sell	O
175	3	the	O
175	4	drugs	O
175	5	only	O
175	6	in	O
175	7	Japan	LOCATION
175	8	and	O
175	9	other	O
175	10	markets	O
175	11	but	O
175	12	not	O
175	13	in	O
175	14	North	O
175	15	American	O
175	16	and	O
175	17	Western	LOCATION
175	18	Europe	LOCATION
175	19	.	O


176	0	"	O
176	1	We	O
176	2	wouldn	O
176	3	'	O
176	4	t	O
176	5	have	O
176	6	done	O
176	7	this	O
176	8	deal	O
176	9	had	O
176	10	it	O
176	11	not	O
176	12	been	O
176	13	understood	O
176	14	that	O
176	15	Cetus	ORGANIZATION
176	16	wants	O
176	17	to	O
176	18	build	O
176	19	its	O
176	20	own	O
176	21	fully	O
176	22	integrated	O
176	23	business	O
176	24	in	O
176	25	North	LOCATION
176	26	America	LOCATION
176	27	and	O
176	28	Europe	LOCATION
176	29	,"	O
176	30	said	O
176	31	Fildes	PERSON
176	32	.	O

15	31	employee
15	25	location

177	0	He	O
177	1	said	O
177	2	Squibb	ORGANIZATION
177	3	was	O
177	4	the	O
177	5	good	O
177	6	partner	O
177	7	because	O
177	8	Squibb	ORGANIZATION
177	9	has	O
177	10	a	O
177	11	major	O
177	12	joint	O
177	13	venture	O
177	14	in	O
177	15	Japan	LOCATION
177	16	and	O
177	17	has	O
177	18	sales	O
177	19	capabilities	O
177	20	of	O
177	21	its	O
177	22	own	O
177	23	in	O
177	24	that	O
177	25	market	O
177	26	.	O


178	0	Fildes	PERSON
178	1	said	O
178	2	Cetus	ORGANIZATION
178	3	has	O
178	4	shunned	O
178	5	licensing	O
178	6	arrangements	O
178	7	with	O
178	8	pharmaceutical	O
178	9	companies	O
178	10	because	O
178	11	it	O
178	12	wanted	O
178	13	to	O
178	14	build	O
178	15	its	O
178	16	own	O
178	17	business	O
178	18	.	O

2	0	employee

179	0	But	O
179	1	Squibb	ORGANIZATION
179	2	'	O
179	3	s	O
179	4	investment	O
179	5	in	O
179	6	Cetus	ORGANIZATION
179	7	is	O
179	8	the	O
179	9	first	O
179	10	it	O
179	11	has	O
179	12	made	O
179	13	in	O
179	14	biotechnology	O
179	15	.	O


180	0	Fildes	PERSON
180	1	said	O
180	2	that	O
180	3	was	O
180	4	attractive	O
180	5	to	O
180	6	Cetus	ORGANIZATION
180	7	because	O
180	8	it	O
180	9	wanted	O
180	10	a	O
180	11	partner	O
180	12	that	O
180	13	didn	O
180	14	'	O
180	15	t	O
180	16	have	O
180	17	a	O
180	18	relationship	O
180	19	with	O
180	20	a	O
180	21	large	O
180	22	number	O
180	23	of	O
180	24	other	O
180	25	biotechnology	O
180	26	companies	O
180	27	."	O

6	0	employee

181	0	Fildes	PERSON
181	1	said	O
181	2	the	O
181	3	partnership	O
181	4	with	O
181	5	Squibb	ORGANIZATION
181	6	would	O
181	7	be	O
181	8	used	O
181	9	to	O
181	10	broaden	O
181	11	the	O
181	12	company	O
181	13	'	O
181	14	s	O
181	15	reach	O
181	16	in	O
181	17	such	O
181	18	big	O
181	19	money	O
181	20	making	O
181	21	areas	O
181	22	as	O
181	23	the	O
181	24	cardiovascular	O
181	25	,	O
181	26	anti	O
181	27	-	O
181	28	infective	O
181	29	and	O
181	30	the	O
181	31	anti	O
181	32	-	O
181	33	inflammatory	O
181	34	markets	O
181	35	.	O


182	0	Squibb	ORGANIZATION
182	1	is	O
182	2	also	O
182	3	investming	O
182	4	75	O
182	5	mln	O
182	6	dlrs	O
182	7	in	O
182	8	Cetus	ORGANIZATION
182	9	'	O
182	10	research	O
182	11	over	O
182	12	the	O
182	13	next	O
182	14	five	O
182	15	years	O
182	16	.	O


183	0	"	O
183	1	Squibb	ORGANIZATION
183	2	is	O
183	3	putting	O
183	4	up	O
183	5	over	O
183	6	75	O
183	7	mln	O
183	8	dlrs	O
183	9	in	O
183	10	research	O
183	11	and	O
183	12	development	O
183	13	to	O
183	14	make	O
183	15	it	O
183	16	happen	O
183	17	,	O
183	18	while	O
183	19	the	O
183	20	equity	O
183	21	position	O
183	22	part	O
183	23	of	O
183	24	the	O
183	25	package	O
183	26	is	O
183	27	simply	O
183	28	to	O
183	29	demonstrate	O
183	30	the	O
183	31	seriousness	O
183	32	of	O
183	33	this	O
183	34	partnership	O
183	35	,"	O
183	36	said	O
183	37	Fildes	PERSON
183	38	.	O

