0	0	The	DT	The	O
0	1	September-October	NNP	September-October	O
0	2	term	NN	term	O
0	3	jury	NN	jury	O
0	4	had	VBD	have	O
0	5	been	VBN	be	O
0	6	charged	VBN	charge	O
0	7	by	IN	by	O
0	8	Fulton	NNP	Fulton	ORGANIZATION
0	9	Superior	NNP	Superior	ORGANIZATION
0	10	Court	NNP	Court	ORGANIZATION
0	11	Judge	NNP	Judge	O
0	12	Durwood	NNP	Durwood	PERSON
0	13	Pye	NNP	Pye	PERSON
0	14	to	TO	to	O
0	15	investigate	VB	investigate	O
0	16	reports	NNS	report	O
0	17	of	IN	of	O
0	18	possible	JJ	possible	O
0	19	``	``	``	O
0	20	irregularities	NNS	irregularity	O
0	21	''	''	''	O
0	22	in	IN	in	O
0	23	the	DT	the	O
0	24	hard-fought	JJ	hard-fought	O
0	25	primary	NN	primary	O
0	26	which	WDT	which	O
0	27	was	VBD	be	O
0	28	won	VBN	win	O
0	29	by	IN	by	O
0	30	Mayor-nominate	NNP	Mayor-nominate	O
0	31	Ivan	NNP	Ivan	PERSON
0	32	Allen	NNP	Allen	PERSON
0	33	Jr.	NNP	Jr.	PERSON
0	34	.	.	.	O

8	12	employee

1	0	Mayor	NNP	Mayor	O
1	1	William	NNP	William	PERSON
1	2	B.	NNP	B.	PERSON
1	3	Hartsfield	NNP	Hartsfield	PERSON
1	4	filed	VBD	file	O
1	5	suit	NN	suit	O
1	6	for	IN	for	O
1	7	divorce	NN	divorce	O
1	8	from	IN	from	O
1	9	his	PRP$	his	O
1	10	wife	NN	wife	O
1	11	,	,	,	O
1	12	Pearl	NNP	Pearl	PERSON
1	13	Williams	NNP	Williams	PERSON
1	14	Hartsfield	NNP	Hartsfield	PERSON
1	15	,	,	,	O
1	16	in	IN	in	O
1	17	Fulton	NNP	Fulton	ORGANIZATION
1	18	Superior	NNP	Superior	ORGANIZATION
1	19	Court	NNP	Court	ORGANIZATION
1	20	Friday	NNP	Friday	O
1	21	.	.	.	O

1	12	spouse

2	0	They	PRP	They	O
2	1	have	VBP	have	O
2	2	a	DT	a	O
2	3	son	NN	son	O
2	4	,	,	,	O
2	5	William	NNP	William	PERSON
2	6	Berry	NNP	Berry	PERSON
2	7	Jr.	NNP	Jr.	PERSON
2	8	,	,	,	O
2	9	and	CC	and	O
2	10	a	DT	a	O
2	11	daughter	NN	daughter	O
2	12	,	,	,	O
2	13	Mrs.	NNP	Mrs.	O
2	14	J.	NNP	J.	PERSON
2	15	M.	NNP	M.	PERSON
2	16	Cheshire	NNP	Cheshire	PERSON
2	17	of	IN	of	PERSON
2	18	Griffin	NNP	Griffin	PERSON
2	19	.	.	.	O

5	14	relatedTo

3	0	He	PRP	He	O
3	1	will	MD	will	O
3	2	be	VB	be	O
3	3	succeeded	VBN	succeed	O
3	4	by	IN	by	O
3	5	Ivan	NNP	Ivan	PERSON
3	6	Allen	NNP	Allen	PERSON
3	7	Jr.	NNP	Jr.	PERSON
3	8	,	,	,	O
3	9	who	WP	who	O
3	10	became	VBD	become	O
3	11	a	DT	a	O
3	12	candidate	NN	candidate	O
3	13	in	IN	in	O
3	14	the	DT	the	O
3	15	Sept.	NNP	Sept.	O
3	16	13	CD	13	O
3	17	primary	NN	primary	O
3	18	after	IN	after	O
3	19	Mayor	NNP	Mayor	PERSON
3	20	Hartsfield	NNP	Hartsfield	PERSON
3	21	announced	VBD	announce	O
3	22	that	IN	that	O
3	23	he	PRP	he	O
3	24	would	MD	would	O
3	25	not	RB	not	O
3	26	run	VB	run	O
3	27	for	IN	for	O
3	28	reelection	NN	reelection	O
3	29	.	.	.	O


4	0	State	NNP	State	ORGANIZATION
4	1	Party	NNP	Party	ORGANIZATION
4	2	Chairman	NNP	Chairman	O
4	3	James	NNP	James	PERSON
4	4	W.	NNP	W.	PERSON
4	5	Dorsey	NNP	Dorsey	PERSON
4	6	added	VBD	add	O
4	7	that	IN	that	O
4	8	enthusiasm	NN	enthusiasm	O
4	9	was	VBD	be	O
4	10	picking	VBG	pick	O
4	11	up	RP	up	O
4	12	for	IN	for	O
4	13	a	DT	a	O
4	14	state	NN	state	O
4	15	rally	NN	rally	O
4	16	to	TO	to	O
4	17	be	VB	be	O
4	18	held	VBN	hold	O
4	19	Sept.	NNP	Sept.	O
4	20	8	CD	8	O
4	21	in	IN	in	O
4	22	Savannah	NNP	Savannah	LOCATION
4	23	at	IN	at	O
4	24	which	WDT	which	O
4	25	newly	RB	newly	O
4	26	elected	VBN	elect	O
4	27	Texas	NNP	Texas	LOCATION
4	28	Sen.	NNP	Sen.	O
4	29	John	NNP	John	PERSON
4	30	Tower	NNP	Tower	PERSON
4	31	will	MD	will	O
4	32	be	VB	be	O
4	33	the	DT	the	O
4	34	featured	JJ	featured	O
4	35	speaker	NN	speaker	O
4	36	.	.	.	O

0	3	employee
27	22	containsPlace
29	27	homeLocation

5	0	Sam	NNP	Sam	PERSON
5	1	Caldwell	NNP	Caldwell	PERSON
5	2	,	,	,	O
5	3	State	NNP	State	ORGANIZATION
5	4	Highway	NNP	Highway	ORGANIZATION
5	5	Department	NNP	Department	ORGANIZATION
5	6	public	JJ	public	O
5	7	relations	NNS	relation	O
5	8	director	NN	director	O
5	9	,	,	,	O
5	10	resigned	VBD	resign	O
5	11	Tuesday	NNP	Tuesday	O
5	12	to	TO	to	O
5	13	work	VB	work	O
5	14	for	IN	for	O
5	15	Lt.	NNP	Lt.	O
5	16	Gov.	NNP	Gov.	O
5	17	Garland	NNP	Garland	PERSON
5	18	Byrd's	NNP	Byrd's	O
5	19	campaign	NN	campaign	O
5	20	.	.	.	O

3	0	employee

6	0	When	WRB	When	O
6	1	the	DT	the	O
6	2	gubernatorial	JJ	gubernatorial	O
6	3	campaign	NN	campaign	O
6	4	starts	VBZ	start	O
6	5	,	,	,	O
6	6	Caldwell	NNP	Caldwell	PERSON
6	7	is	VBZ	be	O
6	8	expected	VBN	expect	O
6	9	to	TO	to	O
6	10	become	VB	become	O
6	11	a	DT	a	O
6	12	campaign	NN	campaign	O
6	13	coordinator	NN	coordinator	O
6	14	for	IN	for	O
6	15	Byrd	NNP	Byrd	PERSON
6	16	.	.	.	O

6	15	colleague

7	0	Vandiver	RB	Vandiver	PERSON
7	1	opened	VBD	open	O
7	2	his	PRP$	his	O
7	3	race	NN	race	O
7	4	for	IN	for	O
7	5	governor	NN	governor	O
7	6	in	IN	in	O
7	7	1958	CD	1958	O
7	8	with	IN	with	O
7	9	a	DT	a	O
7	10	battle	NN	battle	O
7	11	in	IN	in	O
7	12	the	DT	the	O
7	13	Legislature	NNP	Legislature	ORGANIZATION
7	14	against	IN	against	O
7	15	the	DT	the	O
7	16	issuance	NN	issuance	O
7	17	of	IN	of	O
7	18	$50	NNP	$50	O
7	19	million	CD	million	O
7	20	worth	NN	worth	O
7	21	of	IN	of	O
7	22	additional	JJ	additional	O
7	23	rural	JJ	rural	O
7	24	roads	NNS	road	O
7	25	bonds	NNS	bond	O
7	26	proposed	VBN	propose	O
7	27	by	IN	by	O
7	28	then	RB	then	O
7	29	Gov.	NNP	Gov.	O
7	30	Marvin	NNP	Marvin	PERSON
7	31	Griffin	NNP	Griffin	PERSON
7	32	.	.	.	O


8	0	The	DT	The	O
8	1	new	JJ	new	O
8	2	school	NN	school	O
8	3	superintendent	NN	superintendent	O
8	4	is	VBZ	be	O
8	5	Harry	NNP	Harry	PERSON
8	6	Davis	NNP	Davis	PERSON
8	7	,	,	,	O
8	8	a	DT	a	O
8	9	veteran	JJ	veteran	O
8	10	agriculture	NN	agriculture	O
8	11	teacher	NN	teacher	O
8	12	,	,	,	O
8	13	who	WP	who	O
8	14	defeated	VBD	defeat	O
8	15	Felix	NNP	Felix	PERSON
8	16	Bush	NNP	Bush	PERSON
8	17	,	,	,	O
8	18	a	DT	a	O
8	19	school	NN	school	O
8	20	principal	NN	principal	O
8	21	and	CC	and	O
8	22	chairman	NN	chairman	O
8	23	of	IN	of	O
8	24	the	DT	the	O
8	25	Miller	NNP	Miller	ORGANIZATION
8	26	County	NNP	County	ORGANIZATION
8	27	Democratic	NNP	Democratic	ORGANIZATION
8	28	Executive	NNP	Executive	ORGANIZATION
8	29	Committee	NNP	Committee	ORGANIZATION
8	30	.	.	.	O

25	15	employee

9	0	Davis	NNP	Davis	PERSON
9	1	received	VBD	receive	O
9	2	1,119	CD	1,119	O
9	3	votes	NNS	vote	O
9	4	in	IN	in	O
9	5	Saturday's	NNP	Saturday's	O
9	6	election	NN	election	O
9	7	,	,	,	O
9	8	and	CC	and	O
9	9	Bush	NNP	Bush	PERSON
9	10	got	VBD	get	O
9	11	402	CD	402	O
9	12	.	.	.	O


10	0	During	IN	During	O
10	1	the	DT	the	O
10	2	election	NN	election	O
10	3	campaign	NN	campaign	O
10	4	,	,	,	O
10	5	both	DT	both	O
10	6	candidates	NNS	candidate	O
10	7	,	,	,	O
10	8	Davis	NNP	Davis	PERSON
10	9	and	CC	and	O
10	10	Bush	NNP	Bush	PERSON
10	11	,	,	,	O
10	12	reportedly	RB	reportedly	O
10	13	received	VBD	receive	O
10	14	anonymous	JJ	anonymous	O
10	15	telephone	NN	telephone	O
10	16	calls	NNS	call	O
10	17	.	.	.	O


11	0	Dewey	NNP	Dewey	PERSON
11	1	Lawrence	NNP	Lawrence	PERSON
11	2	,	,	,	O
11	3	a	DT	a	O
11	4	Tyler	NNP	Tyler	PERSON
11	5	lawyer	NN	lawyer	O
11	6	representing	VBG	represent	O
11	7	the	DT	the	O
11	8	Texas	NNP	Texas	ORGANIZATION
11	9	Bankers	NNP	Bankers	ORGANIZATION
11	10	Association	NNP	Association	ORGANIZATION
11	11	,	,	,	O
11	12	sounded	VBD	sound	O
11	13	the	DT	the	O
11	14	opposition	NN	opposition	O
11	15	keynote	NN	keynote	O
11	16	when	WRB	when	O
11	17	he	PRP	he	O
11	18	said	VBD	say	O
11	19	it	PRP	it	O
11	20	would	MD	would	O
11	21	force	VB	force	O
11	22	banks	NNS	bank	O
11	23	to	TO	to	O
11	24	violate	VB	violate	O
11	25	their	PRP$	their	O
11	26	contractual	JJ	contractual	O
11	27	obligations	NNS	obligation	O
11	28	with	IN	with	O
11	29	depositors	NNS	depositor	O
11	30	and	CC	and	O
11	31	undermine	VB	undermine	O
11	32	the	DT	the	O
11	33	confidence	NN	confidence	O
11	34	of	IN	of	O
11	35	bank	NN	bank	O
11	36	customers	NNS	customer	O
11	37	.	.	.	O

8	0	employee

12	0	Rep.	NNP	Rep.	O
12	1	Charles	NNP	Charles	PERSON
12	2	E.	NNP	E.	PERSON
12	3	Hughes	NNP	Hughes	PERSON
12	4	of	IN	of	O
12	5	Sherman	NNP	Sherman	PERSON
12	6	,	,	,	O
12	7	sponsor	NN	sponsor	O
12	8	of	IN	of	O
12	9	the	DT	the	O
12	10	bill	NN	bill	O
12	11	,	,	,	O
12	12	said	VBD	say	O
12	13	a	DT	a	O
12	14	failure	NN	failure	O
12	15	to	TO	to	O
12	16	enact	VB	enact	O
12	17	it	PRP	it	O
12	18	would	MD	would	O
12	19	amount	VB	amount	O
12	20	``	``	``	O
12	21	to	TO	to	O
12	22	making	VBG	make	O
12	23	a	DT	a	O
12	24	gift	NN	gift	O
12	25	out	IN	out	O
12	26	of	IN	of	O
12	27	the	DT	the	O
12	28	taxpayers'	JJ	taxpayers'	O
12	29	pockets	NNS	pocket	O
12	30	to	TO	to	O
12	31	banks	NNS	bank	O
12	32	,	,	,	O
12	33	insurance	NN	insurance	O
12	34	and	CC	and	O
12	35	pipeline	NN	pipeline	O
12	36	companies	NNS	company	O
12	37	''	''	''	O
12	38	.	.	.	O


13	0	His	PRP$	His	O
13	1	contention	NN	contention	O
13	2	was	VBD	be	O
13	3	denied	VBN	deny	O
13	4	by	IN	by	O
13	5	several	JJ	several	O
13	6	bankers	NNS	banker	O
13	7	,	,	,	O
13	8	including	VBG	include	O
13	9	Scott	NNP	Scott	PERSON
13	10	Hudson	NNP	Hudson	PERSON
13	11	of	IN	of	O
13	12	Sherman	NNP	Sherman	PERSON
13	13	,	,	,	O
13	14	Gaynor	NNP	Gaynor	PERSON
13	15	B.	NNP	B.	PERSON
13	16	Jones	NNP	Jones	PERSON
13	17	of	IN	of	O
13	18	Houston	NNP	Houston	LOCATION
13	19	,	,	,	O
13	20	J.	NNP	J.	PERSON
13	21	B.	NNP	B.	PERSON
13	22	Brady	NNP	Brady	PERSON
13	23	of	IN	of	O
13	24	Harlingen	NNP	Harlingen	LOCATION
13	25	and	CC	and	O
13	26	Howard	NNP	Howard	ORGANIZATION
13	27	Cox	NNP	Cox	ORGANIZATION
13	28	of	IN	of	ORGANIZATION
13	29	Austin	NNP	Austin	ORGANIZATION
13	30	.	.	.	O

14	18	homeLocation
20	24	homeLocation

14	0	Operating	NN	Operating	O
14	1	budget	NN	budget	O
14	2	for	IN	for	O
14	3	the	DT	the	O
14	4	day	NN	day	O
14	5	schools	NNS	school	O
14	6	in	IN	in	O
14	7	the	DT	the	O
14	8	five	CD	five	O
14	9	counties	NNS	county	O
14	10	of	IN	of	O
14	11	Dallas	NNP	Dallas	LOCATION
14	12	,	,	,	O
14	13	Harris	NNP	Harris	PERSON
14	14	,	,	,	O
14	15	Bexar	NNP	Bexar	LOCATION
14	16	,	,	,	O
14	17	Tarrant	NNP	Tarrant	LOCATION
14	18	and	CC	and	O
14	19	El	NNP	El	LOCATION
14	20	Paso	NNP	Paso	LOCATION
14	21	would	MD	would	O
14	22	be	VB	be	O
14	23	$451,500	CD	$451,500	O
14	24	,	,	,	O
14	25	which	WDT	which	O
14	26	would	MD	would	O
14	27	be	VB	be	O
14	28	a	DT	a	O
14	29	savings	NNS	saving	O
14	30	of	IN	of	O
14	31	$157,460	NNP	$157,460	O
14	32	yearly	RB	yearly	O
14	33	after	IN	after	O
14	34	the	DT	the	O
14	35	first	JJ	first	O
14	36	year's	JJ	year's	O
14	37	capital	NN	capital	O
14	38	outlay	NN	outlay	O
14	39	of	IN	of	O
14	40	$88,000	NN	$88,000	O
14	41	was	VBD	be	O
14	42	absorbed	VBN	absorb	O
14	43	,	,	,	O
14	44	Parkhouse	NNP	Parkhouse	PERSON
14	45	told	VBD	tell	O
14	46	the	DT	the	O
14	47	Senate	NNP	Senate	ORGANIZATION
14	48	.	.	.	O


15	0	Dallas	NNP	Dallas	LOCATION
15	1	may	MD	may	O
15	2	get	VB	get	O
15	3	to	TO	to	O
15	4	hear	VB	hear	O
15	5	a	DT	a	O
15	6	debate	NN	debate	O
15	7	on	IN	on	O
15	8	horse	NN	horse	O
15	9	race	NN	race	O
15	10	parimutuels	NNS	parimutuel	O
15	11	soon	RB	soon	O
15	12	between	IN	between	O
15	13	Reps.	NNP	Reps.	O
15	14	V.	NNP	V.	PERSON
15	15	E.	NNP	E.	PERSON
15	16	(	(	(	PERSON
15	17	Red	NNP	Red	PERSON
15	18	)	)	)	PERSON
15	19	Berry	NNP	Berry	PERSON
15	20	and	CC	and	O
15	21	Joe	NNP	Joe	PERSON
15	22	Ratcliff	NNP	Ratcliff	PERSON
15	23	.	.	.	O


16	0	All	DT	All	O
16	1	Dallas	NNP	Dallas	LOCATION
16	2	members	NNS	member	O
16	3	voted	VBD	vote	O
16	4	with	IN	with	O
16	5	Roberts	NNP	Roberts	PERSON
16	6	,	,	,	O
16	7	except	IN	except	O
16	8	Rep.	NNP	Rep.	O
16	9	Bill	NNP	Bill	PERSON
16	10	Jones	NNP	Jones	PERSON
16	11	,	,	,	O
16	12	who	WP	who	O
16	13	was	VBD	be	O
16	14	absent	NN	absent	O
16	15	.	.	.	O


17	0	Rep.	NNP	Rep.	O
17	1	James	NNP	James	PERSON
17	2	Cotten	NNP	Cotten	PERSON
17	3	of	IN	of	O
17	4	Weatherford	NNP	Weatherford	PERSON
17	5	insisted	VBD	insist	O
17	6	that	IN	that	O
17	7	a	DT	a	O
17	8	water	NN	water	O
17	9	development	NN	development	O
17	10	bill	NN	bill	O
17	11	passed	VBN	pass	O
17	12	by	IN	by	O
17	13	the	DT	the	O
17	14	Texas	NNP	Texas	ORGANIZATION
17	15	House	NNP	House	ORGANIZATION
17	16	of	IN	of	ORGANIZATION
17	17	Representatives	NNP	Representatives	ORGANIZATION
17	18	was	VBD	be	O
17	19	an	DT	an	O
17	20	effort	NN	effort	O
17	21	by	IN	by	O
17	22	big	JJ	big	O
17	23	cities	NNS	city	O
17	24	like	IN	like	O
17	25	Dallas	NNP	Dallas	LOCATION
17	26	and	CC	and	O
17	27	Fort	NNP	Fort	LOCATION
17	28	Worth	NNP	Worth	LOCATION
17	29	to	TO	to	O
17	30	cover	VB	cover	O
17	31	up	RP	up	O
17	32	places	NNS	place	O
17	33	like	IN	like	O
17	34	Paradise	NNP	Paradise	O
17	35	,	,	,	O
17	36	a	DT	a	O
17	37	Wise	NNP	Wise	LOCATION
17	38	County	NNP	County	LOCATION
17	39	hamlet	NN	hamlet	O
17	40	of	IN	of	O
17	41	250	CD	250	O
17	42	people	NNS	people	O
17	43	.	.	.	O


18	0	Most	JJS	Most	O
18	1	of	IN	of	O
18	2	the	DT	the	O
18	3	fire	NN	fire	O
18	4	was	VBD	be	O
18	5	directed	VBN	direct	O
18	6	by	IN	by	O
18	7	Cotten	NNP	Cotten	PERSON
18	8	against	IN	against	O
18	9	Dallas	NNP	Dallas	LOCATION
18	10	and	CC	and	O
18	11	Sen.	NNP	Sen.	O
18	12	Parkhouse	NNP	Parkhouse	PERSON
18	13	.	.	.	O

12	9	homeLocation

19	0	Cotten	NNP	Cotten	PERSON
19	1	construed	VBD	construe	O
19	2	this	DT	this	O
19	3	as	IN	a	O
19	4	a	DT	a	O
19	5	veiled	JJ	veiled	O
19	6	effort	NN	effort	O
19	7	by	IN	by	O
19	8	Parkhouse	NNP	Parkhouse	PERSON
19	9	to	TO	to	O
19	10	help	VB	help	O
19	11	Dallas	NNP	Dallas	LOCATION
19	12	and	CC	and	O
19	13	other	JJ	other	O
19	14	large	JJ	large	O
19	15	cities	NNS	city	O
19	16	get	VBP	get	O
19	17	money	NN	money	O
19	18	which	WDT	which	O
19	19	Cotten	NNP	Cotten	PERSON
19	20	felt	VBD	felt	O
19	21	could	MD	could	O
19	22	better	RB	well	O
19	23	be	VB	be	O
19	24	spent	VBN	spend	O
19	25	providing	JJ	providing	O
19	26	water	NN	water	O
19	27	for	IN	for	O
19	28	rural	JJ	rural	O
19	29	Texas	NNP	Texas	LOCATION
19	30	.	.	.	O


20	0	The	DT	The	O
20	1	bill's	NN	bill's	O
20	2	defenders	NNS	defender	O
20	3	were	VBD	be	O
20	4	mostly	RB	mostly	O
20	5	small-town	JJ	small-town	O
20	6	legislators	NNS	legislator	O
20	7	like	IN	like	O
20	8	J.	NNP	J.	PERSON
20	9	W.	NNP	W.	PERSON
20	10	Buchanan	NNP	Buchanan	PERSON
20	11	of	IN	of	O
20	12	Dumas	NNP	Dumas	LOCATION
20	13	,	,	,	O
20	14	Eligio	NNP	Eligio	ORGANIZATION
20	15	(	(	(	ORGANIZATION
20	16	Kika	NNP	Kika	ORGANIZATION
20	17	)	)	)	O
20	18	De	NNP	De	PERSON
20	19	La	NNP	La	PERSON
20	20	Garza	NNP	Garza	PERSON
20	21	of	IN	of	O
20	22	Mission	NNP	Mission	O
20	23	,	,	,	O
20	24	Sam	NNP	Sam	PERSON
20	25	F.	NNP	F.	PERSON
20	26	Collins	NNP	Collins	PERSON
20	27	of	IN	of	O
20	28	Newton	NNP	Newton	LOCATION
20	29	and	CC	and	O
20	30	Joe	NNP	Joe	PERSON
20	31	Chapman	NNP	Chapman	PERSON
20	32	of	IN	of	O
20	33	Sulphur	NNP	Sulphur	LOCATION
20	34	Springs	NNP	Springs	LOCATION
20	35	.	.	.	O

8	12	homeLocation
24	28	homeLocation
30	33	homeLocation

21	0	--	:	--	O
21	1	The	DT	The	O
21	2	board	NN	board	O
21	3	of	IN	of	O
21	4	regents	NNS	regent	O
21	5	of	IN	of	O
21	6	Paris	NNP	Paris	ORGANIZATION
21	7	Junior	NNP	Junior	ORGANIZATION
21	8	College	NNP	College	ORGANIZATION
21	9	has	VBZ	have	O
21	10	named	VBN	name	O
21	11	Dr.	NNP	Dr.	O
21	12	Clarence	NNP	Clarence	PERSON
21	13	Charles	NNP	Charles	PERSON
21	14	Clark	NNP	Clark	PERSON
21	15	of	IN	of	O
21	16	Hays	NNP	Hays	LOCATION
21	17	,	,	,	O
21	18	Kan.	NNP	Kan.	LOCATION
21	19	as	IN	a	O
21	20	the	DT	the	O
21	21	school's	JJ	school's	O
21	22	new	JJ	new	O
21	23	president	NN	president	O
21	24	.	.	.	O

6	12	employee
12	16	homeLocation
18	16	containsPlace

22	0	Dr.	NNP	Dr.	O
22	1	Clark	NNP	Clark	PERSON
22	2	will	MD	will	O
22	3	succeed	VB	succeed	O
22	4	Dr.	NNP	Dr.	O
22	5	J.	NNP	J.	PERSON
22	6	R.	NNP	R.	PERSON
22	7	McLemore	NNP	McLemore	PERSON
22	8	,	,	,	O
22	9	who	WP	who	O
22	10	will	MD	will	O
22	11	retire	VB	retire	O
22	12	at	IN	at	O
22	13	the	DT	the	O
22	14	close	NN	close	O
22	15	of	IN	of	O
22	16	the	DT	the	O
22	17	present	JJ	present	O
22	18	school	NN	school	O
22	19	term	NN	term	O
22	20	.	.	.	O


23	0	Bellows	NNS	Bellows	PERSON
23	1	made	VBD	make	O
23	2	the	DT	the	O
23	3	disclosure	NN	disclosure	O
23	4	when	WRB	when	O
23	5	he	PRP	he	O
23	6	asked	VBD	ask	O
23	7	Judge	NNP	Judge	O
23	8	Parsons	NNP	Parsons	PERSON
23	9	to	TO	to	O
23	10	grant	VB	grant	O
23	11	his	PRP$	his	O
23	12	client	NN	client	O
23	13	,	,	,	O
23	14	Alan	NNP	Alan	PERSON
23	15	Clements	NNP	Clements	PERSON
23	16	,	,	,	O
23	17	30	CD	30	O
23	18	,	,	,	O
23	19	a	DT	a	O
23	20	separate	JJ	separate	O
23	21	trial	NN	trial	O
23	22	.	.	.	O


24	0	Salinger	NNP	Salinger	PERSON
24	1	said	VBD	say	O
24	2	the	DT	the	O
24	3	work	NN	work	O
24	4	President	NNP	President	O
24	5	Kennedy	NNP	Kennedy	PERSON
24	6	,	,	,	O
24	7	advisers	NNS	adviser	O
24	8	,	,	,	O
24	9	and	CC	and	O
24	10	members	NNS	member	O
24	11	of	IN	of	O
24	12	his	PRP$	his	O
24	13	staff	NN	staff	O
24	14	were	VBD	be	O
24	15	doing	VBG	do	O
24	16	on	IN	on	O
24	17	the	DT	the	O
24	18	address	NN	address	O
24	19	involved	VBN	involve	O
24	20	composition	NN	composition	O
24	21	and	CC	and	O
24	22	wording	NN	wording	O
24	23	,	,	,	O
24	24	rather	RB	rather	O
24	25	than	IN	than	O
24	26	last	JJ	last	O
24	27	minute	JJ	minute	O
24	28	decisions	NNS	decision	O
24	29	on	IN	on	O
24	30	administration	NN	administration	O
24	31	plans	NNS	plan	O
24	32	to	TO	to	O
24	33	meet	VB	meet	O
24	34	the	DT	the	O
24	35	latest	JJS	late	O
24	36	Berlin	NNP	Berlin	LOCATION
24	37	crisis	NN	crisis	O
24	38	precipitated	VBN	precipitate	O
24	39	by	IN	by	O
24	40	Russia's	NNP	Russia's	O
24	41	demands	NNS	demand	O
24	42	and	CC	and	O
24	43	proposals	NNS	proposal	O
24	44	for	IN	for	O
24	45	the	DT	the	O
24	46	city	NN	city	O
24	47	.	.	.	O


25	0	Karns	NNP	Karns	PERSON
25	1	said	VBD	say	O
25	2	it	PRP	it	O
25	3	was	VBD	be	O
25	4	a	DT	a	O
25	5	``	``	``	O
25	6	wrongful	JJ	wrongful	O
25	7	act	NN	act	O
25	8	''	''	''	O
25	9	for	IN	for	O
25	10	Wexler	NNP	Wexler	PERSON
25	11	to	TO	to	O
25	12	take	VB	take	O
25	13	statements	NNS	statement	O
25	14	``	``	``	O
25	15	privately	RB	privately	O
25	16	and	CC	and	O
25	17	outside	IN	outside	O
25	18	of	IN	of	O
25	19	the	DT	the	O
25	20	grand	JJ	grand	O
25	21	jury	NN	jury	O
25	22	room	NN	room	O
25	23	''	''	''	O
25	24	.	.	.	O


26	0	``	``	``	O
26	1	Actually	RB	Actually	O
26	2	,	,	,	O
26	3	the	DT	the	O
26	4	abuse	NN	abuse	O
26	5	of	IN	of	O
26	6	the	DT	the	O
26	7	process	NN	process	O
26	8	may	MD	may	O
26	9	have	VB	have	O
26	10	constituted	VBN	constitute	O
26	11	a	DT	a	O
26	12	contempt	NN	contempt	O
26	13	of	IN	of	O
26	14	the	DT	the	O
26	15	Criminal	NNP	Criminal	O
26	16	court	NN	court	O
26	17	of	IN	of	O
26	18	Cook	NNP	Cook	PERSON
26	19	county	NN	county	O
26	20	,	,	,	O
26	21	altho	JJ	altho	O
26	22	vindication	NN	vindication	O
26	23	of	IN	of	O
26	24	the	DT	the	O
26	25	authority	NN	authority	O
26	26	of	IN	of	O
26	27	that	DT	that	O
26	28	court	NN	court	O
26	29	is	VBZ	be	O
26	30	not	RB	not	O
26	31	the	DT	the	O
26	32	function	NN	function	O
26	33	of	IN	of	O
26	34	this	DT	this	O
26	35	court	NN	court	O
26	36	''	''	''	O
26	37	,	,	,	O
26	38	said	VBD	say	O
26	39	Karns	NNP	Karns	PERSON
26	40	,	,	,	O
26	41	who	WP	who	O
26	42	is	VBZ	be	O
26	43	a	DT	a	O
26	44	City	NNP	City	O
26	45	judge	NN	judge	O
26	46	in	IN	in	O
26	47	East	NNP	East	LOCATION
26	48	St.	NNP	St.	LOCATION
26	49	Louis	NNP	Louis	LOCATION
26	50	sitting	VBG	sit	O
26	51	in	IN	in	O
26	52	Cook	NNP	Cook	LOCATION
26	53	County	NNP	County	LOCATION
26	54	court	NN	court	O
26	55	.	.	.	O

39	47	homeLocation
52	47	containsPlace

27	0	After	IN	After	O
27	1	reading	VBG	read	O
27	2	his	PRP$	his	O
27	3	statement	NN	statement	O
27	4	discharging	VBG	discharge	O
27	5	the	DT	the	O
27	6	23d	CD	23d	O
27	7	ward	NN	ward	O
27	8	case	NN	case	O
27	9	,	,	,	O
27	10	Karns	NNP	Karns	PERSON
27	11	told	VBD	tell	O
27	12	Wexler	NNP	Wexler	PERSON
27	13	that	IN	that	O
27	14	if	IN	if	O
27	15	the	DT	the	O
27	16	seven	CD	seven	O
27	17	cases	NNS	case	O
27	18	scheduled	VBN	schedule	O
27	19	for	IN	for	O
27	20	trial	NN	trial	O
27	21	also	RB	also	O
27	22	involved	JJ	involved	O
27	23	persons	NNS	person	O
27	24	who	WP	who	O
27	25	had	VBD	have	O
27	26	been	VBN	be	O
27	27	subpenaed	RB	subpenaed	O
27	28	,	,	,	O
27	29	he	PRP	he	O
27	30	would	MD	would	O
27	31	dismiss	VB	dismiss	O
27	32	them	PRP	them	O
27	33	.	.	.	O


28	0	Senate	NNP	Senate	ORGANIZATION
28	1	Republican	NNP	Republican	O
28	2	Leader	NNP	Leader	O
28	3	Dirksen	NNP	Dirksen	O
28	4	(	(	(	O
28	5	Ill.	NNP	Ill.	O
28	6	)	)	)	O
28	7	and	CC	and	O
28	8	House	NNP	House	ORGANIZATION
28	9	Republican	NNP	Republican	O
28	10	Leader	NNP	Leader	O
28	11	Charles	NNP	Charles	PERSON
28	12	Halleck	NNP	Halleck	PERSON
28	13	(	(	(	O
28	14	Ind.	NNP	Ind.	O
28	15	)	)	)	O
28	16	said	VBD	say	O
28	17	the	DT	the	O
28	18	message	NN	message	O
28	19	did	VBD	do	O
28	20	not	RB	not	O
28	21	persuade	VB	persuade	O
28	22	them	PRP	them	O
28	23	to	TO	to	O
28	24	change	VB	change	O
28	25	their	PRP$	their	O
28	26	opposition	NN	opposition	O
28	27	to	TO	to	O
28	28	compulsory	VB	compulsory	O
28	29	medical	JJ	medical	O
28	30	insurance	NN	insurance	O
28	31	.	.	.	O

8	11	employee

29	0	House	NNP	House	ORGANIZATION
29	1	Speaker	NNP	Speaker	O
29	2	Sam	NNP	Sam	PERSON
29	3	Rayburn	NNP	Rayburn	PERSON
29	4	(	(	(	O
29	5	D.	NNP	D.	O
29	6	,	,	,	O
29	7	Tex.	NNP	Tex.	LOCATION
29	8	)	)	)	O
29	9	called	VBD	call	O
29	10	the	DT	the	O
29	11	Kennedy	NNP	Kennedy	PERSON
29	12	program	NN	program	O
29	13	``	``	``	O
29	14	a	DT	a	O
29	15	mighty	JJ	mighty	O
29	16	fine	JJ	fine	O
29	17	thing	NN	thing	O
29	18	''	''	''	O
29	19	,	,	,	O
29	20	but	CC	but	O
29	21	made	VBD	make	O
29	22	no	DT	no	O
29	23	prediction	NN	prediction	O
29	24	on	IN	on	O
29	25	its	PRP$	it	O
29	26	fate	NN	fate	O
29	27	in	IN	in	O
29	28	the	DT	the	O
29	29	House	NNP	House	ORGANIZATION
29	30	.	.	.	O

0	2	employee
2	7	homeLocation

30	0	The	DT	The	O
30	1	Republicans	NNPS	Republicans	O
30	2	some	DT	some	O
30	3	weeks	NNS	week	O
30	4	ago	RB	ago	O
30	5	served	VBD	serve	O
30	6	notice	RB	notice	O
30	7	through	IN	through	O
30	8	Senator	NNP	Senator	O
30	9	Thruston	NNP	Thruston	PERSON
30	10	B.	NNP	B.	PERSON
30	11	Morton	NNP	Morton	PERSON
30	12	(	(	(	O
30	13	R	NNP	R	O
30	14	)	)	)	O
30	15	of	IN	of	O
30	16	Kentucky	NNP	Kentucky	LOCATION
30	17	,	,	,	O
30	18	chairman	NN	chairman	O
30	19	of	IN	of	O
30	20	the	DT	the	O
30	21	Republican	NNP	Republican	ORGANIZATION
30	22	National	NNP	National	ORGANIZATION
30	23	Committee	NNP	Committee	ORGANIZATION
30	24	,	,	,	O
30	25	that	IN	that	O
30	26	the	DT	the	O
30	27	Kennedy	NNP	Kennedy	PERSON
30	28	administration	NN	administration	O
30	29	would	MD	would	O
30	30	be	VB	be	O
30	31	held	VBN	hold	O
30	32	responsible	JJ	responsible	O
30	33	if	IN	if	O
30	34	the	DT	the	O
30	35	outcome	NN	outcome	O
30	36	in	IN	in	O
30	37	Laos	NNP	Laos	LOCATION
30	38	was	VBD	be	O
30	39	a	DT	a	O
30	40	coalition	JJ	coalition	O
30	41	government	NN	government	O
30	42	susceptible	NN	susceptible	O
30	43	of	IN	of	O
30	44	Communist	JJ	Communist	O
30	45	domination	NN	domination	O
30	46	.	.	.	O

9	16	homeLocation
21	9	employee

31	0	Until	IN	Until	O
31	1	the	DT	the	O
31	2	Cuban	NNP	Cuban	O
31	3	fiasco	NN	fiasco	O
31	4	and	CC	and	O
31	5	the	DT	the	O
31	6	Communist	NNP	Communist	O
31	7	military	JJ	military	O
31	8	victories	NNS	victory	O
31	9	in	IN	in	O
31	10	Laos	NNP	Laos	LOCATION
31	11	,	,	,	O
31	12	almost	RB	almost	O
31	13	any	DT	any	O
31	14	observer	NN	observer	O
31	15	would	MD	would	O
31	16	have	VB	have	O
31	17	said	VBD	say	O
31	18	that	IN	that	O
31	19	President	NNP	President	O
31	20	Kennedy	NNP	Kennedy	PERSON
31	21	had	VBD	have	O
31	22	blended	VBN	blend	O
31	23	a	DT	a	O
31	24	program	NN	program	O
31	25	that	WDT	that	O
31	26	respected	VBD	respect	O
31	27	,	,	,	O
31	28	generally	RB	generally	O
31	29	,	,	,	O
31	30	the	DT	the	O
31	31	opinions	NNS	opinion	O
31	32	voiced	VBD	voice	O
31	33	both	DT	both	O
31	34	by	IN	by	O
31	35	Mr.	NNP	Mr.	O
31	36	Nixon	NNP	Nixon	PERSON
31	37	and	CC	and	O
31	38	the	DT	the	O
31	39	professors	NNS	professor	O
31	40	.	.	.	O


32	0	Noting	VBG	Noting	O
32	1	that	IN	that	O
32	2	President	NNP	President	O
32	3	Kennedy	NNP	Kennedy	PERSON
32	4	has	VBZ	have	O
32	5	handed	VBN	hand	O
32	6	the	DT	the	O
32	7	Defense	NNP	Defense	ORGANIZATION
32	8	Department	NNP	Department	ORGANIZATION
32	9	the	DT	the	O
32	10	major	JJ	major	O
32	11	responsibility	NN	responsibility	O
32	12	for	IN	for	O
32	13	the	DT	the	O
32	14	nation's	JJ	nation's	O
32	15	civil	JJ	civil	O
32	16	defense	NN	defense	O
32	17	program	NN	program	O
32	18	,	,	,	O
32	19	Mr.	NNP	Mr.	O
32	20	Hawksley	NNP	Hawksley	PERSON
32	21	said	VBD	say	O
32	22	the	DT	the	O
32	23	federal	JJ	federal	O
32	24	government	NN	government	O
32	25	would	MD	would	O
32	26	pay	VB	pay	O
32	27	half	PDT	half	O
32	28	the	DT	the	O
32	29	salary	NN	salary	O
32	30	of	IN	of	O
32	31	a	DT	a	O
32	32	full-time	JJ	full-time	O
32	33	local	JJ	local	O
32	34	director	NN	director	O
32	35	.	.	.	O


33	0	Mr.	NNP	Mr.	O
33	1	Notte	NNP	Notte	PERSON
33	2	was	VBD	be	O
33	3	responding	VBG	respond	O
33	4	to	TO	to	O
33	5	a	DT	a	O
33	6	resolution	NN	resolution	O
33	7	adopted	VBN	adopt	O
33	8	by	IN	by	O
33	9	the	DT	the	O
33	10	Central	NNP	Central	ORGANIZATION
33	11	Falls	NNP	Falls	ORGANIZATION
33	12	City	NNP	City	ORGANIZATION
33	13	Council	NNP	Council	ORGANIZATION
33	14	on	IN	on	O
33	15	July	NNP	July	O
33	16	10	CD	10	O
33	17	and	CC	and	O
33	18	sent	VBD	send	O
33	19	to	TO	to	O
33	20	the	DT	the	O
33	21	state	NN	state	O
33	22	house	NN	house	O
33	23	by	IN	by	O
33	24	Miss	NNP	Miss	O
33	25	Grant	NNP	Grant	PERSON
33	26	.	.	.	O


34	0	While	IN	While	O
34	1	the	DT	the	O
34	2	city	NN	city	O
34	3	council	NN	council	O
34	4	suggested	VBD	suggest	O
34	5	that	IN	that	O
34	6	the	DT	the	O
34	7	Legislative	NNP	Legislative	ORGANIZATION
34	8	Council	NNP	Council	ORGANIZATION
34	9	might	MD	might	O
34	10	perform	VB	perform	O
34	11	the	DT	the	O
34	12	review	NN	review	O
34	13	,	,	,	O
34	14	Mr.	NNP	Mr.	O
34	15	Notte	NNP	Notte	PERSON
34	16	said	VBD	say	O
34	17	that	IN	that	O
34	18	instead	RB	instead	O
34	19	he	PRP	he	O
34	20	will	MD	will	O
34	21	take	VB	take	O
34	22	up	RP	up	O
34	23	the	DT	the	O
34	24	matter	NN	matter	O
34	25	with	IN	with	O
34	26	Atty.	NNP	Atty.	O
34	27	Gen.	NNP	Gen.	O
34	28	J.	NNP	J.	PERSON
34	29	Joseph	NNP	Joseph	PERSON
34	30	Nugent	NNP	Nugent	PERSON
34	31	to	TO	to	O
34	32	get	VB	get	O
34	33	``	``	``	O
34	34	the	DT	the	O
34	35	benefit	NN	benefit	O
34	36	of	IN	of	O
34	37	his	PRP$	his	O
34	38	views	NNS	view	O
34	39	''	''	''	O
34	40	.	.	.	O


35	0	William	NNP	William	PERSON
35	1	A.	NNP	A.	PERSON
35	2	Martinelli	NNP	Martinelli	PERSON
35	3	,	,	,	O
35	4	chairman	NN	chairman	O
35	5	of	IN	of	O
35	6	the	DT	the	O
35	7	Citizens	NNP	Citizens	ORGANIZATION
35	8	Group	NNP	Group	ORGANIZATION
35	9	of	IN	of	ORGANIZATION
35	10	Johnston	NNP	Johnston	ORGANIZATION
35	11	,	,	,	O
35	12	transferred	VBD	transfer	O
35	13	the	DT	the	O
35	14	petitions	NNS	petition	O
35	15	from	IN	from	O
35	16	his	PRP$	his	O
35	17	left	JJ	left	O
35	18	hand	NN	hand	O
35	19	to	TO	to	O
35	20	his	PRP$	his	O
35	21	right	JJ	right	O
35	22	hand	NN	hand	O
35	23	after	IN	after	O
35	24	the	DT	the	O
35	25	council	NN	council	O
35	26	voted	VBD	vote	O
35	27	to	TO	to	O
35	28	accept	VB	accept	O
35	29	them	PRP	them	O
35	30	at	IN	at	O
35	31	the	DT	the	O
35	32	suggestion	NN	suggestion	O
35	33	of	IN	of	O
35	34	Council	NNP	Council	O
35	35	President	NNP	President	O
35	36	Raymond	NNP	Raymond	PERSON
35	37	Fortin	NNP	Fortin	PERSON
35	38	Sr.	NNP	Sr.	O
35	39	.	.	.	O

7	0	employee

36	0	A	DT	A	O
36	1	difference	NN	difference	O
36	2	of	IN	of	O
36	3	opinion	NN	opinion	O
36	4	arose	NN	arose	O
36	5	between	IN	between	O
36	6	Mr.	NNP	Mr.	O
36	7	Martinelli	NNP	Martinelli	PERSON
36	8	and	CC	and	O
36	9	John	NNP	John	PERSON
36	10	P.	NNP	P.	PERSON
36	11	Bourcier	NNP	Bourcier	PERSON
36	12	,	,	,	O
36	13	town	NN	town	O
36	14	solicitor	NN	solicitor	O
36	15	,	,	,	O
36	16	over	IN	over	O
36	17	the	DT	the	O
36	18	exact	JJ	exact	O
36	19	manner	NN	manner	O
36	20	in	IN	in	O
36	21	which	WDT	which	O
36	22	the	DT	the	O
36	23	vote	NN	vote	O
36	24	is	VBZ	be	O
36	25	handled	VBN	handle	O
36	26	.	.	.	O


37	0	Mr.	NNP	Mr.	O
37	1	Martinelli	NNP	Martinelli	PERSON
37	2	has	VBZ	have	O
37	3	,	,	,	O
37	4	in	IN	in	O
37	5	recent	JJ	recent	O
37	6	weeks	NNS	week	O
37	7	,	,	,	O
37	8	been	VBN	be	O
37	9	of	IN	of	O
37	10	the	DT	the	O
37	11	opinion	NN	opinion	O
37	12	that	IN	that	O
37	13	a	DT	a	O
37	14	special	JJ	special	O
37	15	town	NN	town	O
37	16	meeting	NN	meeting	O
37	17	would	MD	would	O
37	18	be	VB	be	O
37	19	called	VBN	call	O
37	20	for	IN	for	O
37	21	the	DT	the	O
37	22	vote	NN	vote	O
37	23	,	,	,	O
37	24	while	IN	while	O
37	25	Mr.	NNP	Mr.	O
37	26	Bourcier	NNP	Bourcier	PERSON
37	27	said	VBD	say	O
37	28	that	IN	that	O
37	29	a	DT	a	O
37	30	special	JJ	special	O
37	31	election	NN	election	O
37	32	might	MD	might	O
37	33	be	VB	be	O
37	34	called	VBN	call	O
37	35	instead	RB	instead	O
37	36	.	.	.	O


38	0	Mr.	NNP	Mr.	O
38	1	Martinelli	NNP	Martinelli	PERSON
38	2	said	VBD	say	O
38	3	yesterday	NN	yesterday	O
38	4	that	IN	that	O
38	5	the	DT	the	O
38	6	Citizens	NNP	Citizens	ORGANIZATION
38	7	Group	NNP	Group	ORGANIZATION
38	8	of	IN	of	O
38	9	Johnston	NNP	Johnston	LOCATION
38	10	will	MD	will	O
38	11	meet	VB	meet	O
38	12	again	RB	again	O
38	13	July	NNP	July	O
38	14	24	CD	24	O
38	15	to	TO	to	O
38	16	plan	VB	plan	O
38	17	further	JJ	further	O
38	18	strategy	NN	strategy	O
38	19	in	IN	in	O
38	20	the	DT	the	O
38	21	charter	NN	charter	O
38	22	movement	NN	movement	O
38	23	.	.	.	O

6	9	location

39	0	Council	NNP	Council	ORGANIZATION
39	1	president	NN	president	O
39	2	Frank	NNP	Frank	PERSON
39	3	SanAntonio	NNP	SanAntonio	PERSON
39	4	said	VBD	say	O
39	5	yesterday	NN	yesterday	O
39	6	he	PRP	he	O
39	7	may	MD	may	O
39	8	ask	VB	ask	O
39	9	the	DT	the	O
39	10	council	NN	council	O
39	11	to	TO	to	O
39	12	formally	RB	formally	O
39	13	request	VB	request	O
39	14	Town	NNP	Town	O
39	15	Solicitor	NNP	Solicitor	O
39	16	Michael	NNP	Michael	PERSON
39	17	A.	NNP	A.	PERSON
39	18	Abatuno	NNP	Abatuno	PERSON
39	19	to	TO	to	O
39	20	draft	VB	draft	O
39	21	the	DT	the	O
39	22	ordinance	NN	ordinance	O
39	23	.	.	.	O

0	2	employee

40	0	--	:	--	O
40	1	James	NNP	James	PERSON
40	2	P.	NNP	P.	PERSON
40	3	Mitchell	NNP	Mitchell	PERSON
40	4	and	CC	and	O
40	5	Sen.	NNP	Sen.	O
40	6	Walter	NNP	Walter	PERSON
40	7	H.	NNP	H.	PERSON
40	8	Jones	NNP	Jones	PERSON
40	9	R-Bergen	NNP	R-Bergen	PERSON
40	10	,	,	,	O
40	11	last	JJ	last	O
40	12	night	NN	night	O
40	13	disagreed	VBD	disagree	O
40	14	on	IN	on	O
40	15	the	DT	the	O
40	16	value	NN	value	O
40	17	of	IN	of	O
40	18	using	VBG	use	O
40	19	as	IN	a	O
40	20	a	DT	a	O
40	21	campaign	NN	campaign	O
40	22	issue	NN	issue	O
40	23	a	DT	a	O
40	24	remark	NN	remark	O
40	25	by	IN	by	O
40	26	Richard	NNP	Richard	PERSON
40	27	J.	NNP	J.	PERSON
40	28	Hughes	NNP	Hughes	PERSON
40	29	,	,	,	O
40	30	Democratic	JJ	Democratic	O
40	31	gubernatorial	JJ	gubernatorial	O
40	32	candidate	NN	candidate	O
40	33	,	,	,	O
40	34	that	IN	that	O
40	35	the	DT	the	O
40	36	GOP	NNP	GOP	ORGANIZATION
40	37	is	VBZ	be	O
40	38	``	``	``	O
40	39	Campaigning	VBG	Campaigning	O
40	40	on	IN	on	O
40	41	the	DT	the	O
40	42	carcass	NN	carcass	O
40	43	of	IN	of	O
40	44	Eisenhower	NNP	Eisenhower	O
40	45	Republicanism	NNP	Republicanism	O
40	46	''	''	''	O
40	47	.	.	.	O

1	6	colleague

41	0	Mitchell	NNP	Mitchell	PERSON
41	1	was	VBD	be	O
41	2	for	IN	for	O
41	3	using	VBG	use	O
41	4	it	PRP	it	O
41	5	,	,	,	O
41	6	Jones	NNP	Jones	PERSON
41	7	against	IN	against	O
41	8	,	,	,	O
41	9	and	CC	and	O
41	10	Sen.	NNP	Sen.	O
41	11	Wayne	NNP	Wayne	PERSON
41	12	Dumont	NNP	Dumont	PERSON
41	13	Jr.	NNP	Jr.	PERSON
41	14	R-Warren	NNP	R-Warren	PERSON
41	15	did	VBD	do	O
41	16	not	RB	not	O
41	17	mention	VB	mention	O
41	18	it	PRP	it	O
41	19	when	WRB	when	O
41	20	the	DT	the	O
41	21	three	CD	three	O
41	22	Republican	NNP	Republican	O
41	23	gubernatorial	JJ	gubernatorial	O
41	24	candidates	NNS	candidate	O
41	25	spoke	VBD	speak	O
41	26	at	IN	at	O
41	27	staggered	JJ	staggered	O
41	28	intervals	NNS	interval	O
41	29	before	IN	before	O
41	30	100	CD	100	O
41	31	persons	NNS	person	O
41	32	at	IN	at	O
41	33	the	DT	the	O
41	34	Park	NNP	Park	O
41	35	Hotel	NNP	Hotel	O
41	36	.	.	.	O


42	0	Hughes	NNP	Hughes	PERSON
42	1	said	VBD	say	O
42	2	Monday	NNP	Monday	O
42	3	,	,	,	O
42	4	``	``	``	O
42	5	It	PRP	It	O
42	6	is	VBZ	be	O
42	7	the	DT	the	O
42	8	apparent	JJ	apparent	O
42	9	intention	NN	intention	O
42	10	of	IN	of	O
42	11	the	DT	the	O
42	12	Republican	NNP	Republican	ORGANIZATION
42	13	Party	NNP	Party	ORGANIZATION
42	14	to	TO	to	O
42	15	campaign	NN	campaign	O
42	16	on	IN	on	O
42	17	the	DT	the	O
42	18	carcass	NN	carcass	O
42	19	of	IN	of	O
42	20	what	WP	what	O
42	21	they	PRP	they	O
42	22	call	VBP	call	O
42	23	Eisenhower	NNP	Eisenhower	O
42	24	Republicanism	NNP	Republicanism	O
42	25	,	,	,	O
42	26	but	CC	but	O
42	27	the	DT	the	O
42	28	heart	NN	heart	O
42	29	stopped	VBD	stop	O
42	30	beating	VBG	beat	O
42	31	and	CC	and	O
42	32	the	DT	the	O
42	33	lifeblood	NN	lifeblood	O
42	34	congealed	VBD	congeal	O
42	35	after	IN	after	O
42	36	Eisenhower	NNP	Eisenhower	PERSON
42	37	retired	VBD	retire	O
42	38	.	.	.	O


43	0	Mitchell	NNP	Mitchell	PERSON
43	1	said	VBD	say	O
43	2	the	DT	the	O
43	3	closeness	NN	closeness	O
43	4	of	IN	of	O
43	5	the	DT	the	O
43	6	outcome	NN	outcome	O
43	7	in	IN	in	O
43	8	last	JJ	last	O
43	9	fall's	JJ	fall's	O
43	10	Presidential	NNP	Presidential	O
43	11	election	NN	election	O
43	12	did	VBD	do	O
43	13	not	RB	not	O
43	14	mean	VB	mean	O
43	15	that	IN	that	O
43	16	Eisenhower	NNP	Eisenhower	PERSON
43	17	Republicanism	NNP	Republicanism	PERSON
43	18	was	VBD	be	O
43	19	a	DT	a	O
43	20	dead	JJ	dead	O
43	21	issue	NN	issue	O
43	22	.	.	.	O


44	0	Jones	NNP	Jones	PERSON
44	1	said	VBD	say	O
44	2	he	PRP	he	O
44	3	regretted	VBD	regret	O
44	4	Hughes	NNP	Hughes	PERSON
44	5	had	VBD	have	O
44	6	made	VBN	make	O
44	7	a	DT	a	O
44	8	personal	JJ	personal	O
44	9	attack	NN	attack	O
44	10	on	IN	on	O
44	11	a	DT	a	O
44	12	past	JJ	past	O
44	13	president	NN	president	O
44	14	.	.	.	O


45	0	Mitchell	NNP	Mitchell	PERSON
45	1	decried	VBD	decry	O
45	2	the	DT	the	O
45	3	high	JJ	high	O
45	4	rate	NN	rate	O
45	5	of	IN	of	O
45	6	unemployment	NN	unemployment	O
45	7	in	IN	in	O
45	8	the	DT	the	O
45	9	state	NN	state	O
45	10	and	CC	and	O
45	11	said	VBD	say	O
45	12	the	DT	the	O
45	13	Meyner	NNP	Meyner	PERSON
45	14	administration	NN	administration	O
45	15	and	CC	and	O
45	16	the	DT	the	O
45	17	Republican-controlled	JJ	Republican-controlled	O
45	18	State	NNP	State	O
45	19	Senate	NNP	Senate	ORGANIZATION
45	20	``	``	``	O
45	21	Must	NNP	Must	O
45	22	share	NN	share	O
45	23	the	DT	the	O
45	24	blame	NN	blame	O
45	25	for	IN	for	O
45	26	this	DT	this	O
45	27	''	''	''	O
45	28	.	.	.	O


46	0	Jones	NNP	Jones	PERSON
46	1	,	,	,	O
46	2	unhappy	JJ	unhappy	O
46	3	that	IN	that	O
46	4	the	DT	the	O
46	5	candidates	NNS	candidate	O
46	6	were	VBD	be	O
46	7	limited	VBN	limit	O
46	8	to	TO	to	O
46	9	eight	CD	eight	O
46	10	minutes	NNS	minute	O
46	11	for	IN	for	O
46	12	a	DT	a	O
46	13	speech	NN	speech	O
46	14	and	CC	and	O
46	15	no	DT	no	O
46	16	audience	NN	audience	O
46	17	questions	NNS	question	O
46	18	,	,	,	O
46	19	saved	VBD	save	O
46	20	his	PRP$	his	O
46	21	barbs	NN	barb	O
46	22	for	IN	for	O
46	23	Mitchell	NNP	Mitchell	PERSON
46	24	.	.	.	O


47	0	``	``	``	O
47	1	I	PRP	I	O
47	2	think	VBP	think	O
47	3	that	IN	that	O
47	4	all	DT	all	O
47	5	Americans	NNPS	Americans	O
47	6	will	MD	will	O
47	7	resent	VB	resent	O
47	8	deeply	RB	deeply	O
47	9	the	DT	the	O
47	10	statements	NNS	statement	O
47	11	made	VBN	make	O
47	12	about	IN	about	O
47	13	President	NNP	President	O
47	14	Eisenhower	NNP	Eisenhower	PERSON
47	15	by	IN	by	O
47	16	Richard	NNP	Richard	PERSON
47	17	J.	NNP	J.	PERSON
47	18	Hughes	NNP	Hughes	PERSON
47	19	.	.	.	O


48	0	Sen.	NNP	Sen.	O
48	1	Charles	NNP	Charles	PERSON
48	2	W.	NNP	W.	PERSON
48	3	Sandman	NNP	Sandman	PERSON
48	4	,	,	,	O
48	5	R-Cape	NNP	R-Cape	O
48	6	May	NNP	May	O
48	7	,	,	,	O
48	8	said	VBD	say	O
48	9	today	NN	today	O
48	10	Jones	NNP	Jones	PERSON
48	11	will	MD	will	O
48	12	run	VB	run	O
48	13	well	RB	well	O
48	14	ahead	RB	ahead	O
48	15	of	IN	of	O
48	16	his	PRP$	his	O
48	17	GOP	NNP	GOP	ORGANIZATION
48	18	opponents	NNS	opponent	O
48	19	for	IN	for	O
48	20	the	DT	the	O
48	21	gubernatorial	JJ	gubernatorial	O
48	22	nomination	NN	nomination	O
48	23	.	.	.	O


49	0	Sandman	NNP	Sandman	PERSON
49	1	,	,	,	O
49	2	state	NN	state	O
49	3	campaign	NN	campaign	O
49	4	chairman	NN	chairman	O
49	5	for	IN	for	O
49	6	Jones	NNP	Jones	PERSON
49	7	,	,	,	O
49	8	was	VBD	be	O
49	9	addressing	VBG	address	O
49	10	a	DT	a	O
49	11	meeting	NN	meeting	O
49	12	in	IN	in	O
49	13	the	DT	the	O
49	14	Military	NNP	Military	LOCATION
49	15	Park	NNP	Park	LOCATION
49	16	Hotel	NNP	Hotel	LOCATION
49	17	,	,	,	O
49	18	Newark	NNP	Newark	LOCATION
49	19	,	,	,	O
49	20	of	IN	of	O
49	21	Essex	NNP	Essex	LOCATION
49	22	County	NNP	County	LOCATION
49	23	leaders	NNS	leader	O
49	24	and	CC	and	O
49	25	campaign	NN	campaign	O
49	26	managers	NNS	manager	O
49	27	for	IN	for	O
49	28	Jones	NNP	Jones	PERSON
49	29	.	.	.	O

0	6	colleague
18	14	containsPlace

50	0	Sandman	NNP	Sandman	PERSON
50	1	told	VBD	tell	O
50	2	the	DT	the	O
50	3	gathering	NN	gathering	O
50	4	that	WDT	that	O
50	5	reports	VBZ	report	O
50	6	from	IN	from	O
50	7	workers	NNS	worker	O
50	8	on	IN	on	O
50	9	a	DT	a	O
50	10	local	JJ	local	O
50	11	level	NN	level	O
50	12	all	DT	all	O
50	13	over	IN	over	O
50	14	the	DT	the	O
50	15	state	NN	state	O
50	16	indicate	NN	indicate	O
50	17	that	IN	that	O
50	18	Jones	NNP	Jones	PERSON
50	19	will	MD	will	O
50	20	be	VB	be	O
50	21	chosen	VBN	choose	O
50	22	the	DT	the	O
50	23	Republican	NNP	Republican	O
50	24	Party's	NNP	Party's	O
50	25	nominee	NN	nominee	O
50	26	with	IN	with	O
50	27	the	DT	the	O
50	28	largest	JJS	large	O
50	29	majority	NN	majority	O
50	30	given	VBN	give	O
50	31	a	DT	a	O
50	32	candidate	NN	candidate	O
50	33	in	IN	in	O
50	34	recent	JJ	recent	O
50	35	years	NNS	year	O
50	36	.	.	.	O


51	0	Sandman	NNP	Sandman	PERSON
51	1	said	VBD	say	O
51	2	:	:	:	O
51	3	``	``	``	O
51	4	The	DT	The	O
51	5	announcement	NN	announcement	O
51	6	that	WDT	that	O
51	7	Sen.	NNP	Sen.	O
51	8	Clifford	NNP	Clifford	PERSON
51	9	Case	NNP	Case	PERSON
51	10	Aj	NNP	Aj	PERSON
51	11	,	,	,	O
51	12	has	VBZ	have	O
51	13	decided	VBN	decide	O
51	14	to	TO	to	O
51	15	spend	VB	spend	O
51	16	all	DT	all	O
51	17	his	PRP$	his	O
51	18	available	JJ	available	O
51	19	time	NN	time	O
51	20	campaigning	VBG	campaign	O
51	21	for	IN	for	O
51	22	Mr.	NNP	Mr.	O
51	23	Mitchell	NNP	Mitchell	PERSON
51	24	is	VBZ	be	O
51	25	a	DT	a	O
51	26	dead	JJ	dead	O
51	27	giveaway	NN	giveaway	O
51	28	.	.	.	O

8	23	colleague

52	0	Sandman	NNP	Sandman	PERSON
52	1	announced	VBD	announce	O
52	2	the	DT	the	O
52	3	appointment	NN	appointment	O
52	4	of	IN	of	O
52	5	Mrs.	NNP	Mrs.	O
52	6	Harriet	NNP	Harriet	PERSON
52	7	Copeland	NNP	Copeland	PERSON
52	8	Greenfield	NNP	Greenfield	PERSON
52	9	of	IN	of	O
52	10	330	CD	330	O
52	11	Woodland	NNP	Woodland	LOCATION
52	12	Ave.	NNP	Ave.	LOCATION
52	13	,	,	,	O
52	14	Westfield	NNP	Westfield	ORGANIZATION
52	15	,	,	,	O
52	16	as	IN	a	O
52	17	state	NN	state	O
52	18	chairman	NN	chairman	O
52	19	of	IN	of	O
52	20	the	DT	the	O
52	21	Republican	NNP	Republican	ORGANIZATION
52	22	Women	NNP	Women	ORGANIZATION
52	23	for	IN	for	ORGANIZATION
52	24	Jones	NNP	Jones	ORGANIZATION
52	25	Committee	NNP	Committee	ORGANIZATION
52	26	.	.	.	O

6	11	homeLocation
21	6	employee

53	0	The	DT	The	O
53	1	candidacy	NN	candidacy	O
53	2	of	IN	of	O
53	3	Mayor	NNP	Mayor	O
53	4	James	NNP	James	PERSON
53	5	J.	NNP	J.	PERSON
53	6	Sheeran	NNP	Sheeran	PERSON
53	7	of	IN	of	O
53	8	West	NNP	West	LOCATION
53	9	Orange	NNP	Orange	LOCATION
53	10	,	,	,	O
53	11	for	IN	for	O
53	12	the	DT	the	O
53	13	Republican	NNP	Republican	ORGANIZATION
53	14	nomination	NN	nomination	O
53	15	for	IN	for	O
53	16	sheriff	NN	sheriff	O
53	17	of	IN	of	O
53	18	Essex	NNP	Essex	LOCATION
53	19	County	NNP	County	LOCATION
53	20	,	,	,	O
53	21	was	VBD	be	O
53	22	supported	VBN	support	O
53	23	today	NN	today	O
53	24	by	IN	by	O
53	25	Edward	NNP	Edward	PERSON
53	26	W.	NNP	W.	PERSON
53	27	Roos	NNP	Roos	PERSON
53	28	,	,	,	O
53	29	West	NNP	West	LOCATION
53	30	Orange	NNP	Orange	LOCATION
53	31	public	JJ	public	O
53	32	safety	NN	safety	O
53	33	commissioner	NN	commissioner	O
53	34	.	.	.	O

4	8	homeLocation
25	29	homeLocation

54	0	Sheeran	NNP	Sheeran	PERSON
54	1	,	,	,	O
54	2	a	DT	a	O
54	3	lawyer	NN	lawyer	O
54	4	and	CC	and	O
54	5	former	JJ	former	O
54	6	FBI	NNP	FBI	ORGANIZATION
54	7	man	NN	man	O
54	8	is	VBZ	be	O
54	9	running	VBG	run	O
54	10	against	IN	against	O
54	11	the	DT	the	O
54	12	Republican	JJ	Republican	O
54	13	organization's	NN	organization's	O
54	14	candidate	NN	candidate	O
54	15	,	,	,	O
54	16	Freeholder	NNP	Freeholder	PERSON
54	17	William	NNP	William	PERSON
54	18	MacDonald	NNP	MacDonald	PERSON
54	19	,	,	,	O
54	20	for	IN	for	O
54	21	the	DT	the	O
54	22	vacancy	NN	vacancy	O
54	23	left	VBN	leave	O
54	24	by	IN	by	O
54	25	the	DT	the	O
54	26	resignation	NN	resignation	O
54	27	of	IN	of	O
54	28	Neil	NNP	Neil	PERSON
54	29	Duffy	NNP	Duffy	PERSON
54	30	,	,	,	O
54	31	now	RB	now	O
54	32	a	DT	a	O
54	33	member	NN	member	O
54	34	of	IN	of	O
54	35	the	DT	the	O
54	36	State	NNP	State	ORGANIZATION
54	37	Board	NNP	Board	ORGANIZATION
54	38	of	IN	of	ORGANIZATION
54	39	Tax	NNP	Tax	ORGANIZATION
54	40	Appeals	NNP	Appeals	ORGANIZATION
54	41	.	.	.	O

6	0	employee
36	28	employee

55	0	Resentment	NN	Resentment	O
55	1	welled	VBD	well	O
55	2	up	RP	up	O
55	3	yesterday	NN	yesterday	O
55	4	among	IN	among	O
55	5	Democratic	JJ	Democratic	O
55	6	district	NN	district	O
55	7	leaders	NNS	leader	O
55	8	and	CC	and	O
55	9	some	DT	some	O
55	10	county	NN	county	O
55	11	leaders	NNS	leader	O
55	12	at	IN	at	O
55	13	reports	NNS	report	O
55	14	that	IN	that	O
55	15	Mayor	NNP	Mayor	O
55	16	Wagner	NNP	Wagner	PERSON
55	17	had	VBD	have	O
55	18	decided	VBN	decide	O
55	19	to	TO	to	O
55	20	seek	VB	seek	O
55	21	a	DT	a	O
55	22	third	JJ	third	O
55	23	term	NN	term	O
55	24	with	IN	with	O
55	25	Paul	NNP	Paul	PERSON
55	26	R.	NNP	R.	PERSON
55	27	Screvane	NNP	Screvane	PERSON
55	28	and	CC	and	O
55	29	Abraham	NNP	Abraham	PERSON
55	30	D.	NNP	D.	PERSON
55	31	Beame	NNP	Beame	PERSON
55	32	as	IN	a	O
55	33	running	VBG	run	O
55	34	mates	NNS	mate	O
55	35	.	.	.	O

16	25	colleague
16	29	colleague
25	29	colleague

56	0	Some	DT	Some	O
56	1	Democratic	JJ	Democratic	O
56	2	district	NN	district	O
56	3	and	CC	and	O
56	4	county	NN	county	O
56	5	leaders	NNS	leader	O
56	6	are	VBP	be	O
56	7	reported	VBN	report	O
56	8	trying	VBG	try	O
56	9	to	TO	to	O
56	10	induce	VB	induce	O
56	11	State	NNP	State	O
56	12	Controller	NNP	Controller	O
56	13	Arthur	NNP	Arthur	PERSON
56	14	Levitt	NNP	Levitt	PERSON
56	15	of	IN	of	O
56	16	Brooklyn	NNP	Brooklyn	LOCATION
56	17	to	TO	to	O
56	18	oppose	VB	oppose	O
56	19	Mr.	NNP	Mr.	O
56	20	Wagner	NNP	Wagner	PERSON
56	21	for	IN	for	O
56	22	the	DT	the	O
56	23	Mayoral	NNP	Mayoral	O
56	24	nomination	NN	nomination	O
56	25	in	IN	in	O
56	26	the	DT	the	O
56	27	Sept.	NNP	Sept.	O
56	28	7	CD	7	O
56	29	Democratic	NNP	Democratic	O
56	30	primary	NN	primary	O
56	31	.	.	.	O

13	16	homeLocation

57	0	In	IN	In	O
57	1	an	DT	an	O
57	2	apparent	JJ	apparent	O
57	3	effort	NN	effort	O
57	4	to	TO	to	O
57	5	head	VB	head	O
57	6	off	RP	off	O
57	7	such	JJ	such	O
57	8	a	DT	a	O
57	9	rival	JJ	rival	O
57	10	primary	JJ	primary	O
57	11	slate	NN	slate	O
57	12	,	,	,	O
57	13	Mr.	NNP	Mr.	O
57	14	Wagner	NNP	Wagner	PERSON
57	15	talked	VBD	talk	O
57	16	by	IN	by	O
57	17	telephone	NN	telephone	O
57	18	yesterday	NN	yesterday	O
57	19	with	IN	with	O
57	20	Representative	NNP	Representative	O
57	21	Charles	NNP	Charles	PERSON
57	22	A.	NNP	A.	PERSON
57	23	Buckley	NNP	Buckley	PERSON
57	24	,	,	,	O
57	25	the	DT	the	O
57	26	Bronx	NNP	Bronx	LOCATION
57	27	Democratic	JJ	Democratic	O
57	28	leader	NN	leader	O
57	29	,	,	,	O
57	30	and	CC	and	O
57	31	with	IN	with	O
57	32	Joseph	NNP	Joseph	PERSON
57	33	T.	NNP	T.	PERSON
57	34	Sharkey	NNP	Sharkey	PERSON
57	35	,	,	,	O
57	36	the	DT	the	O
57	37	Brooklyn	NNP	Brooklyn	ORGANIZATION
57	38	Democratic	JJ	Democratic	ORGANIZATION
57	39	leader	NN	leader	O
57	40	.	.	.	O

14	21	colleague
14	32	colleague
21	26	homeLocation
37	32	employee

58	0	In	IN	In	O
58	1	talks	NNS	talk	O
58	2	with	IN	with	O
58	3	Mr.	NNP	Mr.	O
58	4	Buckley	NNP	Buckley	PERSON
58	5	last	JJ	last	O
58	6	week	NN	week	O
58	7	in	IN	in	O
58	8	Washington	NNP	Washington	LOCATION
58	9	,	,	,	O
58	10	the	DT	the	O
58	11	Mayor	NNP	Mayor	O
58	12	apparently	RB	apparently	O
58	13	received	VBD	receive	O
58	14	the	DT	the	O
58	15	Bronx	NNP	Bronx	LOCATION
58	16	leader's	NN	leader's	O
58	17	assent	NN	assent	O
58	18	to	TO	to	O
58	19	dropping	VBG	drop	O
58	20	Controller	NNP	Controller	O
58	21	Lawrence	NNP	Lawrence	PERSON
58	22	E.	NNP	E.	PERSON
58	23	Gerosa	NNP	Gerosa	PERSON
58	24	,	,	,	O
58	25	who	WP	who	O
58	26	lives	VBZ	live	O
58	27	in	IN	in	O
58	28	the	DT	the	O
58	29	Bronx	NNP	Bronx	LOCATION
58	30	,	,	,	O
58	31	from	IN	from	O
58	32	this	DT	this	O
58	33	year's	NN	year's	O
58	34	ticket	NN	ticket	O
58	35	.	.	.	O

21	29	homeLocation

59	0	But	CC	But	O
59	1	Mr.	NNP	Mr.	O
59	2	Buckley	NNP	Buckley	PERSON
59	3	seems	VBZ	seem	O
59	4	to	TO	to	O
59	5	have	VB	have	O
59	6	assumed	VBN	assume	O
59	7	he	PRP	he	O
59	8	would	MD	would	O
59	9	be	VB	be	O
59	10	given	VBN	give	O
59	11	the	DT	the	O
59	12	right	NN	right	O
59	13	to	TO	to	O
59	14	pick	VB	pick	O
59	15	Mr.	NNP	Mr.	O
59	16	Gerosa's	NNP	Gerosa's	PERSON
59	17	successor	NN	successor	O
59	18	.	.	.	O


60	0	Screvane	NNP	Screvane	PERSON
60	1	and	CC	and	O
60	2	Beame	NNP	Beame	PERSON
60	3	hailed	VBD	hail	O

0	2	colleague

61	0	The	DT	The	O
61	1	Mayor	NNP	Mayor	O
61	2	declined	VBD	decline	O
61	3	in	IN	in	O
61	4	two	CD	two	O
61	5	interviews	NNS	interview	O
61	6	with	IN	with	O
61	7	reporters	NNS	reporter	O
61	8	yesterday	NN	yesterday	O
61	9	to	TO	to	O
61	10	confirm	VB	confirm	O
61	11	or	CC	or	O
61	12	deny	VB	deny	O
61	13	the	DT	the	O
61	14	reports	NNS	report	O
61	15	that	IN	that	O
61	16	he	PRP	he	O
61	17	had	VBD	have	O
61	18	decided	VBN	decide	O
61	19	to	TO	to	O
61	20	run	VB	run	O
61	21	and	CC	and	O
61	22	wanted	VBD	want	O
61	23	Mr.	NNP	Mr.	O
61	24	Screvane	NNP	Screvane	PERSON
61	25	,	,	,	O
61	26	who	WP	who	O
61	27	lives	VBZ	live	O
61	28	in	IN	in	O
61	29	Queens	NNP	Queens	LOCATION
61	30	,	,	,	O
61	31	to	TO	to	O
61	32	replace	VB	replace	O
61	33	Abe	NNP	Abe	PERSON
61	34	Stark	NNP	Stark	PERSON
61	35	,	,	,	O
61	36	the	DT	the	O
61	37	incumbent	NN	incumbent	O
61	38	,	,	,	O
61	39	as	IN	a	O
61	40	the	DT	the	O
61	41	candidate	NN	candidate	O
61	42	for	IN	for	O
61	43	President	NNP	President	O
61	44	of	IN	of	O
61	45	the	DT	the	O
61	46	City	NNP	City	ORGANIZATION
61	47	Council	NNP	Council	ORGANIZATION
61	48	and	CC	and	O
61	49	Mr.	NNP	Mr.	O
61	50	Beame	NNP	Beame	PERSON
61	51	,	,	,	O
61	52	who	WP	who	O
61	53	lives	VBZ	live	O
61	54	in	IN	in	O
61	55	Brooklyn	NNP	Brooklyn	LOCATION
61	56	,	,	,	O
61	57	to	TO	to	O
61	58	replace	VB	replace	O
61	59	Mr.	NNP	Mr.	O
61	60	Gerosa	NNP	Gerosa	PERSON
61	61	as	IN	a	O
61	62	the	DT	the	O
61	63	candidate	NN	candidate	O
61	64	for	IN	for	O
61	65	Controller	NNP	Controller	O
61	66	.	.	.	O

24	29	homeLocation
24	33	colleague
50	55	homeLocation
50	60	colleague

62	0	``	``	``	O
62	1	It's	NNP	It's	O
62	2	'	POS	'	O
62	3	See	NNP	See	O
62	4	Joe	NNP	Joe	PERSON
62	5	,	,	,	O
62	6	see	VB	see	O
62	7	Jim	NNP	Jim	PERSON
62	8	'	POS	'	O
62	9	''	''	''	O
62	10	,	,	,	O
62	11	he	PRP	he	O
62	12	says	VBZ	say	O
62	13	.	.	.	O


63	0	The	DT	The	O
63	1	panel's	JJ	panel's	O
63	2	action	NN	action	O
63	3	depends	VBZ	depend	O
63	4	on	IN	on	O
63	5	the	DT	the	O
63	6	return	NN	return	O
63	7	of	IN	of	O
63	8	Representative	NNP	Representative	O
63	9	James	NNP	James	PERSON
63	10	W.	NNP	W.	PERSON
63	11	Trimble	NNP	Trimble	PERSON
63	12	,	,	,	O
63	13	Democrat	NNP	Democrat	O
63	14	of	IN	of	O
63	15	Arkansas	NNP	Arkansas	LOCATION
63	16	,	,	,	O
63	17	who	WP	who	O
63	18	has	VBZ	have	O
63	19	been	VBN	be	O
63	20	siding	VBG	side	O
63	21	with	IN	with	O
63	22	Speaker	NNP	Speaker	O
63	23	Sam	NNP	Sam	PERSON
63	24	Rayburn's	NNP	Rayburn's	PERSON
63	25	forces	NNS	force	O
63	26	in	IN	in	O
63	27	the	DT	the	O
63	28	Rules	NNP	Rules	ORGANIZATION
63	29	Committee	NNP	Committee	ORGANIZATION
63	30	in	IN	in	O
63	31	moving	VBG	move	O
63	32	bills	NNS	bill	O
63	33	to	TO	to	O
63	34	the	DT	the	O
63	35	floor	NN	floor	O
63	36	.	.	.	O

9	15	homeLocation
28	23	employee

64	0	They	PRP	They	O
64	1	are	VBP	be	O
64	2	James	NNP	James	PERSON
64	3	J.	NNP	J.	PERSON
64	4	Delaney	NNP	Delaney	PERSON
64	5	of	IN	of	O
64	6	Queens	NNP	Queens	LOCATION
64	7	and	CC	and	O
64	8	Thomas	NNP	Thomas	PERSON
64	9	P.	NNP	P.	PERSON
64	10	O'Neill	NNP	O'Neill	PERSON
64	11	Jr.	NNP	Jr.	PERSON
64	12	of	IN	of	O
64	13	Massachusetts	NNP	Massachusetts	LOCATION
64	14	.	.	.	O

2	6	homeLocation
8	13	homeLocation

65	0	Mr.	NNP	Mr.	O
65	1	Delaney	NNP	Delaney	PERSON
65	2	and	CC	and	O
65	3	Mr.	NNP	Mr.	O
65	4	O'Neill	NNP	O'Neill	PERSON
65	5	are	VBP	be	O
65	6	not	RB	not	O
65	7	willing	JJ	willing	O
65	8	to	TO	to	O
65	9	vote	VB	vote	O
65	10	on	IN	on	O
65	11	the	DT	the	O
65	12	public-school	JJ	public-school	O
65	13	measure	NN	measure	O
65	14	until	IN	until	O
65	15	the	DT	the	O
65	16	defense	NN	defense	O
65	17	education	NN	education	O
65	18	bill	NN	bill	O
65	19	clears	VBZ	clear	O
65	20	the	DT	the	O
65	21	House	NNP	House	ORGANIZATION
65	22	Education	NNP	Education	ORGANIZATION
65	23	and	CC	and	ORGANIZATION
65	24	Labor	NNP	Labor	ORGANIZATION
65	25	Committee	NNP	Committee	ORGANIZATION
65	26	.	.	.	O

1	4	colleague

66	0	--	:	--	O
66	1	At	IN	At	O
66	2	a	DT	a	O
66	3	gay	NN	gay	O
66	4	party	NN	party	O
66	5	in	IN	in	O
66	6	the	DT	the	O
66	7	Kremlin	NNP	Kremlin	LOCATION
66	8	for	IN	for	O
66	9	President	NNP	President	O
66	10	Sukarno	NNP	Sukarno	PERSON
66	11	of	IN	of	O
66	12	Indonesia	NNP	Indonesia	LOCATION
66	13	,	,	,	O
66	14	Premier	NNP	Premier	O
66	15	Khrushchev	NNP	Khrushchev	PERSON
66	16	pulled	VBD	pull	O
66	17	out	RP	out	O
66	18	his	PRP$	his	O
66	19	pockets	NNS	pocket	O
66	20	and	CC	and	O
66	21	said	VBD	say	O
66	22	,	,	,	O
66	23	beaming	NN	beaming	O
66	24	:	:	:	O
66	25	``	``	``	O
66	26	Look	VB	Look	O
66	27	,	,	,	O
66	28	he	PRP	he	O
66	29	took	VBD	take	O
66	30	everything	NN	everything	O
66	31	I	PRP	I	O
66	32	had	VBD	have	O
66	33	''	''	''	O
66	34	!	.	!	O
66	35	!	.	!	O

10	12	nationality

67	0	Prince	NNP	Prince	PERSON
67	1	Souvanna	NNP	Souvanna	PERSON
67	2	Phouma	NNP	Phouma	PERSON
67	3	,	,	,	O
67	4	leader	NN	leader	O
67	5	of	IN	of	O
67	6	the	DT	the	O
67	7	nation's	JJ	nation's	O
67	8	neutralists	NNS	neutralist	O
67	9	and	CC	and	O
67	10	recognized	VBN	recognize	O
67	11	as	IN	a	O
67	12	Premier	NNP	Premier	O
67	13	by	IN	by	O
67	14	the	DT	the	O
67	15	Communist	NNP	Communist	O
67	16	bloc	NN	bloc	O
67	17	,	,	,	O
67	18	and	CC	and	O
67	19	Prince	NNP	Prince	PERSON
67	20	Souphanouvong	NNP	Souphanouvong	PERSON
67	21	,	,	,	O
67	22	head	NN	head	O
67	23	of	IN	of	O
67	24	the	DT	the	O
67	25	pro-Communist	JJ	pro-Communist	O
67	26	Pathet	NNP	Pathet	ORGANIZATION
67	27	Lao	NNP	Lao	ORGANIZATION
67	28	forces	NNS	force	O
67	29	.	.	.	O

26	19	employee

68	0	W.	NNP	W.	PERSON
68	1	Averell	NNP	Averell	PERSON
68	2	Harriman	NNP	Harriman	PERSON
68	3	of	IN	of	O
68	4	the	DT	the	O
68	5	United	NNP	United	LOCATION
68	6	States	NNPS	States	LOCATION
68	7	,	,	,	O
68	8	Malcolm	NNP	Malcolm	PERSON
68	9	MacDonald	NNP	MacDonald	PERSON
68	10	of	IN	of	O
68	11	Britain	NNP	Britain	LOCATION
68	12	,	,	,	O
68	13	Maurice	NNP	Maurice	PERSON
68	14	Couve	NNP	Couve	PERSON
68	15	De	NNP	De	PERSON
68	16	Murville	NNP	Murville	PERSON
68	17	,	,	,	O
68	18	France's	NNP	France's	O
68	19	Foreign	NNP	Foreign	O
68	20	Minister	NNP	Minister	O
68	21	,	,	,	O
68	22	and	CC	and	O
68	23	Howard	NNP	Howard	PERSON
68	24	C.	NNP	C.	PERSON
68	25	Green	NNP	Green	PERSON
68	26	,	,	,	O
68	27	Canada's	NNP	Canada's	O
68	28	Minister	NNP	Minister	O
68	29	of	IN	of	O
68	30	External	NNP	External	O
68	31	Affairs	NNP	Affairs	O
68	32	,	,	,	O
68	33	concluded	VBD	conclude	O
68	34	,	,	,	O
68	35	meanwhile	RB	meanwhile	O
68	36	,	,	,	O
68	37	a	DT	a	O
68	38	round	NN	round	O
68	39	of	IN	of	O
68	40	consultations	NNS	consultation	O
68	41	here	RB	here	O
68	42	on	IN	on	O
68	43	future	JJ	future	O
68	44	tactics	NNS	tactic	O
68	45	in	IN	in	O
68	46	the	DT	the	O
68	47	conference	NN	conference	O
68	48	.	.	.	O

0	5	nationality
0	8	colleague
0	13	colleague
0	23	colleague
8	11	nationality
8	13	colleague
8	23	colleague
13	23	colleague

3	1	children

70	0	Appointment	NN	Appointment	O
70	1	of	IN	of	O
70	2	William	NNP	William	PERSON
70	3	S.	NNP	S.	PERSON
70	4	Pfaff	NNP	Pfaff	PERSON
70	5	Jr.	NNP	Jr.	PERSON
70	6	,	,	,	O
70	7	41	CD	41	O
70	8	,	,	,	O
70	9	as	IN	a	O
70	10	promotion	NN	promotion	O
70	11	manager	NN	manager	O
70	12	of	IN	of	O
70	13	The	DT	The	O
70	14	Times-Picayune	NNP	Times-Picayune	ORGANIZATION
70	15	Publishing	NNP	Publishing	ORGANIZATION
70	16	Company	NNP	Company	ORGANIZATION
70	17	was	VBD	be	O
70	18	announced	VBN	announce	O
70	19	Saturday	NNP	Saturday	O
70	20	by	IN	by	O
70	21	John	NNP	John	PERSON
70	22	F.	NNP	F.	PERSON
70	23	Tims	NNP	Tims	PERSON
70	24	,	,	,	O
70	25	president	NN	president	O
70	26	of	IN	of	O
70	27	the	DT	the	O
70	28	company	NN	company	O
70	29	.	.	.	O

14	2	employee
14	21	employee

71	0	Pfaff	NNP	Pfaff	PERSON
71	1	succeeds	VBZ	succeed	O
71	2	Martin	NNP	Martin	PERSON
71	3	Burke	NNP	Burke	PERSON
71	4	,	,	,	O
71	5	who	WP	who	O
71	6	resigned	VBD	resign	O
71	7	.	.	.	O

0	2	colleague

72	0	He	PRP	He	O
72	1	is	VBZ	be	O
72	2	married	VBN	marry	O
72	3	to	TO	to	O
72	4	the	DT	the	O
72	5	former	JJ	former	O
72	6	Audrey	NNP	Audrey	PERSON
72	7	Knecht	NNP	Knecht	PERSON
72	8	and	CC	and	O
72	9	has	VBZ	have	O
72	10	a	DT	a	O
72	11	daughter	NN	daughter	O
72	12	,	,	,	O
72	13	Karol	NNP	Karol	PERSON
72	14	,	,	,	O
72	15	13	CD	13	O
72	16	.	.	.	O

6	13	children

73	0	Assuming	VBG	Assuming	O
73	1	the	DT	the	O
73	2	weather	NN	weather	O
73	3	is	VBZ	be	O
73	4	halfway	JJ	halfway	O
73	5	decent	JJ	decent	O
73	6	that	IN	that	O
73	7	day	NN	day	O
73	8	,	,	,	O
73	9	hundreds	NNS	hundred	O
73	10	of	IN	of	O
73	11	thousands	NNS	thousand	O
73	12	of	IN	of	O
73	13	persons	NNS	person	O
73	14	will	MD	will	O
73	15	mass	VB	mass	O
73	16	along	IN	along	O
73	17	this	DT	this	O
73	18	thoroughfare	NN	thoroughfare	O
73	19	as	IN	a	O
73	20	President	NNP	President	O
73	21	John	NNP	John	PERSON
73	22	F.	NNP	F.	PERSON
73	23	Kennedy	NNP	Kennedy	PERSON
73	24	and	CC	and	O
73	25	retiring	VBG	retire	O
73	26	President	NNP	President	O
73	27	Dwight	NNP	Dwight	PERSON
73	28	D.	NNP	D.	PERSON
73	29	Eisenhower	NNP	Eisenhower	PERSON
73	30	leave	VBP	leave	O
73	31	Capitol	NNP	Capitol	LOCATION
73	32	Hill	NNP	Hill	LOCATION
73	33	following	VBG	follow	O
73	34	the	DT	the	O
73	35	oath-taking	JJ	oath-taking	O
73	36	ceremonies	NNS	ceremony	O
73	37	and	CC	and	O
73	38	ride	VB	ride	O
73	39	down	RB	down	O
73	40	this	DT	this	O
73	41	historic	JJ	historic	O
73	42	ceremonial	JJ	ceremonial	O
73	43	route	NN	route	O
73	44	.	.	.	O

21	27	colleague

74	0	The	DT	The	O
74	1	builtin	NN	builtin	O
74	2	headache	NN	headache	O
74	3	of	IN	of	O
74	4	the	DT	the	O
74	5	Barnett	NNP	Barnett	PERSON
74	6	regime	NN	regime	O
74	7	thus	RB	thus	O
74	8	far	RB	far	O
74	9	has	VBZ	have	O
74	10	been	VBN	be	O
74	11	the	DT	the	O
74	12	steady	JJ	steady	O
74	13	stream	NN	stream	O
74	14	of	IN	of	O
74	15	job-seekers	NNS	job-seekers	O
74	16	and	CC	and	O
74	17	others	NNS	others	O
74	18	who	WP	who	O
74	19	feel	VBP	feel	O
74	20	they	PRP	they	O
74	21	were	VBD	be	O
74	22	given	VBN	give	O
74	23	commitments	NNS	commitment	O
74	24	by	IN	by	O
74	25	Barnett	NNP	Barnett	PERSON
74	26	at	IN	at	O
74	27	some	DT	some	O
74	28	stage	NN	stage	O
74	29	of	IN	of	O
74	30	his	PRP$	his	O
74	31	eight-year	JJ	eight-year	O
74	32	quest	NN	quest	O
74	33	for	IN	for	O
74	34	the	DT	the	O
74	35	governor's	NN	governor's	O
74	36	office	NN	office	O
74	37	.	.	.	O


75	0	Now	RB	Now	O
75	1	,	,	,	O
75	2	the	DT	the	O
75	3	picture	NN	picture	O
75	4	is	VBZ	be	O
75	5	clouded	VBN	cloud	O
75	6	,	,	,	O
75	7	and	CC	and	O
75	8	even	RB	even	O
75	9	US	NNP	US	LOCATION
75	10	Sens.	NNP	Sens.	O
75	11	James	NNP	James	PERSON
75	12	O.	NNP	O.	PERSON
75	13	Eastland	NNP	Eastland	PERSON
75	14	and	CC	and	O
75	15	John	NNP	John	PERSON
75	16	C.	NNP	C.	PERSON
75	17	Stennis	NNP	Stennis	PERSON
75	18	,	,	,	O
75	19	who	WP	who	O
75	20	remained	VBD	remain	O
75	21	loyal	JJ	loyal	O
75	22	to	TO	to	O
75	23	the	DT	the	O
75	24	ticket	NN	ticket	O
75	25	,	,	,	O
75	26	are	VBP	be	O
75	27	uncertain	JJ	uncertain	O
75	28	of	IN	of	O
75	29	their	PRP$	their	O
75	30	status	NN	status	O
75	31	.	.	.	O

11	9	nationality
11	15	colleague
15	9	nationality

76	0	Managing	VBG	Managing	O
76	1	Director	NNP	Director	O
76	2	Donald	NNP	Donald	PERSON
76	3	C.	NNP	C.	PERSON
76	4	Wagner	NNP	Wagner	PERSON
76	5	has	VBZ	have	O
76	6	agreed	VBN	agree	O
76	7	to	TO	to	O
76	8	cooperate	VB	cooperate	O
76	9	fully	RB	fully	O
76	10	with	IN	with	O
76	11	Hemphill	NNP	Hemphill	PERSON
76	12	after	IN	after	O
76	13	a	DT	a	O
76	14	period	NN	period	O
76	15	of	IN	of	O
76	16	sharp	JJ	sharp	O
76	17	disagreement	NN	disagreement	O
76	18	on	IN	on	O
76	19	the	DT	the	O
76	20	matter	NN	matter	O
76	21	.	.	.	O


77	0	The	DT	The	O
77	1	announcement	NN	announcement	O
77	2	that	IN	that	O
77	3	the	DT	the	O
77	4	city	NN	city	O
77	5	would	MD	would	O
77	6	sue	VB	sue	O
77	7	for	IN	for	O
77	8	recovery	NN	recovery	O
77	9	on	IN	on	O
77	10	the	DT	the	O
77	11	performance	NN	performance	O
77	12	bond	NN	bond	O
77	13	was	VBD	be	O
77	14	made	VBN	make	O
77	15	by	IN	by	O
77	16	City	NNP	City	O
77	17	Solicitor	NNP	Solicitor	O
77	18	David	NNP	David	PERSON
77	19	Berger	NNP	Berger	PERSON
77	20	at	IN	at	O
77	21	a	DT	a	O
77	22	press	NN	press	O
77	23	conference	NN	conference	O
77	24	following	VBG	follow	O
77	25	a	DT	a	O
77	26	meeting	NN	meeting	O
77	27	in	IN	in	O
77	28	the	DT	the	O
77	29	morning	NN	morning	O
77	30	with	IN	with	O
77	31	Wagner	NNP	Wagner	PERSON
77	32	and	CC	and	O
77	33	other	JJ	other	O
77	34	officials	NNS	official	O
77	35	of	IN	of	O
77	36	the	DT	the	O
77	37	city	NN	city	O
77	38	and	CC	and	O
77	39	the	DT	the	O
77	40	PTC	NNP	PTC	O
77	41	as	RB	as	O
77	42	well	RB	well	O
77	43	as	IN	a	O
77	44	representatives	NNS	representative	O
77	45	of	IN	of	O
77	46	an	DT	an	O
77	47	engineering	NN	engineering	O
77	48	firm	NN	firm	O
77	49	that	WDT	that	O
77	50	was	VBD	be	O
77	51	pulled	VBN	pull	O
77	52	off	RP	off	O
77	53	the	DT	the	O
77	54	El	NNP	El	O
77	55	project	NN	project	O
77	56	before	IN	before	O
77	57	its	PRP$	it	O
77	58	completion	NN	completion	O
77	59	in	IN	in	O
77	60	1959	CD	1959	O
77	61	.	.	.	O


78	0	Business	NN	Business	O
78	1	relations	NNS	relation	O
78	2	between	IN	between	O
78	3	the	DT	the	O
78	4	companies	NNS	company	O
78	5	and	CC	and	O
78	6	city	NN	city	O
78	7	have	VBP	have	O
78	8	been	VBN	be	O
78	9	under	IN	under	O
78	10	investigation	NN	investigation	O
78	11	by	IN	by	O
78	12	Hemphill	NNP	Hemphill	PERSON
78	13	and	CC	and	O
78	14	District	NNP	District	O
78	15	Attorney	NNP	Attorney	O
78	16	James	NNP	James	PERSON
78	17	C.	NNP	C.	PERSON
78	18	Crumlish	NNP	Crumlish	PERSON
78	19	,	,	,	O
78	20	Jr.	NNP	Jr.	O
78	21	.	.	.	O


79	0	The	DT	The	O
79	1	new	JJ	new	O
79	2	fee	NN	fee	O
79	3	schedule	NN	schedule	O
79	4	also	RB	also	O
79	5	was	VBD	be	O
79	6	supported	VBN	support	O
79	7	by	IN	by	O
79	8	Commissioner	NNP	Commissioner	O
79	9	of	IN	of	O
79	10	Licenses	NNP	Licenses	O
79	11	and	CC	and	O
79	12	Inspections	NNP	Inspections	O
79	13	Barnet	NNP	Barnet	PERSON
79	14	Lieberman	NNP	Lieberman	PERSON
79	15	and	CC	and	O
79	16	Health	NNP	Health	O
79	17	Commissioner	NNP	Commissioner	O
79	18	Eugene	NNP	Eugene	PERSON
79	19	A.	NN	A.	PERSON
79	20	Gillis	NNP	Gillis	PERSON
79	21	.	.	.	O


80	0	Petitions	NNS	Petitions	O
80	1	asking	VBG	ask	O
80	2	for	IN	for	O
80	3	a	DT	a	O
80	4	jail	JJ	jail	O
80	5	term	NN	term	O
80	6	for	IN	for	O
80	7	Norristown	NNP	Norristown	LOCATION
80	8	attorney	NN	attorney	O
80	9	Julian	NNP	Julian	PERSON
80	10	W.	NNP	W.	PERSON
80	11	Barnard	NNP	Barnard	PERSON
80	12	will	MD	will	O
80	13	be	VB	be	O
80	14	presented	VBN	present	O
80	15	to	TO	to	O
80	16	the	DT	the	O
80	17	Montgomery	NNP	Montgomery	ORGANIZATION
80	18	County	NNP	County	ORGANIZATION
80	19	Court	NNP	Court	ORGANIZATION
80	20	Friday	NNP	Friday	O
80	21	,	,	,	O
80	22	it	PRP	it	O
80	23	was	VBD	be	O
80	24	disclosed	VBN	disclose	O
80	25	Tuesday	NNP	Tuesday	O
80	26	by	IN	by	O
80	27	Horace	NNP	Horace	PERSON
80	28	A.	NNP	A.	PERSON
80	29	Davenport	NNP	Davenport	PERSON
80	30	,	,	,	O
80	31	counsel	NN	counsel	O
80	32	for	IN	for	O
80	33	the	DT	the	O
80	34	widow	NN	widow	O
80	35	of	IN	of	O
80	36	the	DT	the	O
80	37	man	NN	man	O
80	38	killed	VBD	kill	O
80	39	last	JJ	last	O
80	40	Nov.	NNP	Nov.	O
80	41	1	CD	1	O
80	42	by	IN	by	O
80	43	Barnard's	NNP	Barnard's	O
80	44	hit-run	JJ	hit-run	O
80	45	car	NN	car	O
80	46	.	.	.	O

9	7	homeLocation

81	0	The	DT	The	O
81	1	petitions	NNS	petition	O
81	2	will	MD	will	O
81	3	be	VB	be	O
81	4	presented	VBN	present	O
81	5	in	IN	in	O
81	6	open	JJ	open	O
81	7	court	NN	court	O
81	8	to	TO	to	O
81	9	President	NNP	President	O
81	10	Judge	NNP	Judge	O
81	11	William	NNP	William	PERSON
81	12	F.	NNP	F.	PERSON
81	13	Dannehower	NNP	Dannehower	PERSON
81	14	,	,	,	O
81	15	Davenport	NNP	Davenport	PERSON
81	16	said	VBD	say	O
81	17	.	.	.	O


82	0	Barnard	NNP	Barnard	PERSON
82	1	,	,	,	O
82	2	who	WP	who	O
82	3	pleaded	VBD	plead	O
82	4	no	DT	no	O
82	5	defense	NN	defense	O
82	6	to	TO	to	O
82	7	manslaughter	VB	manslaughter	O
82	8	and	CC	and	O
82	9	hit-run	JJ	hit-run	O
82	10	charges	NNS	charge	O
82	11	,	,	,	O
82	12	was	VBD	be	O
82	13	fined	VBN	fin	O
82	14	$500	RB	$500	O
82	15	by	IN	by	O
82	16	Judge	NNP	Judge	O
82	17	Warren	NNP	Warren	PERSON
82	18	K.	NNP	K.	PERSON
82	19	Hess	NNP	Hess	PERSON
82	20	,	,	,	O
82	21	and	CC	and	O
82	22	placed	VBD	place	O
82	23	on	IN	on	O
82	24	two	CD	two	O
82	25	years'	NNS	years'	O
82	26	probation	NN	probation	O
82	27	providing	VBG	provide	O
82	28	he	PRP	he	O
82	29	does	VBZ	do	O
82	30	not	RB	not	O
82	31	drive	VB	drive	O
82	32	during	IN	during	O
82	33	that	DT	that	O
82	34	time	NN	time	O
82	35	.	.	.	O


83	0	Gladden's	NNP	Gladden's	O
83	1	wife	NN	wife	O
83	2	and	CC	and	O
83	3	two	CD	two	O
83	4	of	IN	of	O
83	5	his	PRP$	his	O
83	6	sons	NNS	son	O
83	7	,	,	,	O
83	8	John	NNP	John	PERSON
83	9	,	,	,	O
83	10	17	CD	17	O
83	11	,	,	,	O
83	12	and	CC	and	O
83	13	Jim	NNP	Jim	PERSON
83	14	,	,	,	O
83	15	13	CD	13	O
83	16	,	,	,	O
83	17	were	VBD	be	O
83	18	inside	IN	inside	O
83	19	the	DT	the	O
83	20	house	NN	house	O
83	21	.	.	.	O

8	13	relatedTo

84	0	By-passing	VBG	By-passing	O
84	1	the	DT	the	O
84	2	military	JJ	military	O
84	3	junta	NN	junta	O
84	4	which	WDT	which	O
84	5	has	VBZ	have	O
84	6	ruled	VBN	rule	O
84	7	Turkey	NNP	Turkey	LOCATION
84	8	since	IN	since	O
84	9	the	DT	the	O
84	10	overthrow	NN	overthrow	O
84	11	of	IN	of	O
84	12	Premier	NNP	Premier	O
84	13	Adnan	NNP	Adnan	PERSON
84	14	Menderes	NNP	Menderes	PERSON
84	15	17	CD	17	O
84	16	months	NNS	month	O
84	17	ago	RB	ago	O
84	18	,	,	,	O
84	19	the	DT	the	O
84	20	army	NN	army	O
84	21	general	JJ	general	O
84	22	staff	NN	staff	O
84	23	,	,	,	O
84	24	led	VBN	lead	O
84	25	by	IN	by	O
84	26	Gen.	NNP	Gen.	O
84	27	Cedvet	NNP	Cedvet	PERSON
84	28	Sunay	NNP	Sunay	PERSON
84	29	,	,	,	O
84	30	had	VBD	have	O
84	31	set	VBN	set	O
84	32	a	DT	a	O
84	33	deadline	NN	deadline	O
84	34	for	IN	for	O
84	35	the	DT	the	O
84	36	parties	NNS	party	O
84	37	to	TO	to	O
84	38	join	VB	join	O
84	39	in	IN	in	O
84	40	a	DT	a	O
84	41	national	JJ	national	O
84	42	coalition	NN	coalition	O
84	43	government	NN	government	O
84	44	.	.	.	O

13	7	nationality

85	0	Vincent	NNP	Vincent	PERSON
85	1	G.	NNP	G.	PERSON
85	2	Ierulli	NNP	Ierulli	PERSON
85	3	has	VBZ	have	O
85	4	been	VBN	be	O
85	5	appointed	VBN	appoint	O
85	6	temporary	JJ	temporary	O
85	7	assistant	NN	assistant	O
85	8	district	NN	district	O
85	9	attorney	NN	attorney	O
85	10	,	,	,	O
85	11	it	PRP	it	O
85	12	was	VBD	be	O
85	13	announced	VBN	announce	O
85	14	Monday	NNP	Monday	O
85	15	by	IN	by	O
85	16	Charles	NNP	Charles	PERSON
85	17	E.	NNP	E.	PERSON
85	18	Raymond	NNP	Raymond	PERSON
85	19	,	,	,	O
85	20	District	NNP	District	O
85	21	Attorney	NNP	Attorney	O
85	22	.	.	.	O


86	0	Ierulli	NNP	Ierulli	PERSON
86	1	will	MD	will	O
86	2	replace	VB	replace	O
86	3	Desmond	NNP	Desmond	PERSON
86	4	D.	NNP	D.	PERSON
86	5	Connall	NNP	Connall	PERSON
86	6	who	WP	who	O
86	7	has	VBZ	have	O
86	8	been	VBN	be	O
86	9	called	VBN	call	O
86	10	to	TO	to	O
86	11	active	JJ	active	O
86	12	military	JJ	military	O
86	13	service	NN	service	O
86	14	but	CC	but	O
86	15	is	VBZ	be	O
86	16	expected	VBN	expect	O
86	17	back	RB	back	O
86	18	on	IN	on	O
86	19	the	DT	the	O
86	20	job	NN	job	O
86	21	by	IN	by	O
86	22	March	NNP	March	O
86	23	31	CD	31	O
86	24	.	.	.	O

0	3	colleague

87	0	Mrs.	NNP	Mrs.	O
87	1	Molvar	NNP	Molvar	PERSON
87	2	asked	VBD	ask	O
87	3	again	RB	again	O
87	4	that	IN	that	O
87	5	the	DT	the	O
87	6	board	NN	board	O
87	7	join	NN	join	O
87	8	in	IN	in	O
87	9	taking	VBG	take	O
87	10	a	DT	a	O
87	11	stand	NN	stand	O
87	12	in	IN	in	O
87	13	keeping	VBG	keep	O
87	14	with	IN	with	O
87	15	Jack	NNP	Jack	PERSON
87	16	Lowe's	NNP	Lowe's	O
87	17	program	NN	program	O
87	18	.	.	.	O


88	0	Secretary	NNP	Secretary	O
88	1	of	IN	of	O
88	2	Labor	NNP	Labor	ORGANIZATION
88	3	Arthur	NNP	Arthur	ORGANIZATION
88	4	Goldberg	NNP	Goldberg	ORGANIZATION
88	5	will	MD	will	O
88	6	speak	VB	speak	O
88	7	Sunday	NNP	Sunday	O
88	8	night	NN	night	O
88	9	at	IN	at	O
88	10	the	DT	the	O
88	11	Masonic	NNP	Masonic	ORGANIZATION
88	12	Temple	NNP	Temple	ORGANIZATION
88	13	at	IN	at	O
88	14	a	DT	a	O
88	15	$25-a-plate	JJ	$25-a-plate	O
88	16	dinner	NN	dinner	O
88	17	honoring	VBG	honor	O
88	18	Sen.	NNP	Sen.	O
88	19	Wayne	NNP	Wayne	PERSON
88	20	L.	NNP	L.	PERSON
88	21	Morse	NNP	Morse	PERSON
88	22	,	,	,	O
88	23	Aj	NNP	Aj	PERSON
88	24	.	.	.	O


89	0	Secretary	NNP	Secretary	O
89	1	Goldberg	NNP	Goldberg	PERSON
89	2	and	CC	and	O
89	3	Sen.	NNP	Sen.	O
89	4	Morse	NNP	Morse	PERSON
89	5	will	MD	will	O
89	6	hold	VB	hold	O
89	7	a	DT	a	O
89	8	joint	JJ	joint	O
89	9	press	NN	press	O
89	10	conference	NN	conference	O
89	11	at	IN	at	O
89	12	the	DT	the	O
89	13	Roosevelt	NNP	Roosevelt	ORGANIZATION
89	14	Hotel	NNP	Hotel	ORGANIZATION
89	15	at	IN	at	O
89	16	4:30	CD	4:30	O
89	17	p.m.	NN	p.m.	O
89	18	Sunday	NNP	Sunday	O
89	19	,	,	,	O
89	20	Blaine	NNP	Blaine	PERSON
89	21	Whipple	NNP	Whipple	PERSON
89	22	,	,	,	O
89	23	executive	NN	executive	O
89	24	secretary	NN	secretary	O
89	25	of	IN	of	O
89	26	the	DT	the	O
89	27	Democratic	NNP	Democratic	ORGANIZATION
89	28	Party	NNP	Party	ORGANIZATION
89	29	of	IN	of	ORGANIZATION
89	30	Oregon	NNP	Oregon	ORGANIZATION
89	31	,	,	,	O
89	32	reported	VBD	report	O
89	33	Tuesday	NNP	Tuesday	O
89	34	.	.	.	O

27	20	employee

90	0	Other	JJ	Other	O
90	1	speakers	NNS	speaker	O
90	2	for	IN	for	O
90	3	the	DT	the	O
90	4	fund-raising	JJ	fund-raising	O
90	5	dinner	NN	dinner	O
90	6	include	VBP	include	O
90	7	Reps.	NNP	Reps.	O
90	8	Edith	NNP	Edith	PERSON
90	9	Green	NNP	Green	PERSON
90	10	and	CC	and	O
90	11	Al	NNP	Al	PERSON
90	12	Ullman	NNP	Ullman	PERSON
90	13	,	,	,	O
90	14	Labor	NNP	Labor	O
90	15	Commissioner	NNP	Commissioner	O
90	16	Norman	NNP	Norman	PERSON
90	17	Nilsen	NNP	Nilsen	PERSON
90	18	and	CC	and	O
90	19	Mayor	NNP	Mayor	O
90	20	Terry	NNP	Terry	PERSON
90	21	Schrunk	NNP	Schrunk	PERSON
90	22	,	,	,	O
90	23	all	DT	all	O
90	24	Democrats	NNPS	Democrats	O
90	25	.	.	.	O


91	0	Incumbent	JJ	Incumbent	O
91	1	Richard	NNP	Richard	PERSON
91	2	Salter	NNP	Salter	PERSON
91	3	seeks	VBZ	seek	O
91	4	re-election	NN	re-election	O
91	5	and	CC	and	O
91	6	is	VBZ	be	O
91	7	opposed	VBN	oppose	O
91	8	by	IN	by	O
91	9	Donald	NNP	Donald	PERSON
91	10	Huffman	NNP	Huffman	PERSON
91	11	for	IN	for	O
91	12	the	DT	the	O
91	13	five-year	JJ	five-year	O
91	14	term	NN	term	O
91	15	.	.	.	O



93	0	Seeking	VBG	Seeking	O
93	1	this	DT	this	O
93	2	two-year	JJ	two-year	O
93	3	term	NN	term	O
93	4	are	VBP	be	O
93	5	James	NNP	James	PERSON
93	6	Culbertson	NNP	Culbertson	PERSON
93	7	,	,	,	O
93	8	Dwight	NNP	Dwight	PERSON
93	9	M.	NNP	M.	PERSON
93	10	Steeves	NNP	Steeves	PERSON
93	11	,	,	,	O
93	12	James	NNP	James	PERSON
93	13	C.	NNP	C.	PERSON
93	14	Piersee	NNP	Piersee	PERSON
93	15	,	,	,	O
93	16	W.M.	NNP	W.M.	PERSON
93	17	Sexton	NNP	Sexton	PERSON
93	18	and	CC	and	O
93	19	Theodore	NNP	Theodore	PERSON
93	20	W.	NNP	W.	PERSON
93	21	Heitschmidt	NNP	Heitschmidt	PERSON
93	22	.	.	.	O


94	0	Attorney	NNP	Attorney	O
94	1	Dwight	NNP	Dwight	PERSON
94	2	L.	NNP	L.	PERSON
94	3	Schwab	NNP	Schwab	PERSON
94	4	,	,	,	O
94	5	in	IN	in	O
94	6	behalf	NN	behalf	O
94	7	of	IN	of	O
94	8	defendant	JJ	defendant	O
94	9	Philip	NNP	Philip	PERSON
94	10	Weinstein	NNP	Weinstein	PERSON
94	11	,	,	,	O
94	12	argued	VBD	argue	O
94	13	there	EX	there	O
94	14	is	VBZ	be	O
94	15	no	DT	no	O
94	16	evidence	NN	evidence	O
94	17	linking	VBG	link	O
94	18	Weinstein	NNP	Weinstein	PERSON
94	19	to	TO	to	O
94	20	the	DT	the	O
94	21	conspiracy	NN	conspiracy	O
94	22	,	,	,	O
94	23	but	CC	but	O
94	24	Judge	NNP	Judge	O
94	25	Powell	NNP	Powell	PERSON
94	26	declared	VBD	declare	O
94	27	this	DT	this	O
94	28	is	VBZ	be	O
94	29	a	DT	a	O
94	30	matter	NN	matter	O
94	31	for	IN	for	O
94	32	the	DT	the	O
94	33	jury	NN	jury	O
94	34	to	TO	to	O
94	35	decide	VB	decide	O
94	36	.	.	.	O


95	0	Schwab	NNP	Schwab	PERSON
95	1	also	RB	also	O
95	2	declared	VBD	declare	O
95	3	there	EX	there	O
95	4	is	VBZ	be	O
95	5	no	DT	no	O
95	6	proof	NN	proof	O
95	7	of	IN	of	O
95	8	Weinstein's	NNP	Weinstein's	O
95	9	entering	VBG	enter	O
95	10	a	DT	a	O
95	11	conspiracy	NN	conspiracy	O
95	12	to	TO	to	O
95	13	use	VB	use	O
95	14	the	DT	the	O
95	15	U.S.	NNP	U.S.	LOCATION
95	16	mails	NNS	mail	O
95	17	to	TO	to	O
95	18	defraud	VB	defraud	O
95	19	,	,	,	O
95	20	to	TO	to	O
95	21	which	WDT	which	O
95	22	federal	JJ	federal	O
95	23	prosecutor	NN	prosecutor	O
95	24	A.	NNP	A.	PERSON
95	25	Lawrence	NNP	Lawrence	PERSON
95	26	Burbank	NNP	Burbank	PERSON
95	27	replied	VBD	reply	O
95	28	:	:	:	O


96	0	A	DT	A	O
96	1	two-run	JJ	two-run	O
96	2	homer	NN	homer	O
96	3	by	IN	by	O
96	4	Norm	NNP	Norm	PERSON
96	5	Siebern	NNP	Siebern	PERSON
96	6	and	CC	and	O
96	7	a	DT	a	O
96	8	solo	NN	solo	O
96	9	blast	NN	blast	O
96	10	by	IN	by	O
96	11	Bill	NNP	Bill	PERSON
96	12	Tuttle	NNP	Tuttle	PERSON
96	13	tied	VBD	tie	O
96	14	the	DT	the	O
96	15	game	NN	game	O
96	16	,	,	,	O
96	17	and	CC	and	O
96	18	single	JJ	single	O
96	19	runs	NNS	run	O
96	20	in	IN	in	O
96	21	the	DT	the	O
96	22	eighth	JJ	eighth	O
96	23	and	CC	and	O
96	24	ninth	JJ	ninth	O
96	25	gave	VBD	give	O
96	26	the	DT	the	O
96	27	Athletics	NNPS	Athletics	ORGANIZATION
96	28	their	PRP$	their	O
96	29	fifth	JJ	fifth	O
96	30	victory	NN	victory	O
96	31	in	IN	in	O
96	32	eight	CD	eight	O
96	33	starts	NNS	start	O
96	34	.	.	.	O

4	11	colleague
27	4	employee
27	11	employee

97	0	With	IN	With	O
97	1	one	CD	one	O
97	2	down	NN	down	O
97	3	in	IN	in	O
97	4	the	DT	the	O
97	5	eighth	NN	eighth	O
97	6	,	,	,	O
97	7	Marv	NNP	Marv	PERSON
97	8	Throneberry	NNP	Throneberry	PERSON
97	9	drew	VBD	draw	O
97	10	a	DT	a	O
97	11	walk	NN	walk	O
97	12	and	CC	and	O
97	13	stole	JJ	stole	O
97	14	second	NN	second	O
97	15	as	IN	a	O
97	16	Hyde	NNP	Hyde	PERSON
97	17	fanned	VBD	fan	O
97	18	Tuttle	NNP	Tuttle	PERSON
97	19	.	.	.	O


98	0	Then	RB	Then	O
98	1	Heywood	NNP	Heywood	PERSON
98	2	Sullivan	NNP	Sullivan	PERSON
98	3	,	,	,	O
98	4	Kansas	NNP	Kansas	LOCATION
98	5	City	NNP	City	LOCATION
98	6	catcher	NN	catcher	O
98	7	,	,	,	O
98	8	singled	VBD	single	O
98	9	up	RP	up	O
98	10	the	DT	the	O
98	11	middle	NN	middle	O
98	12	and	CC	and	O
98	13	Throneberry	NNP	Throneberry	PERSON
98	14	was	VBD	be	O
98	15	across	IN	across	O
98	16	with	IN	with	O
98	17	what	WP	what	O
98	18	proved	VBD	prove	O
98	19	to	TO	to	O
98	20	be	VB	be	O
98	21	the	DT	the	O
98	22	winning	VBG	win	O
98	23	run	NN	run	O
98	24	.	.	.	O

1	4	homeLocation

99	0	Rookie	NNP	Rookie	O
99	1	southpaw	NN	southpaw	O
99	2	George	NNP	George	PERSON
99	3	Stepanovich	NNP	Stepanovich	PERSON
99	4	relieved	VBD	relieve	O
99	5	Hyde	NNP	Hyde	PERSON
99	6	at	IN	at	O
99	7	the	DT	the	O
99	8	start	NN	start	O
99	9	of	IN	of	O
99	10	the	DT	the	O
99	11	ninth	JJ	ninth	O
99	12	and	CC	and	O
99	13	gave	VBD	give	O
99	14	up	RP	up	O
99	15	the	DT	the	O
99	16	A's	NNP	A's	O
99	17	fifth	MD	fifth	O
99	18	tally	RB	tally	O
99	19	on	IN	on	O
99	20	a	DT	a	O
99	21	walk	NN	walk	O
99	22	to	TO	to	O
99	23	second	JJ	second	O
99	24	baseman	NN	baseman	O
99	25	Dick	NNP	Dick	PERSON
99	26	Howser	NNP	Howser	PERSON
99	27	,	,	,	O
99	28	a	DT	a	O
99	29	wild	JJ	wild	O
99	30	pitch	NN	pitch	O
99	31	,	,	,	O
99	32	and	CC	and	O
99	33	Frank	NNP	Frank	O
99	34	Cipriani's	NNP	Cipriani's	O
99	35	single	JJ	single	O
99	36	under	IN	under	O
99	37	Shortstop	NNP	Shortstop	O
99	38	Jerry	NNP	Jerry	O
99	39	Adair's	NNP	Adair's	O
99	40	glove	VB	glove	O
99	41	into	IN	into	O
99	42	center	NN	center	O
99	43	.	.	.	O


100	0	Three	CD	Three	O
100	1	were	VBD	be	O
100	2	doubles	NNS	double	O
100	3	,	,	,	O
100	4	Brooks	NNP	Brooks	PERSON
100	5	Robinson	NNP	Robinson	PERSON
100	6	getting	VBG	get	O
100	7	a	DT	a	O
100	8	pair	NN	pair	O
100	9	and	CC	and	O
100	10	Marv	NNP	Marv	PERSON
100	11	Breeding	NNP	Breeding	PERSON
100	12	one	CD	one	O
100	13	.	.	.	O


101	0	Bill	NNP	Bill	PERSON
101	1	Kunkel	NNP	Kunkel	PERSON
101	2	,	,	,	O
101	3	Bob	NNP	Bob	PERSON
101	4	Hartman	NNP	Hartman	PERSON
101	5	and	CC	and	O
101	6	Ed	NNP	Ed	PERSON
101	7	Keegan	NNP	Keegan	PERSON
101	8	did	VBD	do	O
101	9	the	DT	the	O
101	10	mound	NN	mound	O
101	11	chores	VBZ	chores	O
101	12	for	IN	for	O
101	13	the	DT	the	O
101	14	club	NN	club	O
101	15	down	RP	down	O
101	16	from	IN	from	O
101	17	West	NNP	West	LOCATION
101	18	Palm	NNP	Palm	LOCATION
101	19	Beach	NNP	Beach	LOCATION
101	20	to	TO	to	O
101	21	play	VB	play	O
101	22	the	DT	the	O
101	23	game	NN	game	O
101	24	before	IN	before	O
101	25	767	CD	767	O
101	26	paying	VBG	pay	O
101	27	customers	NNS	customer	O
101	28	in	IN	in	O
101	29	Miami	NNP	Miami	LOCATION
101	30	Stadium	NNP	Stadium	LOCATION
101	31	.	.	.	O

0	3	colleague
0	6	colleague
3	6	colleague

102	0	The	DT	The	O
102	1	Birds	NNP	Birds	O
102	2	got	VBD	get	O
102	3	five	CD	five	O
102	4	hits	NNS	hit	O
102	5	and	CC	and	O
102	6	all	DT	all	O
102	7	three	CD	three	O
102	8	of	IN	of	O
102	9	their	PRP$	their	O
102	10	runs	NNS	run	O
102	11	off	IN	off	O
102	12	Kunkel	NNP	Kunkel	PERSON
102	13	before	IN	before	O
102	14	Hartman	NNP	Hartman	PERSON
102	15	took	VBD	take	O
102	16	over	RP	over	O
102	17	in	IN	in	O
102	18	the	DT	the	O
102	19	top	NN	top	O
102	20	of	IN	of	O
102	21	the	DT	the	O
102	22	fourth	JJ	fourth	O
102	23	.	.	.	O


103	0	Whitey	NNP	Whitey	PERSON
103	1	Herzog	NNP	Herzog	PERSON
103	2	,	,	,	O
103	3	performing	VBG	perform	O
103	4	in	IN	in	O
103	5	right	NN	right	O
103	6	as	IN	a	O
103	7	the	DT	the	O
103	8	Orioles	NNP	Orioles	ORGANIZATION
103	9	fielded	VBD	field	O
103	10	possibly	RB	possibly	O
103	11	their	PRP$	their	O
103	12	strongest	JJS	strong	O
103	13	team	NN	team	O
103	14	of	IN	of	O
103	15	the	DT	the	O
103	16	spring	NN	spring	O
103	17	,	,	,	O
103	18	worked	VBD	work	O
103	19	Keegan	NNP	Keegan	PERSON
103	20	for	IN	for	O
103	21	a	DT	a	O
103	22	base	NN	base	O
103	23	on	IN	on	O
103	24	balls	NNS	ball	O
103	25	.	.	.	O

8	0	employee

104	0	Pete	NNP	Pete	PERSON
104	1	Ward	NNP	Ward	PERSON
104	2	was	VBD	be	O
104	3	sent	VBN	send	O
104	4	in	IN	in	O
104	5	for	IN	for	O
104	6	House	NNP	House	ORGANIZATION
104	7	and	CC	and	O
104	8	,	,	,	O
104	9	after	IN	after	O
104	10	failing	VBG	fail	O
104	11	in	IN	in	O
104	12	a	DT	a	O
104	13	bunt	NN	bunt	O
104	14	attempt	NN	attempt	O
104	15	,	,	,	O
104	16	popped	VBD	pop	O
104	17	to	TO	to	O
104	18	Howser	NNP	Howser	PERSON
104	19	on	IN	on	O
104	20	the	DT	the	O
104	21	grass	NN	grass	O
104	22	back	RB	back	O
104	23	of	IN	of	O
104	24	short	JJ	short	O
104	25	.	.	.	O


105	0	John	NNP	John	PERSON
105	1	Powell	NNP	Powell	PERSON
105	2	,	,	,	O
105	3	batting	VBG	bat	O
105	4	for	IN	for	O
105	5	Adair	NNP	Adair	PERSON
105	6	,	,	,	O
105	7	fanned	VBD	fan	O
105	8	after	IN	after	O
105	9	fouling	VBG	foul	O
105	10	off	RP	off	O
105	11	two	CD	two	O
105	12	2-and-2	JJ	2-and-2	O
105	13	pitches	NNS	pitch	O
105	14	,	,	,	O
105	15	and	CC	and	O
105	16	Buddy	NNP	Buddy	PERSON
105	17	Barker	NNP	Barker	PERSON
105	18	,	,	,	O
105	19	up	RB	up	O
105	20	for	IN	for	O
105	21	Stepanovich	NNP	Stepanovich	PERSON
105	22	,	,	,	O
105	23	bounced	VBD	bounce	O
105	24	out	RP	out	O
105	25	sharply	RB	sharply	O
105	26	to	TO	to	O
105	27	Jerry	NNP	Jerry	PERSON
105	28	Lumpe	NNP	Lumpe	PERSON
105	29	at	IN	at	O
105	30	second	NN	second	O
105	31	to	TO	to	O
105	32	end	VB	end	O
105	33	the	DT	the	O
105	34	2-hour-and-27-minute	JJ	2-hour-and-27-minute	O
105	35	contest	NN	contest	O
105	36	.	.	.	O

0	5	colleague
16	21	colleague
16	27	colleague
21	27	colleague

106	0	The	DT	The	O
106	1	Orioles	NNP	Orioles	ORGANIZATION
106	2	got	VBD	get	O
106	3	a	DT	a	O
106	4	run	NN	run	O
106	5	in	IN	in	O
106	6	the	DT	the	O
106	7	first	JJ	first	O
106	8	inning	NN	inning	O
106	9	when	WRB	when	O
106	10	Breeding	NNP	Breeding	O
106	11	,	,	,	O
106	12	along	IN	along	O
106	13	with	IN	with	O
106	14	Robinson	NNP	Robinson	PERSON
106	15	,	,	,	O
106	16	the	DT	the	O
106	17	two	CD	two	O
106	18	Birds	NNS	Birds	O
106	19	who	WP	who	O
106	20	got	VBD	get	O
106	21	a	DT	a	O
106	22	pair	NN	pair	O
106	23	of	IN	of	O
106	24	hits	NNS	hit	O
106	25	,	,	,	O
106	26	doubled	VBD	double	O
106	27	to	TO	to	O
106	28	right	VB	right	O
106	29	center	NN	center	O
106	30	,	,	,	O
106	31	moved	VBD	move	O
106	32	to	TO	to	O
106	33	third	VB	third	O
106	34	on	IN	on	O
106	35	Russ	NNP	Russ	PERSON
106	36	Snyder's	NNP	Snyder's	O
106	37	single	JJ	single	O
106	38	to	TO	to	O
106	39	right	JJ	right	O
106	40	and	CC	and	O
106	41	crossed	VBN	cross	O
106	42	on	IN	on	O
106	43	Kunkel's	NNP	Kunkel's	O
106	44	wild	JJ	wild	O
106	45	pitch	NN	pitch	O
106	46	into	IN	into	O
106	47	the	DT	the	O
106	48	dirt	NN	dirt	O
106	49	in	IN	in	O
106	50	front	NN	front	O
106	51	of	IN	of	O
106	52	the	DT	the	O
106	53	plate	NN	plate	O
106	54	.	.	.	O


107	0	Jim	NNP	Jim	PERSON
107	1	Gentile	NNP	Gentile	PERSON
107	2	bounced	VBD	bounce	O
107	3	a	DT	a	O
107	4	hard	JJ	hard	O
107	5	shot	NN	shot	O
107	6	off	IN	off	O
107	7	Kunkel's	NNP	Kunkel's	O
107	8	glove	NN	glove	O
107	9	and	CC	and	O
107	10	beat	VB	beat	O
107	11	it	PRP	it	O
107	12	out	RP	out	O
107	13	for	IN	for	O
107	14	a	DT	a	O
107	15	single	JJ	single	O
107	16	,	,	,	O
107	17	and	CC	and	O
107	18	when	WRB	when	O
107	19	Lumpe	NNP	Lumpe	PERSON
107	20	grabbed	VBD	grab	O
107	21	the	DT	the	O
107	22	ball	NN	ball	O
107	23	and	CC	and	O
107	24	threw	VBD	throw	O
107	25	it	PRP	it	O
107	26	over	RP	over	O
107	27	first	JJ	first	O
107	28	baseman	NN	baseman	O
107	29	Throneberry's	NNP	Throneberry's	O
107	30	head	NN	head	O
107	31	Brandt	NNP	Brandt	PERSON
107	32	took	VBD	take	O
107	33	third	JJ	third	O
107	34	and	CC	and	O
107	35	Gentile	NNP	Gentile	PERSON
107	36	second	VBP	second	O
107	37	on	IN	on	O
107	38	the	DT	the	O
107	39	error	NN	error	O
107	40	.	.	.	O

31	35	colleague

108	0	When	WRB	When	O
108	1	Robinson	NNP	Robinson	PERSON
108	2	tried	VBD	try	O
108	3	to	TO	to	O
108	4	stretch	VB	stretch	O
108	5	his	PRP$	his	O
108	6	blow	NN	blow	O
108	7	into	IN	into	O
108	8	a	DT	a	O
108	9	triple	NN	triple	O
108	10	,	,	,	O
108	11	he	PRP	he	O
108	12	was	VBD	be	O
108	13	cut	VBN	cut	O
108	14	down	RP	down	O
108	15	in	IN	in	O
108	16	a	DT	a	O
108	17	close	JJ	close	O
108	18	play	NN	play	O
108	19	at	IN	at	O
108	20	third	JJ	third	O
108	21	,	,	,	O
108	22	Tuttle	NNP	Tuttle	PERSON
108	23	to	TO	to	O
108	24	Andy	NNP	Andy	PERSON
108	25	Carey	NNP	Carey	PERSON
108	26	.	.	.	O

22	24	colleague

109	0	Lumpe	NNP	Lumpe	PERSON
109	1	worked	VBD	work	O
109	2	a	DT	a	O
109	3	walk	NN	walk	O
109	4	as	IN	a	O
109	5	the	DT	the	O
109	6	first	JJ	first	O
109	7	batter	NN	batter	O
109	8	to	TO	to	O
109	9	face	VB	face	O
109	10	Hyde	NNP	Hyde	PERSON
109	11	and	CC	and	O
109	12	romped	VBD	romp	O
109	13	around	RB	around	O
109	14	as	IN	a	O
109	15	Siebern	NNP	Siebern	PERSON
109	16	blasted	VBD	blast	O
109	17	Hyde's	NNP	Hyde's	O
109	18	next	JJ	next	O
109	19	toss	NN	toss	O
109	20	415	CD	415	O
109	21	feet	NNS	foot	O
109	22	over	IN	over	O
109	23	the	DT	the	O
109	24	scoreboard	NN	scoreboard	O
109	25	in	IN	in	O
109	26	right	JJ	right	O
109	27	center	NN	center	O
109	28	.	.	.	O

0	10	colleague
0	15	colleague
10	15	colleague

110	0	Carey	NNP	Carey	PERSON
110	1	singled	VBD	single	O
110	2	on	IN	on	O
110	3	a	DT	a	O
110	4	slow-bouncing	JJ	slow-bouncing	O
110	5	ball	NN	ball	O
110	6	to	TO	to	O
110	7	short	VB	short	O
110	8	which	WDT	which	O
110	9	Robinson	NNP	Robinson	PERSON
110	10	cut	VBD	cut	O
110	11	across	IN	across	O
110	12	to	TO	to	O
110	13	field	NN	field	O
110	14	and	CC	and	O
110	15	threw	VBD	throw	O
110	16	wide	JJ	wide	O
110	17	to	TO	to	O
110	18	first	JJ	first	O
110	19	.	.	.	O

0	9	colleague

111	0	Breeding	VBG	Breeding	O
111	1	to	TO	to	O
111	2	Adair	NNP	Adair	PERSON
111	3	to	TO	to	O
111	4	Gentile	NNP	Gentile	PERSON
111	5	,	,	,	O
111	6	setting	VBG	set	O
111	7	up	RP	up	O
111	8	Tuttle's	NNP	Tuttle's	O
111	9	390-foot	JJ	390-foot	O
111	10	homer	NN	homer	O
111	11	over	IN	over	O
111	12	the	DT	the	O
111	13	wall	NN	wall	O
111	14	in	IN	in	O
111	15	left	JJ	left	O
111	16	center	NN	center	O
111	17	.	.	.	O

2	4	colleague

112	0	Skinny	NNP	Skinny	PERSON
112	1	Brown	NNP	Brown	PERSON
112	2	and	CC	and	O
112	3	Hoyt	NNP	Hoyt	PERSON
112	4	Wilhelm	NNP	Wilhelm	PERSON
112	5	,	,	,	O
112	6	the	DT	the	O
112	7	Flock's	NNP	Flock's	O
112	8	veteran	NN	veteran	O
112	9	knuckleball	NN	knuckleball	O
112	10	specialists	NNS	specialist	O
112	11	,	,	,	O
112	12	are	VBP	be	O
112	13	slated	VBN	slat	O
112	14	to	TO	to	O
112	15	oppose	VB	oppose	O
112	16	the	DT	the	O
112	17	American	NNP	American	O
112	18	League	NNP	League	O
112	19	champions	NNS	champion	O
112	20	in	IN	in	O
112	21	tomorrow's	NN	tomorrow's	O
112	22	8	CD	8	O
112	23	P.M.	NNP	P.M.	O
112	24	contest	NN	contest	O
112	25	.	.	.	O

0	3	colleague

114	0	Ryne	NNP	Ryne	PERSON
114	1	Duren	NNP	Duren	PERSON
114	2	and	CC	and	O
114	3	Roland	NNP	Roland	PERSON
114	4	Sheldon	NNP	Sheldon	PERSON
114	5	,	,	,	O
114	6	a	DT	a	O
114	7	rookie	NN	rookie	O
114	8	righthander	NN	righthander	O
114	9	who	WP	who	O
114	10	posted	VBD	post	O
114	11	a	DT	a	O
114	12	15-1	JJ	15-1	O
114	13	record	NN	record	O
114	14	last	JJ	last	O
114	15	year	NN	year	O
114	16	for	IN	for	O
114	17	the	DT	the	O
114	18	Yanks'	NNP	Yanks'	O
114	19	Auburn	NNP	Auburn	O
114	20	(	(	(	O
114	21	N.Y.	NNP	N.Y.	LOCATION
114	22	)	)	)	O
114	23	farm	NN	farm	O
114	24	club	NN	club	O
114	25	of	IN	of	O
114	26	the	DT	the	O
114	27	Class-D	NNP	Class-D	O
114	28	New	NNP	New	ORGANIZATION
114	29	York-Pennsylvania	NNP	York-Pennsylvania	ORGANIZATION
114	30	League	NNP	League	ORGANIZATION
114	31	,	,	,	O
114	32	are	VBP	be	O
114	33	the	DT	the	O
114	34	probable	JJ	probable	O
114	35	rival	JJ	rival	O
114	36	pitchers	NNS	pitcher	O
114	37	.	.	.	O

0	3	colleague

115	0	Twenty-one-year-old	JJ	Twenty-one-year-old	O
115	1	Milt	NNP	Milt	PERSON
115	2	Pappas	NNP	Pappas	PERSON
115	3	and	CC	and	O
115	4	Jerry	NNP	Jerry	PERSON
115	5	Walker	NNP	Walker	PERSON
115	6	,	,	,	O
115	7	22	CD	22	O
115	8	,	,	,	O
115	9	are	VBP	be	O
115	10	scheduled	VBN	schedule	O
115	11	to	TO	to	O
115	12	share	NN	share	O
115	13	the	DT	the	O
115	14	Oriole	NNP	Oriole	LOCATION
115	15	mound	NN	mound	O
115	16	chores	NNS	chore	O
115	17	against	IN	against	O
115	18	the	DT	the	O
115	19	Bombers'	NNP	Bombers'	O
115	20	Art	NNP	Art	O
115	21	Ditmar	NNP	Ditmar	O
115	22	in	IN	in	O
115	23	Sunday's	NNP	Sunday's	O
115	24	2	CD	2	O
115	25	P.M.	NNP	P.M.	O
115	26	encounter	NN	encounter	O
115	27	.	.	.	O

1	4	colleague

116	0	Ralph	NNP	Ralph	PERSON
116	1	Houk	NNP	Houk	PERSON
116	2	,	,	,	O
116	3	successor	NN	successor	O
116	4	to	TO	to	O
116	5	Casey	NNP	Casey	PERSON
116	6	Stengel	NNP	Stengel	PERSON
116	7	at	IN	at	O
116	8	the	DT	the	O
116	9	Yankee	NNP	Yankee	ORGANIZATION
116	10	helm	NN	helm	O
116	11	,	,	,	O
116	12	plans	VBZ	plan	O
116	13	to	TO	to	O
116	14	bring	VB	bring	O
116	15	the	DT	the	O
116	16	entire	JJ	entire	O
116	17	New	NNP	New	LOCATION
116	18	York	NNP	York	LOCATION
116	19	squad	NN	squad	O
116	20	here	RB	here	O
116	21	from	IN	from	O
116	22	St.	NNP	St.	LOCATION
116	23	Petersburg	NNP	Petersburg	LOCATION
116	24	,	,	,	O
116	25	including	VBG	include	O
116	26	Joe	NNP	Joe	PERSON
116	27	Dimaggio	NNP	Dimaggio	PERSON
116	28	and	CC	and	O
116	29	large	JJ	large	O
116	30	crowds	NNS	crowd	O
116	31	are	VBP	be	O
116	32	anticipated	VBN	anticipate	O
116	33	for	IN	for	O
116	34	both	DT	both	O
116	35	weekend	NN	weekend	O
116	36	games	NNS	game	O
116	37	.	.	.	O

0	5	colleague
9	0	employee
9	5	employee
26	22	homeLocation

117	0	``	``	``	O
117	1	Take	VB	Take	O
117	2	a	DT	a	O
117	3	ride	NN	ride	O
117	4	on	IN	on	O
117	5	this	DT	this	O
117	6	one	NN	one	O
117	7	''	''	''	O
117	8	,	,	,	O
117	9	Brooks	NNP	Brooks	PERSON
117	10	Robinson	NNP	Robinson	PERSON
117	11	greeted	VBD	greet	O
117	12	Hansen	NNP	Hansen	PERSON
117	13	as	IN	a	O
117	14	the	DT	the	O
117	15	Bird	NNP	Bird	O
117	16	third	JJ	third	O
117	17	sacker	NN	sacker	O
117	18	grabbed	VBD	grab	O
117	19	a	DT	a	O
117	20	bat	NN	bat	O
117	21	,	,	,	O
117	22	headed	VBN	head	O
117	23	for	IN	for	O
117	24	the	DT	the	O
117	25	plate	NN	plate	O
117	26	and	CC	and	O
117	27	bounced	VBD	bounce	O
117	28	a	DT	a	O
117	29	third-inning	JJ	third-inning	O
117	30	two-run	JJ	two-run	O
117	31	double	NN	double	O
117	32	off	IN	off	O
117	33	the	DT	the	O
117	34	left-centerfield	JJ	left-centerfield	O
117	35	wall	NN	wall	O
117	36	tonight	NN	tonight	O
117	37	.	.	.	O

9	12	colleague

118	0	Hansen	NNP	Hansen	PERSON
118	1	arrived	VBD	arrive	O
118	2	just	RB	just	O
118	3	before	IN	before	O
118	4	nightfall	JJ	nightfall	O
118	5	,	,	,	O
118	6	two	CD	two	O
118	7	hours	NNS	hour	O
118	8	late	JJ	late	O
118	9	,	,	,	O
118	10	in	IN	in	O
118	11	company	NN	company	O
118	12	with	IN	with	O
118	13	Lee	NNP	Lee	PERSON
118	14	MacPhail	NNP	MacPhail	PERSON
118	15	;	:	;	O
118	16	;	:	;	O


119	0	J.	NNP	J.	PERSON
119	1	A.	NN	A.	PERSON
119	2	W.	NNP	W.	PERSON
119	3	Iglehart	NNP	Iglehart	PERSON
119	4	,	,	,	O
119	5	chairman	NN	chairman	O
119	6	of	IN	of	O
119	7	the	DT	the	O
119	8	Oriole	NNP	Oriole	ORGANIZATION
119	9	board	NN	board	O
119	10	of	IN	of	O
119	11	directors	NNS	director	O
119	12	,	,	,	O
119	13	and	CC	and	O
119	14	Public	NNP	Public	O
119	15	Relations	NNP	Relations	O
119	16	Director	NNP	Director	O
119	17	Jack	NNP	Jack	PERSON
119	18	Dunn	NNP	Dunn	PERSON
119	19	.	.	.	O

8	0	employee

120	0	Richard	NNP	Richard	PERSON
120	1	M.	NNP	M.	PERSON
120	2	Forbes's	NNP	Forbes's	PERSON
120	3	Paget	NNP	Paget	PERSON
120	4	,	,	,	O
120	5	which	WDT	which	O
120	6	had	VBD	have	O
120	7	what	WP	what	O
120	8	seemed	VBD	seem	O
120	9	to	TO	to	O
120	10	be	VB	be	O
120	11	a	DT	a	O
120	12	substantial	JJ	substantial	O
120	13	lead	NN	lead	O
120	14	in	IN	in	O
120	15	the	DT	the	O
120	16	early	JJ	early	O
120	17	stages	NNS	stage	O
120	18	,	,	,	O
120	19	tired	VBD	tire	O
120	20	rapidly	RB	rapidly	O
120	21	nearing	VBG	near	O
120	22	the	DT	the	O
120	23	wire	NN	wire	O
120	24	and	CC	and	O
120	25	was	VBD	be	O
120	26	able	JJ	able	O
120	27	to	TO	to	O
120	28	save	VB	save	O
120	29	place	NN	place	O
120	30	money	NN	money	O
120	31	only	RB	only	O
120	32	a	DT	a	O
120	33	head	NN	head	O
120	34	in	IN	in	O
120	35	front	NN	front	O
120	36	of	IN	of	O
120	37	Glen	NNP	Glen	PERSON
120	38	T.	NNP	T.	O
120	39	Hallowell's	NNP	Hallowell's	O
120	40	Milties	NNP	Milties	O
120	41	Miss	NNP	Miss	O
120	42	.	.	.	O


121	0	--	:	--	O
121	1	George	NNP	George	PERSON
121	2	Kerr	NNP	Kerr	PERSON
121	3	,	,	,	O
121	4	the	DT	the	O
121	5	swift-striding	JJ	swift-striding	O
121	6	Jamaican	NNP	Jamaican	O
121	7	,	,	,	O
121	8	set	VBD	set	O
121	9	a	DT	a	O
121	10	meet	NN	meet	O
121	11	record	NN	record	O
121	12	in	IN	in	O
121	13	the	DT	the	O
121	14	600-yard	JJ	600-yard	O
121	15	run	NN	run	O
121	16	in	IN	in	O
121	17	the	DT	the	O
121	18	Knights	NNP	Knights	O
121	19	of	IN	of	O
121	20	Columbus	NNP	Columbus	LOCATION
121	21	track	NNP	track	O
121	22	meet	NN	meet	O
121	23	tonight	NN	tonight	O
121	24	,	,	,	O
121	25	beating	VBG	beat	O
121	26	Purdue's	NNP	Purdue's	O
121	27	Dave	NNP	Dave	PERSON
121	28	Mills	NNP	Mills	PERSON
121	29	in	IN	in	O
121	30	a	DT	a	O
121	31	hot	JJ	hot	O
121	32	duel	NN	duel	O
121	33	in	IN	in	O
121	34	1.10.1	CD	1.10.1	O
121	35	.	.	.	O


1	6	homeLocation

123	0	``	``	``	O
123	1	This	DT	This	O
123	2	year	NN	year	O
123	3	,	,	,	O
123	4	coach	NN	coach	O
123	5	Royal	NNP	Royal	PERSON
123	6	told	VBD	tell	O
123	7	me	PRP	me	O
123	8	if	IN	if	O
123	9	I'd	NNP	I'd	O
123	10	work	NN	work	O
123	11	on	IN	on	O
123	12	my	PRP$	my	O
123	13	place-kicking	NN	place-kicking	O
123	14	he	PRP	he	O
123	15	thought	VBD	think	O
123	16	he	PRP	he	O
123	17	could	MD	could	O
123	18	use	VB	use	O
123	19	me	PRP	me	O
123	20	''	''	''	O
123	21	,	,	,	O
123	22	said	VBD	say	O
123	23	Moritz	NNP	Moritz	PERSON
123	24	.	.	.	O


124	0	Meek	NNS	Meek	PERSON
124	1	expressed	VBD	express	O
124	2	particular	JJ	particular	O
124	3	gratification	NN	gratification	O
124	4	at	IN	at	O
124	5	the	DT	the	O
124	6	defensive	JJ	defensive	O
124	7	performances	NNS	performance	O
124	8	of	IN	of	O
124	9	end	NN	end	O
124	10	Happy	NNP	Happy	O
124	11	Nelson	NNP	Nelson	PERSON
124	12	and	CC	and	O
124	13	halfback	VB	halfback	O
124	14	Billy	NNP	Billy	PERSON
124	15	Gannon	NNP	Gannon	PERSON
124	16	.	.	.	O

11	14	colleague

125	0	``	``	``	O
125	1	Nelson	NNP	Nelson	PERSON
125	2	played	VBD	play	O
125	3	magnificent	NN	magnificent	O
125	4	football	NN	football	O
125	5	''	''	''	O
125	6	,	,	,	O
125	7	Meek	NNP	Meek	PERSON
125	8	praised	VBD	praise	O
125	9	.	.	.	O


126	0	``	``	``	O
126	1	As	RB	As	O
126	2	soon	RB	soon	O
126	3	as	IN	a	O
126	4	it	PRP	it	O
126	5	started	VBD	start	O
126	6	to	TO	to	O
126	7	form	VB	form	O
126	8	,	,	,	O
126	9	Gannon	NNP	Gannon	PERSON
126	10	spotted	VBD	spot	O
126	11	it	PRP	it	O
126	12	''	''	''	O
126	13	,	,	,	O
126	14	Meek	NNP	Meek	PERSON
126	15	said	VBD	say	O
126	16	.	.	.	O


127	0	The	DT	The	O
127	1	Air	NNP	Air	O
127	2	Force's	NNP	Force's	O
127	3	,	,	,	O
127	4	and	CC	and	O
127	5	the	DT	the	O
127	6	game's	NN	game's	O
127	7	,	,	,	O
127	8	final	JJ	final	O
127	9	play	NN	play	O
127	10	,	,	,	O
127	11	was	VBD	be	O
127	12	a	DT	a	O
127	13	long	JJ	long	O
127	14	pass	NN	pas	O
127	15	by	IN	by	O
127	16	quarterback	NN	quarterback	O
127	17	Bob	NNP	Bob	PERSON
127	18	McNaughton	NNP	McNaughton	PERSON
127	19	which	WDT	which	O
127	20	Gannon	NNP	Gannon	PERSON
127	21	intercepted	VBD	intercept	O
127	22	on	IN	on	O
127	23	his	PRP$	his	O
127	24	own	JJ	own	O
127	25	44	CD	44	O
127	26	and	CC	and	O
127	27	returned	VBD	return	O
127	28	22	CD	22	O
127	29	yards	NNS	yard	O
127	30	.	.	.	O

17	20	colleague

128	0	Except	IN	Except	O
128	1	for	IN	for	O
128	2	sophomore	NN	sophomore	O
128	3	center	NN	center	O
128	4	Mike	NNP	Mike	PERSON
128	5	Kelsey	NNP	Kelsey	PERSON
128	6	and	CC	and	O
128	7	fullback	NN	fullback	O
128	8	Mike	NNP	Mike	PERSON
128	9	Rice	NNP	Rice	PERSON
128	10	,	,	,	O
128	11	Meek	NNP	Meek	PERSON
128	12	expects	VBZ	expect	O
128	13	the	DT	the	O
128	14	squad	NN	squad	O
128	15	to	TO	to	O
128	16	be	VB	be	O
128	17	physically	RB	physically	O
128	18	sound	JJ	sound	O
128	19	for	IN	for	O
128	20	Rice	NNP	Rice	PERSON
128	21	.	.	.	O

4	8	colleague

129	0	End	NN	End	O
129	1	Gene	NNP	Gene	PERSON
129	2	Raesz	NNP	Raesz	PERSON
129	3	,	,	,	O
129	4	who	WP	who	O
129	5	broke	VBD	break	O
129	6	a	DT	a	O
129	7	hand	NN	hand	O
129	8	in	IN	in	O
129	9	the	DT	the	O
129	10	Owl's	NNP	Owl's	O
129	11	game	NN	game	O
129	12	with	IN	with	O
129	13	LSU	NNP	LSU	ORGANIZATION
129	14	,	,	,	O
129	15	was	VBD	be	O
129	16	back	RB	back	O
129	17	working	VBG	work	O
129	18	out	RP	out	O
129	19	with	IN	with	O
129	20	Rice	NNP	Rice	O
129	21	Monday	NNP	Monday	O
129	22	,	,	,	O
129	23	and	CC	and	O
129	24	John	NNP	John	PERSON
129	25	Nichols	NNP	Nichols	PERSON
129	26	,	,	,	O
129	27	sophomore	RB	sophomore	O
129	28	guard	NN	guard	O
129	29	,	,	,	O
129	30	moved	VBD	move	O
129	31	back	RB	back	O
129	32	into	IN	into	O
129	33	action	NN	action	O
129	34	after	IN	after	O
129	35	a	DT	a	O
129	36	week's	JJ	week's	O
129	37	idleness	NN	idleness	O
129	38	with	IN	with	O
129	39	an	DT	an	O
129	40	ankle	JJ	ankle	O
129	41	injury	NN	injury	O
129	42	.	.	.	O


130	0	The	DT	The	O
130	1	Texas	NNP	Texas	ORGANIZATION
130	2	Aggies	NNP	Aggies	ORGANIZATION
130	3	got	VBD	get	O
130	4	a	DT	a	O
130	5	day	NN	day	O
130	6	off	IN	off	O
130	7	Monday	NNP	Monday	O
130	8	--	:	--	O
130	9	a	DT	a	O
130	10	special	JJ	special	O
130	11	gift	NN	gift	O
130	12	from	IN	from	O
130	13	Coach	NNP	Coach	O
130	14	Jim	NNP	Jim	PERSON
130	15	Myers	NNP	Myers	PERSON
130	16	for	IN	for	O
130	17	its	PRP$	it	O
130	18	conference	NN	conference	O
130	19	victory	NN	victory	O
130	20	last	JJ	last	O
130	21	Saturday	NNP	Saturday	O
130	22	night	NN	night	O
130	23	,	,	,	O
130	24	but	CC	but	O
130	25	Myers	NNP	Myers	PERSON
130	26	announced	VBD	announce	O
130	27	that	IN	that	O
130	28	halfback	NN	halfback	O
130	29	George	NNP	George	PERSON
130	30	Hargett	NNP	Hargett	PERSON
130	31	,	,	,	O
130	32	shaken	VBD	shake	O
130	33	up	RP	up	O
130	34	in	IN	in	O
130	35	the	DT	the	O
130	36	Tech	NNP	Tech	O
130	37	game	NN	game	O
130	38	,	,	,	O
130	39	would	MD	would	O
130	40	not	RB	not	O
130	41	play	VB	play	O
130	42	against	IN	against	O
130	43	Trinity	NNP	Trinity	ORGANIZATION
130	44	Saturday	NNP	Saturday	O
130	45	.	.	.	O

1	14	employee

131	0	Buffalo	NNP	Buffalo	ORGANIZATION
131	1	coach	NN	coach	O
131	2	Buster	NNP	Buster	PERSON
131	3	Ramsey	NNP	Ramsey	PERSON
131	4	,	,	,	O
131	5	who	WP	who	O
131	6	has	VBZ	have	O
131	7	become	VBN	become	O
131	8	one	CD	one	O
131	9	of	IN	of	O
131	10	the	DT	the	O
131	11	game's	NN	game's	O
131	12	greatest	JJS	great	O
131	13	collectors	NNS	collector	O
131	14	of	IN	of	O
131	15	quarterbacks	NNS	quarterback	O
131	16	,	,	,	O
131	17	apparently	RB	apparently	O
131	18	now	RB	now	O
131	19	has	VBZ	have	O
131	20	found	VBN	find	O
131	21	a	DT	a	O
131	22	productive	JJ	productive	O
131	23	pair	NN	pair	O
131	24	in	IN	in	O
131	25	two	CD	two	O
131	26	ex-National	JJ	ex-National	O
131	27	Football	NNP	Football	ORGANIZATION
131	28	Leaguers	NNP	Leaguers	ORGANIZATION
131	29	,	,	,	O
131	30	M.	NNP	M.	PERSON
131	31	C.	NNP	C.	PERSON
131	32	Reynolds	NNP	Reynolds	PERSON
131	33	and	CC	and	O
131	34	Warren	NNP	Warren	PERSON
131	35	Rabb	NNP	Rabb	PERSON
131	36	.	.	.	O

0	2	employee
30	34	colleague

132	0	Ramsey	NNP	Ramsey	PERSON
132	1	has	VBZ	have	O
132	2	a	DT	a	O
132	3	thing	NN	thing	O
132	4	or	CC	or	O
132	5	two	CD	two	O
132	6	to	TO	to	O
132	7	mutter	VB	mutter	O
132	8	about	IN	about	O
132	9	himself	PRP	himself	O
132	10	,	,	,	O
132	11	for	IN	for	O
132	12	the	DT	the	O
132	13	Dallas	NNP	Dallas	LOCATION
132	14	defensive	JJ	defensive	O
132	15	unit	NN	unit	O
132	16	turned	VBD	turn	O
132	17	in	IN	in	O
132	18	another	DT	another	O
132	19	splendid	JJ	splendid	O
132	20	effort	NN	effort	O
132	21	against	IN	against	O
132	22	Denver	NNP	Denver	LOCATION
132	23	,	,	,	O
132	24	and	CC	and	O
132	25	the	DT	the	O
132	26	Texans	NNPS	Texans	O
132	27	were	VBD	be	O
132	28	able	JJ	able	O
132	29	to	TO	to	O
132	30	whip	VB	whip	O
132	31	the	DT	the	O
132	32	dangerous	JJ	dangerous	O
132	33	Broncs	NNP	Broncs	O
132	34	without	IN	without	O
132	35	the	DT	the	O
132	36	fullbacking	NN	fullbacking	O
132	37	of	IN	of	O
132	38	a	DT	a	O
132	39	top	JJ	top	O
132	40	star	NN	star	O
132	41	,	,	,	O
132	42	Jack	NNP	Jack	PERSON
132	43	Spikes	NNP	Spikes	PERSON
132	44	,	,	,	O
132	45	though	IN	though	O
132	46	he	PRP	he	O
132	47	did	VBD	do	O
132	48	the	DT	the	O
132	49	team's	NN	team's	O
132	50	place-kicking	NN	place-kicking	O
132	51	while	IN	while	O
132	52	nursing	VBG	nurse	O
132	53	a	DT	a	O
132	54	knee	JJ	knee	O
132	55	injury	NN	injury	O
132	56	.	.	.	O


133	0	The	DT	The	O
133	1	Texans	NNPS	Texans	O
133	2	made	VBD	make	O
133	3	themselves	PRP	themselves	O
133	4	a	DT	a	O
133	5	comforting	VBG	comfort	O
133	6	break	NN	break	O
133	7	on	IN	on	O
133	8	the	DT	the	O
133	9	opening	NN	opening	O
133	10	kickoff	NN	kickoff	O
133	11	when	WRB	when	O
133	12	Denver's	NNP	Denver's	O
133	13	Al	NNP	Al	PERSON
133	14	Carmichael	NNP	Carmichael	PERSON
133	15	was	VBD	be	O
133	16	jarred	VBN	jar	O
133	17	loose	RB	loose	O
133	18	from	IN	from	O
133	19	the	DT	the	O
133	20	ball	NN	ball	O
133	21	when	WRB	when	O
133	22	Dave	NNP	Dave	PERSON
133	23	Grayson	NNP	Grayson	PERSON
133	24	,	,	,	O
133	25	the	DT	the	O
133	26	speedy	NN	speedy	O
133	27	halfback	NN	halfback	O
133	28	,	,	,	O
133	29	hit	VBD	hit	O
133	30	him	PRP	him	O
133	31	and	CC	and	O
133	32	Guard	NNP	Guard	O
133	33	Al	NNP	Al	PERSON
133	34	Reynolds	NNP	Reynolds	PERSON
133	35	claimed	VBD	claim	O
133	36	it	PRP	it	O
133	37	for	IN	for	O
133	38	Dallas	NNP	Dallas	LOCATION
133	39	.	.	.	O

13	22	colleague
13	33	colleague
22	33	colleague

134	0	Nischwitz	NNP	Nischwitz	PERSON
134	1	fanned	VBD	fan	O
134	2	six	CD	six	O
134	3	and	CC	and	O
134	4	walked	VBD	walk	O
134	5	only	RB	only	O
134	6	Charley	NNP	Charley	PERSON
134	7	Hinton	NNP	Hinton	PERSON
134	8	in	IN	in	O
134	9	the	DT	the	O
134	10	third	JJ	third	O
134	11	inning	NN	inning	O
134	12	.	.	.	O

0	6	colleague

135	0	Dick	NNP	Dick	PERSON
135	1	McAuliffe	NNP	McAuliffe	PERSON
135	2	cracked	VBD	crack	O
135	3	the	DT	the	O
135	4	first	JJ	first	O
135	5	of	IN	of	O
135	6	his	PRP$	his	O
135	7	two	CD	two	O
135	8	doubles	NNS	double	O
135	9	against	IN	against	O
135	10	Lefty	NNP	Lefty	O
135	11	Don	NNP	Don	PERSON
135	12	Rudolph	NNP	Rudolph	PERSON
135	13	to	TO	to	O
135	14	open	VB	open	O
135	15	the	DT	the	O
135	16	Bear's	NNP	Bear's	O
135	17	attack	NN	attack	O
135	18	.	.	.	O

0	11	colleague

136	0	After	IN	After	O
136	1	Al	NNP	Al	PERSON
136	2	Paschal	NNP	Paschal	PERSON
136	3	gruonded	VBD	gruonded	O
136	4	out	RP	out	O
136	5	,	,	,	O
136	6	Jay	NNP	Jay	PERSON
136	7	Cooke	NNP	Cooke	PERSON
136	8	walked	VBD	walk	O
136	9	and	CC	and	O
136	10	Jim	NNP	Jim	PERSON
136	11	McDaniel	NNP	McDaniel	PERSON
136	12	singled	VBD	single	O
136	13	home	NN	home	O
136	14	McAuliffe	NNP	McAuliffe	PERSON
136	15	.	.	.	O

1	6	colleague
1	10	colleague
1	14	colleague
6	10	colleague
6	14	colleague
10	14	colleague

137	0	Alusik	NNP	Alusik	PERSON
137	1	then	RB	then	O
137	2	moved	VBD	move	O
137	3	Cooke	NNP	Cooke	PERSON
137	4	across	IN	across	O
137	5	with	IN	with	O
137	6	a	DT	a	O
137	7	line	NN	line	O
137	8	drive	NN	drive	O
137	9	to	TO	to	O
137	10	left	VB	leave	O
137	11	.	.	.	O

0	3	colleague

138	0	Jay	NNP	Jay	PERSON
138	1	Porter	NNP	Porter	PERSON
138	2	drew	VBD	draw	O
138	3	a	DT	a	O
138	4	base	NN	base	O
138	5	on	IN	on	O
138	6	balls	NNS	ball	O
138	7	to	TO	to	O
138	8	fill	VB	fill	O
138	9	the	DT	the	O
138	10	bases	NNS	base	O
138	11	but	CC	but	O
138	12	Don	NNP	Don	PERSON
138	13	Wert's	NNP	Wert's	PERSON
138	14	smash	NN	smash	O
138	15	was	VBD	be	O
138	16	knocked	VBN	knock	O
138	17	down	RP	down	O
138	18	by	IN	by	O
138	19	Rudolph	NNP	Rudolph	PERSON
138	20	for	IN	for	O
138	21	the	DT	the	O
138	22	putout	NN	putout	O
138	23	.	.	.	O

0	12	colleague
0	19	colleague
12	19	colleague

139	0	The	DT	The	O
139	1	Bears	NNP	Bears	O
139	2	added	VBD	add	O
139	3	two	CD	two	O
139	4	more	JJR	more	O
139	5	in	IN	in	O
139	6	the	DT	the	O
139	7	fifth	NN	fifth	O
139	8	when	WRB	when	O
139	9	McAuliffe	NNP	McAuliffe	PERSON
139	10	dropped	VBD	drop	O
139	11	a	DT	a	O
139	12	double	JJ	double	O
139	13	into	IN	into	O
139	14	the	DT	the	O
139	15	leftfield	NN	leftfield	O
139	16	corner	NN	corner	O
139	17	,	,	,	O
139	18	Paschal	NNP	Paschal	PERSON
139	19	doubled	VBD	double	O
139	20	down	RP	down	O
139	21	the	DT	the	O
139	22	rightfield	NN	rightfield	O
139	23	line	NN	line	O
139	24	and	CC	and	O
139	25	Cooke	NNP	Cooke	PERSON
139	26	singled	VBD	single	O
139	27	off	RP	off	O
139	28	Phil	NNP	Phil	PERSON
139	29	Shartzer's	NNP	Shartzer's	PERSON
139	30	glove	NN	glove	O
139	31	.	.	.	O

25	28	colleague

140	0	Chuck	NNP	Chuck	PERSON
140	1	Hinton	NNP	Hinton	PERSON
140	2	tripled	VBD	triple	O
140	3	to	TO	to	O
140	4	the	DT	the	O
140	5	rightfield	NN	rightfield	O
140	6	corner	NN	corner	O
140	7	,	,	,	O
140	8	Cliff	NNP	Cliff	PERSON
140	9	Cook	NNP	Cook	PERSON
140	10	and	CC	and	O
140	11	Dan	NNP	Dan	PERSON
140	12	Pavletich	NNP	Pavletich	PERSON
140	13	singled	VBD	single	O
140	14	and	CC	and	O
140	15	Gaines'	NNP	Gaines'	O
140	16	infield	VBP	infield	O
140	17	roller	NN	roller	O
140	18	accounted	VBD	account	O
140	19	for	IN	for	O
140	20	the	DT	the	O
140	21	tallies	NNS	tally	O
140	22	.	.	.	O

0	8	colleague
0	11	colleague
8	11	colleague

141	0	The	DT	The	O
141	1	Bears	NNP	Bears	O
141	2	added	VBD	add	O
141	3	their	PRP$	their	O
141	4	last	JJ	last	O
141	5	run	NN	run	O
141	6	in	IN	in	O
141	7	the	DT	the	O
141	8	sixth	JJ	sixth	O
141	9	on	IN	on	O
141	10	Alusik's	NNP	Alusik's	O
141	11	double	JJ	double	O
141	12	and	CC	and	O
141	13	outfield	JJ	outfield	O
141	14	flies	NNS	fly	O
141	15	by	IN	by	O
141	16	Porter	NNP	Porter	PERSON
141	17	and	CC	and	O
141	18	Wert	NNP	Wert	PERSON
141	19	.	.	.	O

16	18	colleague
